<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Imprint>
			<Army>The Empire</Army>
			<Edition>8</Edition>
			<Released>2011</Released>
			<Authors>Robin Cruddace</Authors>
			<Description>The Empire, sometimes referred to as the Empire of Man, is an electoral monarchy composed of feudal states that is the largest and most important of the Human nations in the Old World. It was forged by the warrior-king and ascended deity Sigmar from the primitive tribes of Human barbarians who inhabited what became the lands of the southern Empire more than 2500 years ago.\n\nAlthough not as skilled in craftsmanship as the Dwarfs or in magic as the High Elves, the people of the Empire are not beholden by the limits of tradition to the same extent as those elder races and continue to progress culturally, technologically and magically.\n\nHaving yet to succumb to any threat, external or internal, it is the faith, the sense of righteousness, and the unconquerable spirit of the realm's citizens which gives the Empire its strength, as well as the ruthless efficiency of its military and religious orders</Description>
		</Imprint>
		<Styles>
			<Colors>
				<Front>5d0e0e</Front>
				<Back>b61b1b</Back>
				<Grid>e6c7c7</Grid>
				<Tooltip>d69393</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>9d6e6e, 7d3e3e, 6d2626</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<Images>
				<Files>
					<Cover/>
					<Symbol/>
					<Illustration/>
				</Files>
				<Folders>
					<Units/>
				</Folders>
			</Images>
		</Styles>
		<Naming>
			<Internal>Empire</Internal>
			<MagicItems>Heirlooms of Magic</MagicItems>
			<Buttons>
				<Add>no, sir!</Add>
				<Drop>yes, sir!</Drop>
			</Buttons>
		</Naming>
		<Magic>
			<Name>The Lore of Fire</Name>
			<Options>Any of eight Lore of Battle Magic</Options>
			<Magic>
				<Spell Name="Fireball" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Cascading Fire-Cloak" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Flaming Sword of Rhuin" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="The Burning Head" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Piercing Bolts of Burning" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Fulminating Flame Cage" Cast="11"/>
				<Spell Name="Flame Storm" Cast="13"/>
			</Magic>
			<Enemy>Daemons of Chaos, The Lore of Nurgle</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Miasma of Pestilence" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Ream of Corruption" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Blades of Putrefaction" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Curse of The Leper" Cast="12"/>
				<Spell Name="Rancid Visitations" Cast="12"/>
				<Spell Name="Fleshy Abundance" Cast="13"/>
				<Spell Name="Plague Wind" Cast="17"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<Local>
			<SpecialRules>
				<Cannon/>
				<Mortar/>
				<Helblaster/>
				<RegimentalUnit/>
				<Detachment/>
				<FastCavalry/>
			</SpecialRules>
			<Options>
				<Pistol/>
				<Handgun/>
				<FullPlateArmour>
					AddToArmour: 4
				</FullPlateArmour>
				<Barding>
					Name: Barding for Warhorse
					AddToArmour: 6
				</Barding>
				<GrenadeBlunderbuss/>
				<HochlandLongRifle/>
				<PigeonBombs/>
				<RepeaterHandgun/>
				<RepeaterPistol/>
				<Bloodroar>
					Rule: Enemy units must roll an additional D6, discarding the lowest result, for Leadership tests caused by this beast's Fear of Terror special rules
					AddToArmour: 6
				</Bloodroar>
				<TwoHeads>
					AddToAttacks: 1
					Rule: +1 To Hit against models with the Large Target special rule
				</TwoHeads>
				<IronHardHoove>
					Name: Iron-hard Hoove
					Rule: Re-rolls failed To Wound rolls when making a Stomp
				</IronHardHoove>
				<SwiftWind>
					Name: Swift as the Wind
					Rule: Re-roll ant dice results of a 1 when determining its charge range
				</SwiftWind>
			</Options>
		</Local>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<Heirlooms Name="Heirlooms of Magic">
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Runefang</Name>
					<Points>85</Points>
					<NoArmour/>
					<AutoWound/>
					<Description>All hits from a Runefang wound automatically and allow no armour saves</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Mace of Helsturm</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="10"/>
					<AttacksTo Val="1"/>
					<MultiWounds Val="D3"/>
					<HitLast/>
					<Description>Always Strikes Last. Requires Two Hands. The wielder of this weapon strikes at +2 Strength in close combat. Instead of attacking normally, the bearer can choose to forfeit all of his normal Attacks to make a single, special Attack (which still has the Always Strikes Last special rule). If this Attack hits, it is resolved at Strength 10 and has both the Flaming Attacks and Multiple Wounds (D3) special rules</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Meteoric Iron</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<ArmourTo Val="1"/>
					<AddToWard Val="6"/>
					<Description>The Armour of Meteoric Iron grants the wearer both a 1+ armour save (that cannot be improved by any means) and a 6+ ward save</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Helm of the Skavenslayer</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Fear/>
					<Rule>Causes Terror in all models in a Skaven army</Rule>
					<Description>Helm. The wearer of the Helm of the Skavenslayer counts his armour save as being one point higher than normal. The wearer also causes Fear. Against models from a Skaven army, the wearer causes Terror instead. However, all Skaven gain the Hatred special rule while attacking the wearer</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>The White Cloak of Ulric</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<SubOpponentToHit Val="1"/>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Rule>2+ Ward save against Flaming Attacks</Rule>
					<Description>Enemies in base contact with the wearer are at -1 to all rolls To Hit. In addition, the wearer has a 5+ ward save, increasing to a 2+ ward save against Wounds caused by Flaming Attacks</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Van Horstmann's Speculum</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>When the wearer fights in a challenge, he must 'swap' the Strength, Toughness, Initiative and Attacks characteristics on his profile with his enemy</Rule>
					<Description>When the wearer fights in a challenge, he must 'swap' the Strength, Toughness, Initiative and Attacks characteristics on his profile with his enemy (but not the enemy's mount, if he has one). So, the wearer fights with his enemy's Strength, Toughness, Initiative and Attacks whilst his enemy fights with the wearer's Strength, Toughness, Initiative and Attacks. Note that you cannot choose not to use Van Horstmann's Speculum and you must swap all of the listed characteristics for the duration of the challenge, not just some of them</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Ring of Volans</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>Bound Spell, Power Level variable, one use only: at the beginning of the game, choose one of the eight Lores of Magic</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. Bound Spell (power level variable). At the beginning of the game, choose one of the eight Lores of Magic from the Warhammer rulebook and generate a spell from it as if the bearer were a Level 1 Wizard. That spell is bound within the Ring of Volans and can lie cast, just like a bound spell, with a power level equal to the normal casting value of the spell</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Griffon Standard</Name>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Rule>A unit counts double its rank bonus when it comes to working out combat results</Rule>
					<Description>A unit joined by a character bearing the Griffon Banner doubles any combat result bonus granted for having extra ranks. However, a character carrying the Griffon Banner, and his unit, cannot pursue a fleeing enemy and must hold their ground instead</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Steel Standard</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>The character and his unit ignore any negative Movement penalties for barding</Rule>
					<Rule>Re-roll any dice rolls of a 1 when determining the distance they charge, flee or pursue</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer of the Steel Standard and his unit ignore any negative Movement penalties for barding (it they have any), and re-roll any dice rolls of a 1 when determining the distance they charge, flee or pursue</Description>
				</Banner>
			</Heirlooms>
			<CommonMagicWeapons>
				<GiantBlade Points="60"/>
				<SwordOfBloodshed Points="60"/>
				<ObsidianBlade Points="50"/>
				<OgreBlade Points="40"/>
				<SwordOfStrife Points="40"/>
				<FencersBlades Points="35"/>
				<SwordOfAntiHeroes Points="30"/>
				<SpellthievingSword Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfSwiftSlaying Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfBattle Points="20"/>
				<BerserkerSword Points="20"/>
				<SwordOfMight Points="20"/>
				<GoldSigilSword Points="15"/>
				<SwordOfStriking Points="15"/>
				<BitingBlade Points="10"/>
				<RelicSword Points="10"/>
				<ShriekingBlade Points="10"/>
				<TormentorSword Points="5"/>
				<WarriorBane Points="5"/>
			</CommonMagicWeapons>
			<CommonMagicArmours>
				<ArmourOfDestiny Points="50"/>
				<TrickstersHelm Points="50"/>
				<ArmourOfSilveredSteel Points="50"/>
				<ArmourOfFortune Points="35"/>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Helm of Discord</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Test Bet="Pass" Context="Round" Profile="Leadership"/>
					<Description>The wearer counts his armour save as being one point higher than normal. In addition, at the start of each Close Combat phase, choose an enemy character in base contact with the bearer or his unit. That character must immediately take a Leadership test. If the test is failed, the character succumbs to the helm's sibilant whispers of malice and jealousy. In this Close Combat phase, the victim cannot make attacks and is hit automatically</Description>
				</Additional>
				<GlitteringScales Points="25"/>
				<ShieldOfPtolos Points="25"/>
				<Spellshield Points="20"/>
				<GamblersArmour Points="20"/>
				<Dragonhelm Points="10"/>
				<EnchantedShield Points="5"/>
				<CharmedShield Points="5"/>
			</CommonMagicArmours>
			<CommonMagicTalismans>
				<TalismanOfPreservation Points="45"/>
				<ObsidianLodestone Points="30"/>
				<TalismanOfEndurance Points="30"/>
				<Dawnstone Points="25"/>
				<OpalAmulet Points="15"/>
				<ObsidianTrinket Points="15"/>
				<TalismanOfProtection Points="15"/>
				<SeedOfRebirt Points="10"/>
				<DragonbaneGem Points="5"/>
				<PidgeonPluckerPendant Points="5"/>
				<Luckstone Points="5"/>
			</CommonMagicTalismans>
			<CommonArcaneItems>
				<BookOfAshur Points="70"/>
				<FeedbackScroll Points="50"/>
				<ScrollOfLeeching Points="50"/>
				<SivejirsHexScroll Points="50"/>
				<PowerScroll Points="50"/>
				<WandOfJet Points="35"/>
				<ForbiddenRod Points="35"/>
				<TrickstersShard Points="25"/>
				<EarthingRod Points="25"/>
				<DispellScroll Points="25"/>
				<PowerStone Points="20"/>
				<SceptreOfStability Points="15"/>
				<ChannellingStaff Points="15"/>
				<ScrollOfShielding Points="15"/>
			</CommonArcaneItems>
			<CommonEnchantedItems>
				<WizardingHat Points="100"/>
				<FozzriksFoldingFortress Points="100"/>
				<ArabyanCarpet Points="50"/>
				<CrownOfCommand Points="35"/>
				<HealingPotion Points="35"/>
				<FeatherfoeTorc Points="35"/>
				<RubyRingOfRuin Points="25"/>
				<TheTerrifyingMaskOfEee Points="25"/>
				<PotionOfStrength Points="20"/>
				<PotionOfToughness Points="20"/>
				<TheOtherTrickstersShard Points="15"/>
				<IroncurseIcon Points="5"/>
				<PotionOfFoolhardiness Points="5"/>
				<PotionOfSpeed Points="5"/>
			</CommonEnchantedItems>
			<CommonMagicStandards>
				<RampagersStandard Points="55"/>
				<WailingBanner Points="50"/>
				<RangersStandard Points="50"/>
				<RazorStandard Points="45"/>
				<WarBanner Points="35"/>
				<BannerOfSwiftness Points="15"/>
				<LichebonePennant Points="15"/>
				<StandardOfDiscipline Points="15"/>
				<BannerOfEternalFlame Points="10"/>
				<GleamingPennant Points="5"/>
				<ScarecrowBanner Points="5"/>
			</CommonMagicStandards>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Karl Franz</Name>
				<Points>340</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Karl Franz, also sometimes styled Karl-Franz or Karl Franz I, Protector of the Empire, Defiler of the Dark, Emperor Himself and the Son of Emperors, Elector Count of Reikland, and prince of Altdorf, is the current emperor of the Empire and the greatest statesman and general the Empire or perhaps the entire Old World has seen in many centuries. Karl Franz, who was elected to the Imperial title in 2502 IC and inherited it from his father, Luitpold I, is acclaimed as a patron of the arts and science, as a military innovator, and as a valiant general. Thanks to his tireless efforts on the behalf of its people, the Empire has flourished during his reign like never before: the Imperial Engineers School in Altdorf has grown, the Colleges of Magic have thrived and his armies have marched from victory to victory, most recently during the terrible events of the Storm of Chaos. The Emperor frequently takes personal command of his troops, wielding Ghal Maraz, the fabled magical warhammer given to Sigmar himself by the Dwarf king Kurgan Ironbeard over two thousand years ago, or his Runefang sword, and riding atop Deathclaw, his Griffon mount of many years.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='6' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='6' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<General/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Hold the Line!</Rule>
						<Rule>Leader of Men</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
					<Armour>
						<Name>The Silver Seal</Name>
						<AddToWard Val="4"/>
						<MagicResistance Val="3"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>The Reikland Runefang</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<AutoWound/>
						<Dependency/>
						<RealisedByDefault/>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Ghal Maraz</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<AutoWound/>
						<MultiWounds Val="D3"/>
						<Points>30</Points>
						<Dependency/>
					</Option>
					<Mount Name="Deathclaw" Points="225"/>
					<Mount Name="The Imperial Dragon" Points="300"/>
					<Mount Name="Imperial Pegasus" Points="45"/>
					<Mount Name="Warhorse" Points="18"/>
					<Barding Points="6" For="Warhorse"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Kurt Helborg</Name>
				<Points>320</Points>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Kurk Helborg, is Karl Franz's closest friend, and one of the greatest military minds in the entire Empire. He is known by most as the Reikmarshal, having full authority when it comes to military affairs, second only in command to the Emperor himself. Kurt is an exceptional warrior as well as a leader and tactican, and has been responsible for leading many battles against the Empire's foes from as far north as Kislev to the furthest south as Araby.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='7' BS='6' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='6' A='4' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Stubborn/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Original>The Emperor's Chosen</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>The Solland Runefang</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<AutoWound/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Laurels of Victory</Name>
						<Rule>Each unsaved Wound caused counts as 2 when calculating the combat result</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Balthasar Gelt</Name>
				<Points>360</Points>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Mount>Imperial Pegasus</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Balthasar Gelt or with his full title, Supreme Patriarch Balthasar Gelt, is one of the Colleges of Magic's most powerful and skillful Wizards of the Gold College and some say, the entire city of Altdorf. Such is his skill in the art of magic that he managed to defeat the former Supreme Patriarch, Thyrus Gormann of the Bright Order, in single combat, replacing the long-standing prominence of Fire with that of Metal.</Description>
				<Image>Balthasar</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='3' I='3' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>Loremaster</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>The Staff of Volans</Name>
						<Rule>+2 to the casting</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<RangeWeapon>
						<Name>Al-kahest</Name>
						<Rule>Attack with range of 6", wounding any target on a 4+, no armour save</Rule>
					</RangeWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>The Cloak of Molten Metal</Name>
						<Rule>3+ Ward save against shooting attacks</Rule>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Amulet of Sea Gold</Name>
						<MagicResistance Val="1"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Volkmar The Grim</Name>
				<Points>190</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Volkmar is the current Grand Theogonist of the Empire, and the leading spiritual leader of the Church of Sigmar. This man has a great aura of influence wherever he goes: such is his reputation that if he wished, he could call an army of followers and zealots onto his banner, who are ready to die for their great leader and prophet. A pious and foreboding man, this man's entire life was bent on holding back the darkness assailing his homeland, never tiring nor resting in his vigil over his own people.</Description>
				<Image>Volkmar</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='5' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Battle Prayers</Rule>
						<Rule>Divine Power</Rule>
						<Rule>Righteous Fury</Rule>
						<Rule>+1 bonus attempt to cast a Battle Prayer</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Staff of Command</Name>
						<Rule>+2 to Strength if mounted upon the War Altar</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<LightArmour/>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Jade Griffon</Name>
						<Regeneration/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>The War Altar</Name>
						<Points>150</Points>
						<Mount/>
						<OnlyOneInArmy/>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Marius Leitdorf</Name>
				<Points>220</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Description>Marius Leitdorf also known as Elector Count Marius Lietdorf of Averland "the Mad", is both a Count of the Empire and also as an exceptional swordsman and leader, but having a known reputation of being mentally-ill, often screaming in rage one moment, then having a period of melancholy and laughter a moment later.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='6' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='5' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Hold the Line!</Rule>
						<Rule>The Mad Count</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>The Averland Runefang</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<AutoWound/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Hand weapon</Name>
						<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Jade Griffon</Name>
						<Regeneration/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>General of the Empire</Name>
				<Points>95</Points>
				<Image>General</Image>
				<Description>Empire Generals are amongst the highest commanding officers within a Imperial army, second only in command to an Elector Count or the Emperor himself. These officers vary greatly in rank, depending on the size of the force they lead, and are usually known within the Empire as captains, marshals, generals or sometimes simply commanders. Regardless of their social status, they will be tested veterans of many years of experience in soldiering, having spent most of their lives practicing the arts of war in defence of their besieged homelands.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='5' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='5' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<Original>Hold the Line!</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightNativeArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="3" Only="Infantry" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Lance Points="7" Only="Mount" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Handgun Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Longbow Points="5" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Pistol Points="5" Dependency="Weapon"/>				
					<FullPlateArmour Points="9" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
					<Mount Name="Imperial Griffon" Points="170"/>
					<Mount Name="Imperial Pegasus" Points="45"/>
					<Mount Name="Warhorse" Points="18"/>
					<Option>
						<Name>Barding for warhorse</Name>
						<Dependencies>
							<On>Warhorse</On>
						</Dependencies>
						<Points>6</Points>
						<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Battle Wizard Lord</Name>
				<Points>165</Points>
				<Wizard>3</Wizard>
				<Image>WizardLord</Image>
				<Description>A Wizard Lord is a highly prestigious rank within the Imperial Colleges of Magic that are second only to the Matriarch or Patriach of a Magic Order. A being of immense but unstable power, these mighty Men of the Empire are amongst the strongest particioner's of magic within the realms of Man. Such is their great knowledge at their perfered Magic Lore that these Wizards are accompanied by a whole cadre of lesser Wizards and Adepts, using their magical abilities to further augment the Wizard Lords already formidable powers into ever grander strenght.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='3' I='3' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Wizard"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="4" Points="35"/>
					<Mount Name="Imperial Pegasus" Points="45"/>
					<Mount Name="Warhorse" Points="18"/>
					<Option>
						<Name>Barding for Warhorse</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
						<Dependencies>
							<On>Warhorse</On>
						</Dependencies>
						<Points>6</Points>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Celestail Hurricanum</Name>
						<Points>125</Points>
						<Rule>May choose spells only from the Lore of Heaven</Rule>
						<Mount/>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Luminark of Hysh</Name>
						<Points>120</Points>
						<Rule>May choose spells only from the Lore of Light</Rule>
						<Mount/>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Imperial Griffon</Name>
						<Points>170</Points>
						<Rule>May choose spells only from the Lore of Beasts</Rule>
						<Mount/>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Arch Lector</Name>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<Description>An Arch Lector of Sigmar is one of the highest positions within the hierarchy of the Church of Sigmar, second only to the Grand Theogonist in terms of his political and religious authority. These men are the very embodiedment of both strenght and faith in their warrior diety Sigmar.  When war calls the High Priests of Sigmar to battle, it is an awe-inspiring sight to see them ride at the head of an army atop the mighty War Altar of Sigmar. </Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<Hate/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Battle Prayers</Rule>
						<Rule>Divine Power</Rule>
						<Rule>Righteous Fury</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightNativeArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="3" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4"/>
					<Shield Points="4"/>
					<Option>
						<Name>The War Altar</Name>
						<Points>150</Points>
						<Mount/>
						<OnlyOneInArmy/>
					</Option>
					<Mount Name="Warhorse" Points="18"/>
					<Barding Points="6" For="Warhorse"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Grand Master</Name>
				<Points>155</Points>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Description>A Grand Master is a warrior and leader of unparalleled valour, having fought in dozens of battles from atop his great warhorse and whose military prowess is beyond question. These mighty warriors are the leaders of one of the many prestigious Knightly Orders that populate many of the Empire's lands, a position of power suited for only the most wisest and martialed member of their Order.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='6' BS='6' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='6' A='4' Ld='9' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Original>Master of Battle</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Lance Points="7" Only="Mount" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Shield Points="4"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Ludwig Schwarzhelm</Name>
				<Points>185</Points>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Lugwig, also known as the Emperor's Champion is another close friend of Emperor Karl Franz and bodyguard to his lord. Not only is he a very skillful swordsman, but he is also the envoy of Karl Franz himself, often acting as his emissary towards several other provinces for political reasons, such as an edict the supposed lord has refused to accept or to uphold the Emperor's justice.</Description>
				<Image>Schwarzhelm</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='6' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='5' A='3' Ld='8' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<NotALeader/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>The Emperor's Bodyguard</Rule>
						<Rule>The Emperor's Herald</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Sword of Justice</Name>
						<Reroll>ToWound</Reroll>
						<KillingBlow/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Luthor Huss</Name>
				<Points>155</Points>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Luthor Huss known by some as the Prophet of Sigmar, is one of the Empire's most devout and zealous Warrior Priests across the land. His desire to smite chaos and all its forms drove this Warrior Priest to scorch the land of Beastmen tribes, Chaos cults, and Imperial corruption wherever he goes. Though his deeds were just, his actions have unveiled the corruption from within the Church of Sigmar itself, and it came to pass that an Arch Lector has asked the Grand Theogonist himself to excommunicate this man. Yet the Theogonist was a just man himself, and knew something about Luthor Huss that no one else knows about, and with a smile upon hearing his deeds, he dismisses the ordeal.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='5' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='4' A='2' Ld='8' AS='5' Ward='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Hate/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Battle Prayers</Rule>
						<Rule>Divine Power</Rule>
						<Rule>Righteous Fury</Rule>
						<Rule>Chosen of Sigmar</Rule>
						<Rule>Fiery Demagogue</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Massive warhammer</Name>
						<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
						<HitLast/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Markus Wulfheart</Name>
				<Points>140</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Markus Wulfhart, known by his title as the Huntmarshal, is the Emperor's "Captain of Scouts" and one of the most successful hunters and monster slayers in the entire Old World. Markus was originally an ordinary inhabitant of the village of Drakenburg, situated within the deepest forest lands of the Middenland province.</Description>
				<Image>Wulfhart</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='5' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='5' A='3' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Hate/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Scouts/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Wulfhart's Hunters</Rule>
						<Rule>Re-roll all failed To Hit rolls when shooting at monsters</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>
						<Name>The Amber Bow</Name>
						<Rule>Range weapon with range 30" and Strength 3 and Volley Fire special rule; if shot hits a monster, it always wound on 4+ and has Multi Wounds (D3) special rule</Rule>
					</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Captain of the Empire</Name>
				<Points>60</Points>
				<Image>Captain</Image>
				<Description>A Captain of the Empire is a veteran military commander possessed of a variety of different formal titles who leads a smaller regiment or other unit of troops within an Imperial army. These leaders take to the field of battle whenever they can. Most of the men appointed by an Elector Count to serve as officers in their province's armies will also be nobles of the Empire, educated in martial pursuits from an early age, whilst others are simply high-born cowards with no courage or leadership.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='5' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='5' A='3' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<Original>Hold the Line!</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightNativeArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="3" Only="Infantry" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Lance Points="7" Only="Mount" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Handgun Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Longbow Points="5" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Pistol Points="5" Dependency="Weapon"/>				
					<FullPlateArmour Points="6" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="2" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
					<Mount Name="Imperial Pegasus" Points="45"/>
					<Mount Name="Warhorse" Points="12"/>
					<Barding Points="4" For="Warhorse"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Battle Wizard</Name>
				<Points>65</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Image>Wizard</Image>
				<Description>Empire Battle Wizards are individuals with the knowledge and power of one of the great Winds of Magic, who has been schooled from one of the eight Colleges of Magic within the capital of Altdorf, and are now giving their services to the Empire.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='2' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Wizard"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="2" Points="35"/>
					<Mount Name="Warhorse" Points="12"/>
					<Barding Points="4" For="Warhorse"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Warrior Priest</Name>
				<Points>65</Points>
				<Description>Warrior Priests are a war-like sect of the Church of Sigmar who not only lead and inspire Imperial troops in battle, but also minister to their spiritual needs. On many an occasion a rousing speech by a Warrior Priest of Sigmar has restored the troops' faith, brought hope to a seemingly lost cause, or prevented a mutiny when the words of even the most respected commanders had fallen on frightened and angry ears. Warrior Priests of Sigmar normally wear mail or full plate armour underneath their holy vestments, wield the mighty warhammers that are the favoured weapon of Sigmar, and ride into battle atop powerful Imperial warhorses. Among the most commonly employed divine powers of a Warrior Priest are prayers.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='4' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<Hate/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Battle Prayers</Rule>
						<Rule>Divine Power</Rule>
						<Rule>Righteous Fury</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightNativeArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="2" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="5" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="2"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
					<Mount Name="Warhorse" Points="12"/>
					<Barding Points="4" For="Warhorse"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Master Engineer</Name>
				<Points>65</Points>
				<Image>Engineer</Image>
				<Description>Empire Master Engineers are those select few individuals amongst many thousand that have the knowledge and skills to create, maintain and operate wonderous inventions of war in the battle against the Empire's foes. These Engineers are highly schooled in mathematics and engineering, having the skills to direct artillery pieces into position and calibrating them to their full potential.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Master of Ballistics</Rule>
						<Rule>'Stand back, Sir!'</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GrenadeBlunderbuss Points="10" Dependency="Range"/>
					<HochlandLongRifle Points="20" Dependency="Range"/>
					<PigeonBombs Points="20" Dependency="Range"/>
					<RepeaterHandgun Points="10" Dependency="Range"/>
					<RepeaterPistol Points="10" Dependency="Range"/>
					<Pistol Points="5" Dependency="Range"/>
					<LightArmour Points="1"/>
					<Mount Name="Mechanical Steed" Points="25"/>
					<Mount Name="Warhorse" Points="12"/>
					<Barding Points="2" For="Warhorse"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Witch Hunter</Name>
				<Points>50</Points>
				<Description>Witch Hunters are highly dreaded figures in the lands of the Empire, feared by both enemies and allies alike. These zealous warriors are part of the Church of Sigmar, also known as the Order of Sigmar, whose job is to eradicate and kill any if not all Chaos Worshippers that dare to defile the lands of the God-King Sigmar of Old.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='4' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<MagicResistance Val="2"/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Accusation</Rule>
						<Rule>Grim Resolve</Rule>
						<Rule>Tools of Judgement</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Pistol</Name>
						<Dependency/>
						<RealisedByDefault/>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Brace of pistols</Name>
						<Points>5</Points>
						<Dependency/>
					</Option>
					<GreatWeapon Points="5"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Warhorse</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Mechanical Steed</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='1' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='1' A='1' Ld='0'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ImpactHit Val="D3"/>
					<Original>Unreliable</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Demigryph</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='4' BS='0' S='5' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='3' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ArmourPiercing Val="1"/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Imperial Griffon</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='5' BS='0' S='6' T='5' W='5' I='4' A='4' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<Fly/>
					<LargeTarget/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Bloodroar Points="25"/>
					<TwoHeads Points="30"/>
				</Options>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Imperial Pegasus</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<IronHardHoove Points="5"/>
					<SwiftWind Points="10"/>
				</Options>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Celestail Hurricanum</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='1' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<AddToHit Val="1"/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Locus of Azyr</Rule>
						<Rule>Portents of Battle</Rule>
						<Rule>Storm of Shemtek</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Luminark of Hysh</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='1' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Locus of Hysh</Rule>
						<Rule>Solheim's Bolt of Illumination</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Arcane>
						<Rule>All friendly units within 6" have a 6+ Ward save</Rule>
						<AddToWard Val="6"/>
					</Arcane>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>The War Altar</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='1' Ld='5' AS='5' Ward='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Stubborn/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Golden Griffon</Rule>
						<Rule>Holy Fervour</Rule>
						<Rule>The Power of Sigmar</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Horn of Sigismund</Name>
						<Points>10</Points>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Deathclaw</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='0' S='6' T='5' W='5' I='4' A='5' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Bloodroar</Rule>
						<Rule>Loyal Beast</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>The Imperial Dragon</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='0' S='6' T='6' W='6' I='3' A='5' Ld='8' AS='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>Fiery Breath</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Halberdiers</Name>
				<Points>6</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Halberdiers are amongst the three most common infantry types fielded by the armies of the Empire. Equipped with a battle-worn halberd, these groups of line infantry are a powerful force on the battlefield, proving the Empire with both offensive and defensive capability with bone-crushing force.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<RegimentalUnit/>
					<Detachment/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Halberd/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Sergeant"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Spearmen</Name>
				<Points>5</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>Spearmans</Image>
				<Description>Spearmen are amongst the three most common infantry types fielded by the armies of the Empire. Equipped with a spear and shield, the solid formation that this unit provides is highly adequate in defensive situations, providing the Empire with much-needed holding power.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<RegimentalUnit/>
					<Detachment/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Spear/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Sergeant"/>
						<Musician/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Swordmen</Name>
				<Points>7</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>Swordman</Image>
				<Description>Swordsmen are amongst the three most common infantry types fielded by the armies of the Empire. Equipped with a sword, shield, and half-plate armor, these brave soldiers often engage the best enemy with both valor and courage. Due to their expertise with the sword and their flexible formation, the Swordsmen of the Empire provides the military with reliable offensive capability.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<RegimentalUnit/>
					<Detachment/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Sword</HandWeapon>
					<LightArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Duellist"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Crossbowmen</Name>
				<Points>9</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>Crossbowman</Image>
				<Description>Crossbowmen are the least most common ranged units following the introduction of gunpowder weaponry. In the past, Crossbowmen provided the Empire with a stronger degree of peneration against heavily-armored foes. As of now, some provinces still retain the use of Crossbows as a substitute should Handguns be unavailable.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<RegimentalUnit/>
					<Detachment/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Crossbow</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Marksman"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Handgunners</Name>
				<Points>9</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Handgunners are one of the primaries ranged units of the Imperial army. Equipped with the loud and deadly handgun, these men are highly trained as a line-formation of missile support that can penetrate even the thickest of enemy armor. As such, they are the mainstay of most Imperial missile support.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<RegimentalUnit/>
					<Detachment/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Handgun</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Marksman"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
					<Option>
						<Name>Brace pistols for Marksman</Name>
						<Dependencies>
							<On>Marksman</On>
							<Off>Hochland long rifle for Marksman, Repeater handgun for Marksman</Off>
						</Dependencies>
						<Points>5</Points>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Hochland long rifle for Marksman</Name>
						<Dependencies>
							<On>Marksman</On>
							<Off>Repeater handgun for Marksman, Brace pistols for Marksman</Off>
						</Dependencies>
						<Points>20</Points>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Repeater handgun for Marksman</Name>
						<Dependencies>
							<On>Marksman</On>
							<Off>Hochland long rifle for Marksman, Brace pistols for Marksman</Off>
						</Dependencies>
						<Points>10</Points>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Archers</Name>
				<Points>7</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Archers are an often irregular group of hunters and trappers that usually band together to form their own regiment of scouts and support units. The more experienced and exceptional hunters and archers hail from the woodland province of Hochland, where hunting is a very popular sport amongst both the nobility and commoner alike. These men are often fielded when regiments of crossbowmen and handgunners are in short supply.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<RegimentalUnit/>
					<Detachment/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Bow/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Marksman"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Free Company Militia</Name>
				<Points>6</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>Freecompany</Image>
				<Description>A Free Company is a polite catch-all term to describe all sell-swords, mercenaries, cut-throats, and bandits paid to fight for the Empire and her armies. They are hardy fighters and are well-accustomed to the rigours of war, but are undisciplined and unruly, liable to cause more harm than good when roaming around in armed bands. An Elector Count might employ these men for military service, but must ensure such men are under close watch to prevent them from running amok in his lands.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Detachment/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Militia Leader"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Knightly Orders</Name>
				<Points>22</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Description>Knights are one of the most common cavalry troops deployed in battle. Many knights have a certain color scheme or heraldry that identifies them with either a knightly order or a noble household. They are considered heavy shock cavalry, wearing heavy plate armor and wielding lances and swords into battle. Knights tend to be born from the nobler families of the Empire, a tradition that is often kept and practiced by most Knightly Orders. Those of common birth who are exceptionally-skilled with a weapon often serves as sergeants and squires for their knights. Although not considered full brothers of their orders, sergeants and squires play vital roles in supporting the knights in battle, and are often equally respected for their prowess in battle.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='8' AS='5'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Knights of the Inner Circle</Name>
						<PointsPerModel>3</PointsPerModel>
						<AddToStrength Val="1"/>
						<OnlyOneInArmy/>
					</Option>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Preceptor"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Greatswords</Name>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Greatswords are the elite infantry of the Imperial army. Operating as a crack fighting force, their main duty is the protection of their Elector Counts during the heat of battle, and to provide the Empire with dedicated shock infantry, often attacking the Empire's foes at their flanks, where their swordsmanship puts even the most battle-hardened foes to their knee's.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Stubborn/>
					<RegimentalUnit/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Count's Champion"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Demigryph Knights</Name>
				<Points>58</Points>
				<Size>3+</Size>
				<Mount>Demigryph</Mount>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='8' AS='5'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Lance</Name>
						<Dependency/>
						<Lance/>
						<RealisedByDefault/>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Halberd</Name>
						<Dependency/>
						<AddToStrength Val="1"/>
					</Option>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Preceptor"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Reiksguard Knights</Name>
				<Points>27</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='8' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Stubborn/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<FullPlateArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Reikscaptain"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Huntsmen</Name>
				<Points>8</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<Scouts/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Bow/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Tracker"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Pistoliers</Name>
				<Points>18</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<FastCavalry/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Brace of pistols</HandWeapon>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Outrider"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<Option>
							<Name>Repeater pistol for Outrider</Name>
							<Dependencies>
								<On>Outrider</On>
								<Off>Repeater Handgun for Outrider</Off>
							</Dependencies>
							<Points>10</Points>
						</Option>
						<Option>
							<Name>Repeater Handgun for Outrider</Name>
							<Dependencies>
								<On>Outrider</On>
								<Off>Repeater pistol for Outrider</Off>
							</Dependencies>
							<Points>10</Points>
						</Option>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Outriders</Name>
				<Points>21</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<FastCavalry/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Repeater handgun</RangeWeapon>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Barding for Warhorse</Name>
						<PointsPerModel>1</PointsPerModel>
						<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					</Option>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Sharpshooter"/>
						<Musician Points="8"/>
						<Option>
							<Name>Brace of pistol for Sharpshooter</Name>
							<Dependencies>
								<On>Sharpshooter</On>
								<Off>Grenade launching for Sharpshooter</Off>
							</Dependencies>
							<Points>10</Points>
						</Option>
						<Option>
							<Name>Grenade launching for Sharpshooter</Name>
							<Dependencies>
								<On>Sharpshooter</On>
								<Off>Brace of pistol for Sharpshooter</Off>
							</Dependencies>
							<Points>10</Points>
						</Option>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Great Cannon</Name>
				<Points>120</Points>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Cannon/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Mortar</Name>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Mortar/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Flagellants</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<Original>The End is Night!</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Flail/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Prophet of Doom"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Hellblaster Volley Gun</Name>
				<Points>120</Points>
				<Image>Hellblaster</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Helblaster/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Helstorm Rocket Battary</Name>
				<Points>120</Points>
				<Image>RocketBattary</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>Rocket Battary</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Steam Tank</Name>
				<Points>250</Points>
				<Profile M='0' WS='0' BS='4' S='6' T='6' W='10' I='0' A='0' Ld='7' AS='1'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<SteamTank/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Random Movement</Rule>
						<Rule>Steam Points</Rule>
						<Rule>Steel Behemoth Points</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<RangeWeapon>Main cannon</RangeWeapon>
					<RangeWeapon>Steam cannon</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Hochland long rifle</Name>
						<Points>20</Points>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Celestail Hurricanum</Name>
				<Points>130</Points>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Chariot>2</Chariot>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='1' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<AddToHit Val="1"/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Locus of Azyr</Rule>
						<Rule>Portents of Battle</Rule>
						<Rule>Storm of Shemtek</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Luminark of Hysh</Name>
				<Points>120</Points>
				<Mount>Warhorse</Mount>
				<Chariot>2</Chariot>
				<Image>Luminark</Image>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='1' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Locus of Hysh</Rule>
						<Rule>Solheim's Bolt of Illumination</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Arcane>
						<AddToWard Val="6"/>
						<Rule>All friendly units within 6" have a 6+ Ward save</Rule>
					</Arcane>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>