<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Imprint>
			<Army>Wood Elves</Army>
			<Edition>8</Edition>
			<Released>2014</Released>
			<Authors>Mat Ward</Authors>
			<Description>The Wood Elves, known as the Asrai in some tales, or as the Fay Folk of Athel Loren, are a reclusive, secretive and highly isolationist race of Elves that have long ago voluntarily split off from the rest of their kin, preferring instead to live out their lives in Nature's embrace beneath the enchanted forested canopy of Athel Loren. However, other conclaves are known to exist, such as the Eonir of Laurelorn.\n\nFrom these mystical realms, the Wood Elves have learnt to dwell in concord with the seasons and the weave of life and death that binds all living things together. They are the defenders of the forest, guardians of all things natural and pure. For millennia, the Wood Elves have lived in this state of harmony, lying in wait and hidden from the prying eyes of the wider World</Description>
		</Imprint>
		<Styles>
			<Colors>
				<Front>0c3004</Front>
				<Back>0d7007</Back>
				<Grid>f2ffec</Grid>
				<Tooltip>83ea83</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>86b783, 559a51, 3d8c38</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<Images>
				<Files>
					<Cover/>
					<Symbol/>
					<Illustration/>
				</Files>
				<Folders>
					<Units/>
				</Folders>
			</Images>
		</Styles>
		<Naming>
			<Internal>WoodElves</Internal>
			<MagicItems>Heirlooms of Athel Loren</MagicItems>
		</Naming>
		<Magic>
			<Name>The Lore of High Magic</Name>
			<Options>Lore of Dark Magic or any of eight Lore of Battle Magic</Options>
			<Magic>
				<Spell Name="Apotheosis" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Hand of Glory" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Walk Between Worlds" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Drain magic" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Soul Quench" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Tempest" Cast="12"/>
				<Spell Name="Arcane Unforging" Cast="13"/>
				<Spell Name="Fiery convocation" Cast="19"/>
			</Magic>
			<Enemy>Beastmen, The Lore of The Wild</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Viletide" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Devolve" Cast="11"/>
				<Spell Name="Bray-scream" Cast="12"/>
				<Spell Name="Traitor-Kin" Cast="12"/>
				<Spell Name="Mantle of Ghorok" Cast="15"/>
				<Spell Name="Savage Dominin" Cast="18"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<Local>
			<SpecialRules>
				<ForestStalker/>
				<Scouts/>
				<FastCavalry/>
				<Flammable/>
				<BonusAttemptsToCast>+1 to all attempts to cast spells</BonusAttemptsToCast>
			</SpecialRules>
			<Options>
				<AsraiLongbow/>
				<AsraiSpear/>
				<HagbaneTips/>
				<TrueflightArrows/>
				<MoontireShot/>
				<StarfireShafts/>
				<SwiftshiverShards/>
				<ArcaneBodkins/>
				<Strangleroots>
					Rule: Shooting attack with Range 12", Strength 5 and Multiple Shots(D6+1)
				</Strangleroots>
			</Options>
		</Local>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<Heirlooms Name="Heirlooms of Athel Loren">
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Spirit Sword</Name>
					<Points>85</Points>
					<NoArmour/>
					<Rule>Immediately when an enemy character, champion or monster suffers one or more unsaved Wounds from the Spirit Sword, both he and the wielder must roll 2D6 and add their respective Leadership values. If the wounded model's total is higher, or the totals are the same, nothing else happens. If the wounded model's total is lower, it immediately suffers a Wound for each point by which its total was exceeded, with no armour saves allowed</Rule>
					<Description>Armour saves cannot be taken against Wounds caused by the Spirit Sword. Furthermore, immediately when an enemy character, champion or monster suffers one or more unsaved Wounds from the Spirit Sword, both he and the wielder must roll 2D6 and add their respective Leadership values. If the wounded model's total is higher, or the totals are the same, nothing else happens. If the wounded model's total is lower, it immediately suffers a Wound for each point by which its total was exceeded, with no armour saves allowed</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Daith's Reaper</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Reroll>ToHit;ToWound;OpponentToArmour</Reroll>
					<Description>All failed To Hit and To Wound rolls made with Daith's Reaper must be re-rolled, as must all successful armour saves taken against Wounds caused by this weapon</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Bow of Loren</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>The Bow of Loren is an Asrai longbow with the Multiple Shots (A+1) special rule, which means it fires a number of shots equal to 1 plus the wielder's Attacks characteristic. It cannot fire enchanted arrows</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Armour>
					<Name>The Helm of the Hunt</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<AddToWeaponSkill Val="1"/>
					<Rule>Devastating Charge</Rule>
					<Description>The wearer of the Helm of the Hunt counts his armour save as being one point higher than normal. Furthermore, the Helm of the Hunt grants the bearer the Devastating Charge special rule and +1 Weapon Skill on a turn in which he charges into combat</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Acorns of The Ages</Name>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<Rule>One use only. At the start of the game, after the battlefield has been set up, but before deployment begins, place D3 Citadel Woods on the battlefield. A forest can be placed anywhere at least 1" away from another terrain feature and the edge of the batdefield. Once all forests have been placed, scatter each 2D6". If this scatter causes a forest to end up within 1" (or on top of) other terrain, or within 1" of the batdefield edge, reduce or increase the scatter by the smallest amount necessary to avoid the obstruction. When this has been done, declare which type of forest you want these to be - choose from the types on the Mysterious Forest table. All forests created by the Acorn of the Ages must be of the same type</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Moonstone of the Hidden Ways</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>If the bearer's unit is wholly within a forest at the end of your Movement phase, and is not in close combat, it can forestwalk. If it does so, remove it from the battlefield and immediately replace it, wholly within any forest on the battlefield, in the same formation, but facing am direction. A forestwalking unit cannot be placed within 1" of an enemy unit or impassable terrain. A unit that forestwalks counts as having marched in the Movement phase</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Hail of Doom Arrow</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>One use only. Model with Asrai longbow only. The Hail of Doom arrow can be used instead of making a Shooting attack with the bearer's Asrai longbow. Declare that the Hail of Doom Arrow is being used before any dice are rolled. Range 30", Strength 4, Armour Piercing, Multiple SHots (3D6)</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Calaingors Stave</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>The bearer generates one less spell than is normal for his Wizard level, but knows the Tree Singing spell</Rule>
				</Arcane>
				<Banner>
					<Name>The Banner of the Eternal Queen</Name>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<MagicResistance Val="3"/>
					<Rule>Once per game, all models in the same unit as the Banner of the Eternal Queen have the Unbreakable special rule until the end of turn, or until the bearer is slain</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer has the Magic Resistance (3) special rule. In addition, once per game, all models in the same unit as the Banner of the Eternal Queen have the Unbreakable special rule until the end of turn, or until the bearer is slain (whichever comes first). Declare you are using this ability at the start of any turn</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>The Banner of the Hunter King</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Rule>Vanguard deployment special rule</Rule>
					<Rule>Unit re-roll their first failed charge of the game</Rule>
					<Description>All models in the same unit as the Banner of the Hunter King have the Vanguard deployment special rule. In addition, the bearer's unit re-roll their first failed charge of the game</Description>
				</Banner>
			</Heirlooms>
			<CommonMagicWeapons>
				<GiantBlade Points="60"/>
				<SwordOfBloodshed Points="60"/>
				<ObsidianBlade Points="50"/>
				<OgreBlade Points="40"/>
				<SwordOfStrife Points="40"/>
				<FencersBlades Points="35"/>
				<SwordOfAntiHeroes Points="30"/>
				<SpellthievingSword Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfSwiftSlaying Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfBattle Points="20"/>
				<BerserkerSword Points="20"/>
				<SwordOfMight Points="20"/>
				<GoldSigilSword Points="15"/>
				<SwordOfStriking Points="15"/>
				<BitingBlade Points="10"/>
				<RelicSword Points="10"/>
				<ShriekingBlade Points="10"/>
				<TormentorSword Points="5"/>
				<WarriorBane Points="5"/>
			</CommonMagicWeapons>
			<CommonMagicArmours>
				<ArmourOfDestiny Points="50"/>
				<TrickstersHelm Points="50"/>
				<ArmourOfSilveredSteel Points="50"/>
				<ArmourOfFortune Points="35"/>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Helm of Discord</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Test Bet="Pass" Context="Round" Profile="Leadership"/>
					<Description>The wearer counts his armour save as being one point higher than normal. In addition, at the start of each Close Combat phase, choose an enemy character in base contact with the bearer or his unit. That character must immediately take a Leadership test. If the test is failed, the character succumbs to the helm's sibilant whispers of malice and jealousy. In this Close Combat phase, the victim cannot make attacks and is hit automatically</Description>
				</Additional>
				<GlitteringScales Points="25"/>
				<ShieldOfPtolos Points="25"/>
				<Spellshield Points="20"/>
				<GamblersArmour Points="20"/>
				<Dragonhelm Points="10"/>
				<EnchantedShield Points="5"/>
				<CharmedShield Points="5"/>
			</CommonMagicArmours>
			<CommonMagicTalismans>
				<TalismanOfPreservation Points="45"/>
				<ObsidianLodestone Points="30"/>
				<TalismanOfEndurance Points="30"/>
				<Dawnstone Points="25"/>
				<OpalAmulet Points="15"/>
				<ObsidianTrinket Points="15"/>
				<TalismanOfProtection Points="15"/>
				<SeedOfRebirt Points="10"/>
				<DragonbaneGem Points="5"/>
				<PidgeonPluckerPendant Points="5"/>
				<Luckstone Points="5"/>
			</CommonMagicTalismans>
			<CommonMagicStandards>
				<RampagersStandard Points="55"/>
				<WailingBanner Points="50"/>
				<RangersStandard Points="50"/>
				<RazorStandard Points="45"/>
				<WarBanner Points="35"/>
				<BannerOfSwiftness Points="15"/>
				<LichebonePennant Points="15"/>
				<StandardOfDiscipline Points="15"/>
				<BannerOfEternalFlame Points="10"/>
				<GleamingPennant Points="5"/>
				<ScarecrowBanner Points="5"/>
			</CommonMagicStandards>
			<CommonArcaneItems>
				<BookOfAshur Points="70"/>
				<FeedbackScroll Points="50"/>
				<ScrollOfLeeching Points="50"/>
				<SivejirsHexScroll Points="50"/>
				<PowerScroll Points="50"/>
				<WandOfJet Points="35"/>
				<ForbiddenRod Points="35"/>
				<TrickstersShard Points="25"/>
				<EarthingRod Points="25"/>
				<DispellScroll Points="25"/>
				<PowerStone Points="20"/>
				<SceptreOfStability Points="15"/>
				<ChannellingStaff Points="15"/>
				<ScrollOfShielding Points="15"/>
			</CommonArcaneItems>
			<CommonEnchantedItems>
				<WizardingHat Points="100"/>
				<FozzriksFoldingFortress Points="100"/>
				<ArabyanCarpet Points="50"/>
				<CrownOfCommand Points="35"/>
				<HealingPotion Points="35"/>
				<FeatherfoeTorc Points="35"/>
				<RubyRingOfRuin Points="25"/>
				<TheTerrifyingMaskOfEee Points="25"/>
				<PotionOfStrength Points="20"/>
				<PotionOfToughness Points="20"/>
				<TheOtherTrickstersShard Points="15"/>
				<IroncurseIcon Points="5"/>
				<PotionOfFoolhardiness Points="5"/>
				<PotionOfSpeed Points="5"/>
			</CommonEnchantedItems>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Orion</Name>
				<Points>600</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Description>The immortal Consort King of Athel Loren, Orion is the rampaging avatar of the elf god Kurnous. He is a terrifying sight to behold, standing over ten feet tall and his green skin ripples with muscle. Although he must die each winter, he is reborn each spring, and reaches the peak of his power in mid-summer. Such is the way of things, the "continuation of the never-ending process of death and rebirth". Orion is normally accompanied by his baying hounds and the Wild Riders of Kurnous. Orion counts as both a Lord and a Hero choice. At the height of his power in midsummer, Orion is a terrifying being of majesty and power. And his lithe, green-tinged body ripples with barely contained anger. As the moons align overhead on midsummer's eve, a beautiful cloak crafted by his Queen is draped over his shoulders, and the great horn of the Wild Hunt is placed reverently before him. As the time of the conjunction draws near, he takes up his weapons from their shrine within the Oak of Ages. At midnight, Athel Loren goes utterly silent – not a creature stirs – for all know that the ride of the Wild Hunt has come.</Description>
				<Profile M='9' WS='8' BS='8' S='6' T='5' W='5' I='9' A='5' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<Terror/>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Original>If Orion is accompanied by Hounds of Orion, they must be deployed as a unit (even though as a monster, Orion is not normally permitted to join units). Orion cannot leave this unit, and cannot join other units</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Spear of Kurnous</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<Rule>A missile weapon with the Range 18", Strength 7 and Multiple Shots (D3)</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<RangeWeapon>
						<Name>Hawk's Talon</Name>
						<Rule>A missile weapon with the Range 30", Strength 5 and Multiple Shots (6)</Rule>
					</RangeWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Cloak of Isha</Name>
						<AddToWard Val="5"/>
						<MagicResistance Val="2"/>
						<Rule>At the start of each of your turns, roll a D6. On a score of 6, Orion regains a Wound lost earlier in the battle</Rule>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Horn of the Wild Hunt</Name>
						<AddToWard Val="5"/>
						<Rule>At the start of each turn, the Horn of the Wild Hunt grants the Devastating Charge special rule to Orion, his unit, and all friendly Wood Elf units within 6"</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Mount Name="Hound of Orion" Points="20"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Durthu</Name>
				<Points>385</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Durthu, or Oakheart, is an Elder of Athel Loren, a Treeman so ancient that even Ariel’s millennia-long existence pales in comparison. It was he who first forged a union between Elves and forest, and he also who argued with his fellow Elders that the binding be made permanent. In those days, he was ever a friend to the children of Isha, always willing to help them broaden their understanding of the forest and of the Weave.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='7' BS='7' S='6' T='6' W='6' I='2' A='6' Ld='10' AS='3' Ward='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Terror/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<Hate/>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Flammable/>
					<BonusAttemptsToCast/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Use Lore of Beast</Rule>
						<Rule>A model can choose to make a single Tree Whack in place of making his normal close combat attacks. It must be declared before rolling To Hit. To resolve a Tree Whack, nominate an enemy model in base contact. That model must pass an Initiative test or suffer D6 Wounds with no armour saves allowed. A character with this special rule may make a Tree Whack in a challenge.</Rule>
						<Rule>Can make the shooting attack with Range 12", Strength 2, Multiple Shots (2D6) and Killing Blow special rule</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Araloth</Name>
				<Points>260</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Araloth the Bold or Araloth the Hooked Blade is the current Lord of Talysn and one of Athel Loren's greatest military commanders and warriors.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='8' BS='7' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='8' A='5' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Original>Whilst Araloth is a lone character, he has the Unbreakable special rule (this replaces Stubborn)</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<RangeWeapon>
						<Name>Skarvn the Eye Thief</Name>
						<Rule>At the start of each of your turns, nominate a single enemy model within 18" of Araloth. That model takes a Strength 4 hit. If the Wound is unsaved, and the To Wound roll was a 6, the model suffers a -5 penalty to Weapon Skill and Initiative (to a minimum of 1) for the rest of the game. A model can only suffer this penalty once</Rule>
					</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Glade Lord</Name>
				<Points>145</Points>
				<Description>Glade Lords, or Highborns, are the upper, ruling class of Elven society. They lead the Wood Elves in time of peace, and it is expected of them to be equally capable generals in times of war. They are far more skilled then the average elven foot troop. Highborns (and nobles) can take up special areas of training (called kindreds), which give them various skills and abilities. Most notably, the kindreds include the "Alters" who are characters that have been changed by the forest. They take on the aspects of the creatures of the forest, through which they move as rapidly as cavalry, and when they come upon the intruder they visit it with a torrent of attacks.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='7' BS='7' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='8' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Original>Once both sides have deployed, but before the first turn begins, check to see if the enemy General is within 36" and within line of sight of at least one of your models with this special rule. If he is, he immediately suffers a single Strength 3 hit against which no armour saves can be taken. Otherwise, nothing happens</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<AsraiSpear Points="3" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="3" Only="Infantry" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
					<HagbaneTips Points="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<TrueflightArrows Points="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<MoontireShot Points="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<StarfireShafts Points="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<SwiftshiverShards Points="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<ArcaneBodkins Points="5" Dependency="Range"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="20"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Eagle" Points="50"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Stag" Points="65"/>
					<Mount Name="Forest Dragon" Points="300"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Asrai longbow</RangeWeapon>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Spellweaver</Name>
				<Points>185</Points>
				<Wizard>3</Wizard>
				<Description>The Lord-level Mage is similar to mages in every other army, though she (female mages are far more attuned to Isha than males are) is limited to choosing spells from the Lore of Life, the Lore of Beasts, or the Wood Elf-specific Lore of Athel Loren - a set of magical skills which allow Spellweaver and Spellsingers to communicate with the forest for a variety of offensive and defensive benefits.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='3' I='5' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Wizard"/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<BonusAttemptsToCast/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="4" Points="35"/>
					<AsraiLongbow Points="5"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="20"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Eagle" Points="50"/>
					<Mount Name="Unicorn" Points="60"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Treeman Ancient</Name>
				<Points>385</Points>
				<Wizard>2</Wizard>
				<Description>Treeman Ancients are the oldest and wisest of the treemen that live in Athel Loren. They are just as large and strong as their brethren, but their knowledge of the past and workings of the Forest give the abilities much stronger than those of the average treeman.</Description>
				<Profile M='2' WS='7' BS='7' S='6' T='6' W='6' I='2' A='6' Ld='10' AS='3' Ward='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Terror/>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Flammable/>
					<BonusAttemptsToCast/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Use Lore of Life</Rule>
						<Rule>A model can choose to make a single Tree Whack in place of making his normal close combat attacks. It must be declared before rolling To Hit. To resolve a Tree Whack, nominate an enemy model in base contact. That model must pass an Initiative test or suffer D6 Wounds with no armour saves allowed. A character with this special rule may make a Tree Whack in a challenge.</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Wizard Level 3</Name>
						<Points>35</Points>
						<Dependency/>
						<AddToCast Val="1"/>
						<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
						<AddToWizard Val="1"/>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Wizard Level 4</Name>
						<Points>70</Points>
						<Dependency/>
						<AddToCast Val="2"/>
						<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
						<AddToWizard Val="2"/>
					</Option>
					<Strangleroots Points="20"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Drycha</Name>
				<Points>255</Points>
				<Wizard>2</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Drycha is the most powerful Branchwraith in Athel Loren. The Asrai believe she was driven mad when the blood of the powerful beastman Morghur was spilled in her glade, though in truth, she was malevolent and capricious long before that. She hates all who enter into Athel Loren, and blames the Wood Elves for all the evils that threaten the enchanted forest. In recent years, she and the forest creatures that serve her have taken to attacking villages around Athel Loren, leaving no survivors and showing no mercy. Drycha is believed to have entered the service of Coeddil, a tree-man whose hatred of the Asrai is legendary, and it is rumoured that she is forming a resistance to exterminate the Asrai.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='7' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='7' A='4' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fear/>
					<Hate/>
					<BonusAttemptsToCast/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Use Lore of Shadow</Rule>
						<Rule>Each time Drycha suffers an unsaved Wound, her Attacks characteristic increases by 2 for the remainder of the battle. Each time Drycha regains a Wound lost earlier in the batde, her Attacks characteristic decreases by 2 for the remainder of the battle</Rule>
						<Rule>This rule cannot be used if there are no forests on the battlefield when it is time to deploy vour army. When you deploy, you may choose D3 units wholly composed of the models with Forest Spirit special rule - thes are not deployed at the start of the game, but are 'slumbering' somewhere on the battiefield. At the start of the Remaining Moves sub-phase of your first turn, roll a D6 for each slumbering unit. On a roll of 1-2, nothing happens - roll again next turn. On a roll of 3-6, the unit awakens Place it on the battlefield so that all models in the unit are wholly within a forest, and at least 1" away from other units and impassable terrain. Treat units that cannot be placed as having rolled a 1-2. Any units that have not yet awoken by the timf the game ends award victory points as if they had been destroyed.</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Glade Captain</Name>
				<Points>75</Points>
				<Description>Noble are the upper, ruling class of Elven society. They lead the Wood Elves in time of peace, and it is expected of them to be equally capable generals in times of war. They are far more skilled then the average elven foot troop. Nobles can take up special areas of training (called kindreds), which give them various skills and abilities.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='6' S='4' T='3' W='2' I='7' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Original>Once both sides have deployed, but before the first turn begins, check to see if the enemy General is within 36" and within line of sight of at least one of your models with this special rule. If he is, he immediately suffers a single Strength 3 hit against which no armour saves can be taken. Otherwise, nothing happens</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<AsraiSpear Points="2" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="2" Only="Infantry" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
					<HagbaneTips Points="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<TrueflightArrows Points="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<MoontireShot Points="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<StarfireShafts Points="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<SwiftshiverShards Points="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<ArcaneBodkins Points="5" Dependency="Range"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="10"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Eagle" Points="50"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Stag" Points="65"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Asrai longbow</RangeWeapon>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Spellsinger</Name>
				<Points>80</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Description>Spellsingers are those among the Wood Elves dedicated to the study of the art of magic, essentially serving as the Asrai's wizards. However, those spellsingers who choose to specialise in either High or Dark Magic become what are called spellweavers. Spellweavers in turn are divided between High Magic specialists known as highweavers and Dark Magic sorcerers called darkweavers who often work together in balanced pairs.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Wizard"/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Original>+1 to all attempts to cast spells</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="2" Points="35"/>
					<AsraiLongbow Points="5"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="10"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Eagle" Points="50"/>
					<Mount Name="Unicorn" Points="60"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Shadowdancer</Name>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<Description>Shadowdancers are the closest thing that the Trickster God has to a priesthood, and they are both respected and feared as a result. They, and only they, know all the paths through Athel Loren — indeed, it is said that they tread the paths of the Dreaming Wood as surely as they do the mortal world.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='8' BS='6' S='4' T='3' W='2' I='8' A='3' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<MagicItems Points="25" Type="Hero"/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Once both sides have deployed, but before the first turn begins, check to see if the enemy General is within 36" and within line of sight of at least one of your models with this special rule. If he is, he immediately suffers a single Strength 3 hit against which no armour saves can be taken. Otherwise, nothing happens</Rule>
						<Rule>At the start of each round of close combat in which they are fighting, models choose one of the following dances: Whirling Death (Armour Piercing and Killing Blow), Storm of Blades (+1 Attack), The Shadows Coil (3+ ward save); the effect of which lasts until the end of that turn or until a new dance is chosen. This is done before Impact Hits are resolved. All dancers in the same unit must choose the same dance. Dancers cannot choose the same dance in two consecutive rounds of combat</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Wizard Level 1</Name>
						<Points>35</Points>
						<AddToCast Val="1"/>
						<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
						<AddToWizard Val="1"/>
						<Rule>Use Lore of Shadow</Rule>
					</Option>
					<AsraiLongbow Points="5"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="10"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Eagle" Points="50"/>
					<Mount Name="Unicorn" Points="60"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Waystalker</Name>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<Description>Waystalkers’ personalities have become entirely submerged by their obsession with stalking prey. They are taciturn and solitary individuals, and they may let years pass between visits to Wood Elf halls. Waystalkers are perfectly at ease within their forest homeland and effortlessly survive by their wits and cunning in the wilds.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='7' S='4' T='3' W='2' I='7' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<MagicItems Points="25" Type="Hero"/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Scouts/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Before a models makes a shooting attack, decide whether it will make afast shot or an aimed shot. If the former is chosen, the model's missile weapon has the Multiple Shots (2) special rule for the duration of that attack. If the latter is chosen, then armour saves cannot be taken against Wounds caused by the attack. Model in the same unit must choose the same type of shot</Rule>
						<Rule>Sniper</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
					<RangeWeapon>Asrai longbow</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Branchwraith</Name>
				<Points>75</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Description>Branchwraiths are the oldest of the Dryads. They have ever served as the handmaidens to the Ancients of Athel Loren, and attend to the Treemen with a dedication bordering upon the fanatical.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='6' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='7' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Hate/>
					<Fear/>
					<Original>+1 to all attempts to cast spells</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Elven Steed</Name>
				<Profile M='9' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Hound of Orion</Name>
				<ModelsInPack Val="2"/>
				<Profile M='9' WS='4' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='4' A='2' Ld='6'/>
				<Equipments/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<Frenzy/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<SpecialRulesAndAmmunition/>
				<Other/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Steed of Kurnous</Name>
				<Profile M='9' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Steed of Isha</Name>
				<Profile M='9' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Warhawk</Name>
				<Profile M='1' WS='4' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='5' A='2' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ArmourPiercing Val="1"/>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<FlyingCavalry/>
					<ForestStalker/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Great Eagle</Name>
				<Profile M='2' WS='5' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Great Stag</Name>
				<Profile M='9' WS='5' BS='0' S='5' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ImpactHit Val="D3"/>
					<Fear/>
					<LargeBase/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Unicorn</Name>
				<Profile M='10' WS='5' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='5' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<MagicResistance Val="2"/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>A Unicorn's close combat attacks have a +2 Strength bonus on a turn in which it charges</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Forest Dragon</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='0' S='6' T='6' W='6' I='3' A='5' Ld='8' AS='3' Ward='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Fly/>
					<Original>A Forest Dragon has a Strength 2 Breath Weapon. Armour saves taken against Wounds caused by Soporific Breath suffer a -3 penalty. All models in a unit that suffers one or more hits from Soporific Breath gain the Stupidity special rule for the remainder of the game</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Glade Guard</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>The Glade Guards forms the very core of Athel Loren's armies. In time of need, every Wood Elf can answer the call to defend their forest home, for all are trained in the arts of the longbow as soon as they can hold one.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<ForestStalker/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Asrai longbow</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<HagbaneTips PointsPerModel="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<TrueflightArrows PointsPerModel="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<MoontireShot PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<StarfireShafts PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<SwiftshiverShards PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<ArcaneBodkins PointsPerModel="5" Dependency="Range"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Lord's Bowman"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Dryads</Name>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Forest spirits that are the embodiment of nature's duality: Beauty and Ferocity. Dryads will lure intruders off roads and trails, then let their sharp branches and thorns teach the intruder the folly of trespassing in Athel Loren. Dryads are some of the most capable assault troops in the Wood Elf host, being fast, strong, tough, fear causing and nigh unstoppable.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='5' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Hate/>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Branch Nymph"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Glade Riders</Name>
				<Points>19</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Elven Steed</Mount>
				<Description>Forming a friendship of trust and understanding with their horses, Glade Riders move swiftly through the forest branches to bring their deadly bows to bear on the less mobile intruders. Glade Riders are capable of both ranged combat and close combat and often provide a curtain force on the front ranks, to delay and channel the intruder into a prepared devastating attack by wardancers, dryads, treekin and treemen.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<FastCavalry/>
					<Original>Ambushers</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Asrai spear</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Asrai longbow</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<HagbaneTips PointsPerModel="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<TrueflightArrows PointsPerModel="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<MoontireShot PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<StarfireShafts PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<SwiftshiverShards PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<ArcaneBodkins PointsPerModel="5" Dependency="Range"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Glade Knight"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Eternal Guard</Name>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Using a unique fighting form with deadly swordstaff called saearath, the Eternal Guard will solidly stand against any who threaten Athel Loren. Eternal Guard are frequently utilised as bodyguards for Highborn and other Wood Elven nobility. They are the only ones standing between the enemy and the destruction of the forest during winter time. During other seasons they have a mostly ceremonial role.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<Stubborn/>
					<ForestStalker/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Asrai spear</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Eternal Warden"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Wildwood Rangers</Name>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Wildwood Rangers are those Elves that have suffered a great tragedy by the hands of those entities that live within the Wildwoods, and have thusly dedicated their lives in patrolling those cursed grounds.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Original>If a models is in base contact with at least one enemy model with either the Fear or Terror special rule, it has +1 Attack</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Wildwood Warden"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Wardancers</Name>
				<Points>15</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Wardancers are the elven equivalent of berserkers—they have no armour, move fluidly, weave 'dances of death' around their opponents, and are immune to both fear and terror. In Wood Elf folklore, Wardancers are treated with the utmost respect.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='6' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Original>At the start of each round of close combat in which they are fighting, models choose one of the following dances: Whirling Death (Armour Piercing and Killing Blow), Storm of Blades (+1 Attack), The Shadows Coil (3+ ward save); the effect of which lasts until the end of that turn or until a new dance is chosen. This is done before Impact Hits are resolved. All dancers in the same unit must choose the same dance. Dancers cannot choose the same dance in two consecutive rounds of combat</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<AsraiSpear PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Bladesinger"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Tree Kin</Name>
				<Points>45</Points>
				<Size>3+</Size>
				<Description>Tree Kin is the name given to the spirits of Athel Loren that bond themselves with dead trees to create an abominable, moving tree monster. They are, in essence, lesser forms of Treemen.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='3' A='3' Ld='8' AS='4' Ward='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Flammable/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Tree Kin Elder"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Deepwood Scout</Name>
				<Points>13</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Deepwood Scouts hold the responsibility of patrolling those areas of the forest deemed too dangerous for Glade Guard to enter. To tread such paths, an Elf must be invisible not only to a predator’s sight, but to his other senses also - no easy matter when contending with otherworldly creatures to whom an Elf’s soul manifests as a brightly burning light.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Scouts/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Asrai longbow</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<HagbaneTips PointsPerModel="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<TrueflightArrows PointsPerModel="3" Dependency="Range"/>
					<MoontireShot PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<StarfireShafts PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<SwiftshiverShards PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<ArcaneBodkins PointsPerModel="5" Dependency="Range"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Master Scout"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Warhawk Riders</Name>
				<Points>45</Points>
				<Size>3+</Size>
				<Mount>Warhawk</Mount>
				<Description>Warhawk Riders are light, flying units used mostly for march-blocking and hit-and-run tactics. They are highly skilled elves riding agile, giant hawks, and resemble a sort of aerial cavalry.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<FlyingCavalry/>
					<ForestStalker/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Asrai spear</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Asrai longbow</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Wind Rider"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Sisters of the Thorn</Name>
				<Points>26</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Wizard>2</Wizard>
				<Mount>Steed of Isha</Mount>
				<Image>SistersOfThorn</Image>
				<Description>The Sisters of the Thorn are Ariel’s handmaidens. In many ways, they are equal and opposite to the Wild Riders of Kurnous, a sisterhood pledged to sorcery and subtlety where Orion’s equerries know loyalty only to the glory of the hunt. Where the Wild Riders are borne into battle on steeds as reckless as they, the Sisters ride upon Steeds of Isha — mounts whose viciousness lies hidden beneath a graceful aspect.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<PoisonAttack/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<FastCavalry/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Blackbriar javelin</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Handmaiden of the Thorn"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Wild Riders</Name>
				<Points>26</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Steed of Kurnous</Mount>
				<Description>The Wild Riders of Kurnous are Orion’s personal guard, each as aggressive and impulsive as he. They are fey and dangerous creatures who are no longer truly the Elves they once were. Now and forever they are a part of the Wild Hunt’s eternal glory. They ride Steeds of Kurnous, physical manifestations of the hunt.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='9' Ward=''/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<Fear/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<FastCavalry/>
					<Original>Devastating Charge</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Asrai spear</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Wild Hunter"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Waywatchers</Name>
				<Points>20</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Waywatchers are silent sentinels, the guardians of the paths leading into Athel Loren. They are masters of concealment, and can lie unmoving and unnoticed for days on end before springing an ambush on a startled and unfortunate prey.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='5' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8' Ward=''/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HitFirst/>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<ForestStalker/>
					<Scouts/>
					<Original>Before a models makes a shooting attack, decide whether it will make afast shot or an aimed shot. If the former is chosen, the model's missile weapon has the Multiple Shots (2) special rule for the duration of that attack. If the latter is chosen, then armour saves cannot be taken against Wounds caused by the attack. Model in the same unit must choose the same type of shot</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
					<RangeWeapon>Asrai longbow</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Waywatchers Sentiel"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Great Eagles</Name>
				<Points>50</Points>
				<Size>1+</Size>
				<Description>A Great Eagle is just that — an eagle of epic proportions. They live in the Grey Mountains, or on the very highest treetops of Athel Loren and have a special connection with elves. Wood elves use eagles as deadly flying monsters. Some heroes of the Wood Elf race are even known to ride them to battle.</Description>
				<Profile M='2' WS='5' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Treemen</Name>
				<Points>225</Points>
				<Description>Treemen are the most powerful spirits in Athel Loren. They, unlike Tree Kin, are permanently bound to a living tree, making a connection that only death can sever. Also, Treemen are ancient beings - some are old beyond mortal reckoning- of gigantic size and have many abilities that Tree Kin do not. One example is the mystical power of tree-singing, which can enable trees to walk or attack nearby enemies.</Description>
				<Profile M='2' WS='6' BS='6' S='5' T='6' W='5' I='2' A='5' Ld='9' AS='3' Ward='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Terror/>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Flammable/>
					<Original>A model can choose to make a single Tree Whack in place of making his normal close combat attacks. It must be declared before rolling To Hit. To resolve a Tree Whack, nominate an enemy model in base contact. That model must pass an Initiative test or suffer D6 Wounds with no armour saves allowed. A character with this special rule may make a Tree Whack in a challenge.</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Strangleroots Points="20"/>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>