<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Info>
			<Army>Dogs of War</Army>
			<Edition>5</Edition>
			<Released>1998</Released>
			<Authors>Nigel Stillman</Authors>
		</Info>
		<Styles>
			<Images>
				<Folders>
					<Units/>
				</Folders>
			</Images>
		</Styles>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Heroes/>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Volands warhorse</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5' AS='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Desert horse</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='0' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='0' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Deathfang</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='7' BS='0' S='7' T='7' W='8' I='5' A='8' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Fly/>
					<Individual>
						<Rule>Dragonrage</Rule>
					</Individual>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Scaly skin</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="3"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Cold One</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='1' A='2' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Stupidity/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<ThickSkinned/>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Braganza's Basiegers</Name>
				<Hire>!Skaven</Hire>
				<Points>13</Points>
				<Prepayment>86</Prepayment>
				<Image>BraganzasBasiegers</Image>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>The Braganza's Besiegers are heavily armoured crossbowmen skilled in the use of pavises. They're without a shadow of a doubt, one of the best mercenary regiments ever to come out of Tilea.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Crossbow/>
					<Shield>
						<Name>Pavise</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					</Shield>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Long Drong Slayer's Pirates</Name>
				<Hire>!Orcs</Hire>
				<Points>13</Points>
				<Prepayment>198</Prepayment>
				<Image>LongDrongSlayersPirates</Image>
				<Size>5-20</Size>
				<Description>Long Drong's Slayer Pirates also written as Long Drong Slayer's Pirates, are an infamous band of mercenary Dwarf Sea Slayers that travel the seven seas aboard the Fair Fregar. They specialise in recovering lost mercenary pay chests --for the right price.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='2' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Individual>
						<Rule>Festooned with Pistols</Rule>
						<Rule>Dwarf Rum</Rule>
					</Individual>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeanon>
						<Name>Pistols</Name>
					</RangeWeanon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Voland's Venators</Name>
				<Hire>!Bretonnia</Hire>
				<Points>35</Points>
				<Prepayment>40</Prepayment>
				<Image>VolandsVenators</Image>
				<Mount>Volands warhorse</Mount>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Voland's Venators is a famous mercenary band of knights who hire their members from Tileans, Imperials, and Bretonnians without distinction.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Pirazzo's Lost Legion</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>10</Points>
				<Prepayment>46</Prepayment>
				<Image>PirazzosLostLegion</Image>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Pirazzo's Lost Legion is a company of dogs of war who are legendary for being one of the few military forces in the Known World to have set foot upon the lush jungle-continent of Lustria and lived to tell the tale. Not only did these men survive this perilous journey, but their leader, the mercenary captain Fernando Pirazzo, became fantastically wealthy from the treasure he claimed there, and has since become a highly successful mercenary employed by the wealthy and powerful of many realms in the Old World.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>			
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Pike</Name>
						<Points>0</Points>
						<Dependencies>
							<Rule>Crossbow</Rule>
						</Dependencies>
						<Rule>Heavy Armour</Rule>
						<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
						<RealisedByDefault/>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Crossbow</Name>
						<Points>0</Points>
						<Dependencies>
							<Off>Pike</Off>
						</Dependencies>
						<Rule>Light Armour</Rule>
						<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Al Muktar's Desert Dogs</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Prepayment>152</Prepayment>
				<Image>AlMuktarsDesertDogs</Image>
				<Mount>Desert horse</Mount>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Al Muktar's Desert Dogs are a famous band of Dogs of War mercenaries that hail from the arid-deserts of great Araby. This band of bandit's and mercenaries are experienced raiders and skirmishers often raiding isolated villages, and caravans, while riding in calvary and wearing light armour or leather to make them agile in their attacks. Also, this Mercenary band is almost entirely composed of Arabyan corsairs or bandits from the inner deserts, where tribes of vicious warriors on camel-back raid the rich and fertile lands of Araby. This group however is lead by a foreigner, a man of the Empire, known as Werner Glook, a former son of a rich and aristocratic noblemen and merchant of the great City-State of Marienburg.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Scimitar of Dakisir</Name>
						<Points>25</Points>
						<Rule>+1 Strength to blows strikes and +2 Strength for blows struck in the turn in which charges for Sheikh Ahmed Shufti</Rule>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Black Banner of Muktarhin</Name>
						<Points>25</Points>
						<AddToCloseCombat Val="D3"/>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Asarnil the Dragonlord</Name>
				<Hire>HighElves, WoodElves, Dwarfs, Bretonnia, Empire, Lizardmen</Hire>
				<Points>750</Points>
				<Image>AsarnilDragonlord</Image>
				<Mount>Deathfang</Mount>
				<Size>1</Size>
				<Description>Asarnil the Dragonlord is a famous High Elven mercenary who hailed from the mist-shrouded lands of far-off Ulthuan. A former prince of the Kingdom of Caledor, Asarnil is now famous throughout the Old World as a powerful and mighty warrior riding atop his terrifying Dragon.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='6' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='8' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Amulet of Dragonheart</Name>
						<Points>45</Points>
						<Rule>Enemy's Weapon Skill in base contact reduce to 1</Rule>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Birdmen of Catrazza</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>20</Points>
				<Prepayment>70</Prepayment>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>The Birdmen of Catrazza are a famous band of Dogs of War mercenaries that hail from Tilea. Wearing their trademark bird-mask, these mercenaries are famed throughout the Old World for their ability to fly across the battlefield by using a pair of wings made entirely of canvas stretched out over a light wooden frame. This is strapped to their shoulders by means of a harness that leaves both hands free to shoot a smaller variant of the crossbow. In flight, the wings can be flapped by means of a stirrup attached to the feet, allowing the Birdmen to glide up and down the battlefield.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Fly/>
					<Individual>
						<Rule>Shoot on the Wing</Rule>
						<Rule>Shoot at High Flyers</Rule>
					</Individual>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<AdditionalWeapon/>
					<Crossbow/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Golgfag's mercenary Ogres</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>44</Points>
				<Prepayment>280</Prepayment>
				<Image>MercenaryOgres</Image>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Golgfag's Maneaters, also known as Golgfag's Ogres, are a band of Dogs of War hailing from the arid mountains of the Ogre Kingdoms. This band of mercenaries consists entirely of Ogre Maneaters, lead by their leader and perhaps the most infamous Maneater alive, Golgfag Maneater. For as long as he had lived, Golfag Maneater has lead his brethren into countless battles for riches, glory, and most importantly, food. He has served in the armies of many warlords and generals of many nations, never discriminating on who he is fighting for or against.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='3' BS='2' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='3' A='2' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Leopold's Leopard Company</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>10</Points>
				<Prepayment>80</Prepayment>
				<Image>LeopardCompany</Image>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Leopold's Leopard Company is a famous band of mercenaries that has its origins within the great Tilean city-state of Luccini. The Leopard Company takes its name from the legendary Leopard of Luccini, which is a badge and mascot of the city. It is said that this Leopard was the guardian of the divine twins Lucan and Luccina, the founders of the city.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Long pike</HandWeapon>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Bronzino's Galloper Guns</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<Prepayment>69</Prepayment>
				<Image>GalloperGuns</Image>
				<Size>1+</Size>
				<ModelsInPack Val="3"/>
				<Description>Bronzino's Galloper Guns are a famous band of Dogs of War mercenaries. First employed during the battle of Pattio, this band of mercenaries has been rewarded with fame and fortune throughout their career, first serving under the leadership of the Tilean Merchant Prince Borgio "the Besieger". The Galloper Guns were in fact, lightweight cannons removed from their mountings on the galleys of Remas and fixed onto specially made carriages, allowing for rapid deployment during the heat of battle.</Description>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='2' I='1' A='2' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Cannon</Rule>
						<Rule>Rapid Movement</Rule>
						<Rule>Deployment</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Marksmen of Miragliano</Name>
				<Hire>!Skaven</Hire>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Prepayment>81</Prepayment>
				<Image>Marksmens</Image>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>The Marksmen of Miragliano are a famous band of Dogs of War mercenaries whoses origins hails from the Tilean city-state of Miragliano as their name implies. Although the use of the crossbow as a weapon of war is far from uncommon in Tilea, very few mercenary companies can hope to match the accuracy and precision of these marksmen. Captain Maximilian Damark, who is a veteran marksman with dozens of years of experience, currently leads the company.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Skirmishers/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Sword</HandWeapon>
					<Crossbow/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Bearmens of Urslo</Name>
				<Hire>!HighElves</Hire>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Prepayment>176</Prepayment>
				<Image>Bearmens</Image>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>The Bearmen of Urslo, also known as the Tribe of the Bear by those they kill, is a band of Norscan warriors who often sell themselves out as mercenaries.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Axes</HandWeapon>
					<Shield/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Vespero's Vendetta</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>9</Points>
				<Prepayment>70</Prepayment>
				<Image>VesperosVendetta</Image>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Vespero's Vendetta are a famous band of Dogs of War who soon earned a notorious reputation as deadly duellists, reliable bodyguards, and expert saboteurs and assassins. The rivalry between the merchant princes of Tilea are so violent that everyone of a right mind would hire bodyguards. These bodyguards would protect their master from plotters, assassins, and rebels alike. Inevitably however, bodyguards of rival families or houses would often clash with other families and small street duels are an often common place in the largest of Tilean cities.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Cloak and Dagger</Rule>
						<Rule>Grimacing Death Mask</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Alcatani Fellowship</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>9</Points>
				<Prepayment>45</Prepayment>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>The Alcatani Fellowship are a famous band of Dogs of War mercenaries that hail from the tranquil countryside of war-torn Tilea. The Alcatani Fellowship are unlike any other mercenary company in existence, for not only are they a crack and able fighting force but they also share a common heart for all commoners and peasants alike. As such, the Fellowship were considered the only mercenary company not completely driven by money, fighting also for the good-will of the people, making Rodrigo an extremely famous and popular mercenary captain amongst the common people.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Steel-tipped pikes</HandWeapon>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Ricco's Republican Guard</Name>
				<Hire>*</Hire>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Prepayment>81</Prepayment>
				<Image>RepublicanGuard</Image>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Ricco's Republican Guard are a famous band of Dogs of War mercenaries hailing from the great Republican city-state of Remas. The Republican Guard was raised in Remas by a rebellious group of merchants during the time of disastrous famines and widespread revolt that preceded the birth of the Republic. The regiment played a leading part in overthrowing the tyrannical Merchant Prince of Remas, the notorious Omilio Mondo. It was upon one of the Guard's pikes that Mondo's head was paraded around the city to the drunken applause of the mob.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Long pikes</HandWeapon>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>The Cursed Company</Name>
				<Hire>!Bretonnia, Vampires, TombKings</Hire>
				<Points>10</Points>
				<Prepayment>205</Prepayment>
				<Size>10-30</Size>
				<Description>The Cursed Company of Richter Kreugar the Damned is an ancient mercenary company of Undead, rumoured to enslave those who fall to their deadly blades to eternal servitude. The battle-cry of Richter Kreugar has long been forgotten by the people of the Old World. The silence of the grave hangs over the Cursed Company as it traverses the land, marching to war accompanied only by the sound of creaking ancient leather and the scrape of rusted metal.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='2' BS='2' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Undead/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Fear/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>The Banner of Malediction</Rule>
						<Rule>"Join us in damnation..."</Rule>
						<Rule>Independent</Rule>
						<Rule>Hate all other Undead</Rule>
						<Rule>Leader</Rule>
						<Rule>Break Test</Rule>
						<Rule>Charge Reactions</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Shield/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Ruglud's Armoured Orcs</Name>
				<Hire>!Bretonnia, Dwarfs, HighElves, WoodElves</Hire>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Prepayment>70</Prepayment>
				<Image>ArmouredOrcs</Image>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Ruglud's Armoured Orcs are a famous band of Dogs of War mercenaries lead by the infamous Warlord, Ruglud Bonechewer. Ruglud is a powerful and wealthy Orc mercenary who sells his services all across the known world, from the treacherous Badlands in the south up through the realm of the Border Princes and throughout the mountains surrounding the Empire.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<Animosity/>
					<IgnoreGreenskinPanic/>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="2"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Choppa</HandWeapon>
					<Crossbow/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Tichi-Huichi's Raiders</Name>
				<Hire>!Bretonnia, WarriorOfChaos, Skaven, Vampires, TombKings</Hire>
				<Points>22</Points>
				<Prepayment>118</Prepayment>
				<Image>TichiHuich</Image>
				<Size>6-20</Size>
				<Description>Tichi-Huichi's Raiders are a famous band of Dogs of War mercenaries that hail from the distant jungle-continent of the Southlands. This mercenary band consist entirely of Skink warriors riding on-top of Cold Ones, known famously for their swiftness and speed during the heat of battle. Lead by the eldest of their host, Tichi-Huichi was the last inhabitant of the city of Enxilada until the day came when he became the caregiver of a whole new spawning of Lizardmen offspring.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='2' BS='3' S='3' T='2' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='6' AS="4"/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<DogsOfWar/>
					<ColdBlooded/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Blessed by the Old Ones</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Spears/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>