<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Info>
			<Army>Dwarfs</Army>
			<Edition>6</Edition>
			<Released>2000</Released>
			<Authors>Gav Thorpe and Alessio Cavatore</Authors>
			<Description>The Dwarfs, also called the "Elder Race" (or the Dawi as they call themselves) are one of the oldest and proudest intelligent races of the Warhammer World, with a great wealth of history and power that stretches back to time immemorial. They once held an empire which stretched from Norsca in the north to the jungles in the south, and from Mount Silverspear in the east to the Grey Mountains in the west. But the heart of the Dwarfen realm, the Karaz Ankor as they call it, will always lie within the domains of the Worlds Edge Mountains. The highest mountain range in the world, it is filled with the magnificent halls and holds of the Dwarfen people - a testament to the great feats of engineering and power once wielded by this ancient civilization</Description>
		</Info>
		<Styles>
			<Colors>
				<Front>dbbe5d</Front>
				<Back>ffd65b</Back>
				<Grid>fdf5e2</Grid>
				<Tooltip>fdf5e2</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>ffeebd, ffe28c, ffda6b</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<Images>
				<Files>
					<Cover/>
					<Symbol/>
					<Illustration/>
				</Files>
				<Folders>
					<Units/>
				</Folders>
			</Images>
		</Styles>
		<Naming>
			<Internal>Dwarfs</Internal>
			<MagicItems>Runic Magic</MagicItems>
		</Naming>
		<Magic>
			<Magic/>
			<Enemy>Skaven, Skaven Spell List</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Skitterleap" Cast="6"/>
				<Spell Name="Warp Lightning" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Vermintide" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Pestilent Breath" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Death Frenzy" Cast="11"/>
				<Spell Name="Plague" Cast="15"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<Local>
			<SpecialRules>
				<WarMachine/>
			</SpecialRules>		
			<Options>
				<GromrilArmour>
					AddToArmour: 4
				</GromrilArmour>
				<Pistol/>
				<DwarfHandgun/>
				<BracePistols>
					Name: Brace of pistols
				</BracePistols>
				<DwarfPistols/>
				<ThrowingAxe/>
			</Options>
		</Local>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<WeaponsRunes>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Master Rune of Snorri Spangelhelm</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<AutoHit/>
					<Lore>Runesmith to the High King of Karaz-a-Karak during the time of Kallon Vikramsson, Snorri wrought the exquisite war panoply of the High Kings for several generations. He fought in many battles and was renowned for his magnificent gromril armour as well as this unique weapon rune. This unique suit of mail and plate was strong enough to turn the hardest blade or heaviest blow and yet was as light and flexible as silk. Such is the awesomeness of his work that it still brings tears to a Runesmith's eyes</Lore>
					<Description>Any blows struck by a weapon engraved with this rune will always hit. No roll to hit is necessary</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Master Rune of Skalf Blackhammer</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<AutoWound/>
					<Lore>A legendary Runesmith who worked in Karaz-a-Karak in the earliest days, Skalf forged many great hammers, and some say even Sigmar's hammer was his work. Many of his hammers were later held by Dwarf Lords as heirlooms of their power and kingship</Lore>
					<Description>Any weapon bearing this rune will automatically wound if it hits. Roll to hit as normal. No roll to wound is required. Use the character's Strength for the save modifier</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Master Rune of Alaric the Mad</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<NoArmour/>
					<Lore>The famed Runesmith who forged the famous and rightly feared Runefangs of the Elector Counts of the Empire. Alaric made twelve swords, one for each of Sigmar's warlords in return for his help in recapturing Alaric's stronghold of Zhufbar after it had been overrun by Orcs. Alaric kept his word and delivered twelve rune swords to the Imperial counts. The forging took so long that Sigmar had long passed from his mortal form, but the swords were presented to his successor, the Emperor. No one knows exactly what happened to Alaric after this. Some say he wrought rune weapons for the Khan Queens of Kislev, possibly even the dreaded blade Fearfrost</Lore>
					<Description>This rune cancels an opponent's armour saving throw. When wounded by this weapon, the target is not allowed an armour saving throw of any kind</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Master Rune of Flight</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Weapon can be thrown like a throwing weapon with a range of up to 12" which always hits as if the target had suffered a hit from the weapon in close combat</Rule>
					<Lore>This rune has been used to surprise the Dwarfs' foes since the world was young. The original inscription for this rune did not specify that the hammer return to the wielder's band, and many Dwarfs found themselves knocked unconscious as their own weapons returned to them</Lore>
					<Description>This rune may only be inscribed onto a hammer. The hammer can be thrown at any model in sight and within 12", including models which cannot be singled out by normal shooting (like characters inside units). The target is automatically hit once as if the two models were in close combat, then the hammer flies back into the wielder's hand</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Master Rune of Breaking</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>If character scores a hit against an enemy with a magic weapon, the enemy's magic weapon is destroyed immediately</Rule>
					<Lore>First used during the War of Vengeance, this rune was inscribed upon King Gorrin's axe, which destroyed the High Elf General Elthior's enchanted blade. It has become a popularly used rune ever since. Runesmiths take particular delight in the sound of the inferior works of other races breaking like icicles beneath a hammer blow</Lore>
					<Description>If the Dwarf character scores a hit against an enemy with a magic weapon, the enemy's magic weapon is destroyed immediately. Multiple runes have no further effect</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Master Rune of Swiftness</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<HitFirst/>
					<Lore>This rune was first struck by Thurgrom the Hermit, the last Runesmith to work in the High Elf cities of the Old World, now reduced to ruins throughout the Empire and Bretonnia. The name of this rune suggests Elven influence which seems to confirm the story that Thurgard stole the ritual from the Elves and devised his own rune using Elven magical words in the ritual incantations. Since his lore is kept so utterly secret by his descendants, this is impossible to confirm</Lore>
					<Description>A weapon engraved with this rune always strikes first. In situations where both sides are entitled to strike first, the highest Initiative value has priority over the lower value. If Initiatives are equal, both sides roll a D6 and the highest score strikes first</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Might</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Doubles Strength against foes of Toughness 5 or higher in close combat</Rule>
					<Lore>Though short in stature, a Dwarf using a weapon inscribed with this rune is a powerful opponent, and can fell a Giant in a flurry of axe blows</Lore>
					<Description>Double Strength against any enemies with Toughness 5 or more. Multiple runes have no further effect</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Fury</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
					<Description>The wielder of this weapon adds +1 to his Attack characteristic</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Fury</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<AddToAttacks Val="2"/>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Fury</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<AddToAttacks Val="3"/>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Cleaving</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="1"/>
					<Description>The wielder of this weapon adds +1 to his Strength</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Cleaving</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Cleaving</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="3"/>
					<KillingBlow/>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Grudge Rune</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>Nominate one enemy character or monster at the beginning of the game: the model may re-roll misses in close combat when attacking this enemy model</Rule>
					<Description>Nominate one enemy character or monster at the beginning of the game. The wielder may re-roll misses in close combat when attacking this enemy model. Multiple runes of this type have no additional effect (a dice can only be re-rolled once)</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Striking</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<AddToWeaponSkill Val="1"/>
					<Description>The wielder of this weapon may add +1 to his Weapon Skill</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Striking</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToWeaponSkill Val="2"/>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Striking</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToWeaponSkill Val="3"/>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Speed</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>5</Points>
					<AddToInitiative Val="1"/>
					<Description>The wielder of this weapon adds +1 to his Initiative</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Speed</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<AddToInitiative Val="2"/>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Speed</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<AddToInitiative Val="3"/>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Fire</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>5</Points>
					<Rule>Flaming Attacks</Rule>
					<Description>Flaming attacks. This can cause extra damage on some targets (such as Treemen, Mummies, etc)</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</WeaponsRunes>
			<ArmourRunes>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Steel</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Reroll>OpponentToWound</Reroll>
					<Description>Your opponent must re-roll successful rolls to wound against the character</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Adamant</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<AddToToughness Val="1"/>
					<Description>This rune adds +1 to the Toughness of the character</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Gromril</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<ArmourTo Val="1"/>
					<Description>Confers a 1+ armour save that cannot be improved in any way</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Fortitude</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<AddToWounds Val="1"/>
					<Description>This rune gives its bearer +1 Wound</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Fortitude</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<AddToWounds Val="2"/>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Shielding</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>2+ Ward save against missile attacks only</Rule>
					<Description>The character has a 2+ Ward save against missile attacks only (including magic missiles). Multiple runes have no further effect</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Resistance</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Reroll>ToArmour</Reroll>
					<Description>This rune allows the character to re-roll any failed armour saving throws. As you're only ever allowed one re-roll, multiples of this rune would have no effect</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Iron</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="6"/>
					<Description>This rune confers a 6+ Ward save. Two of these runes confer a 5+ Ward save, but three cannot be taken, because only the-Master Rune of Spite can bind such huge power</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Iron</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Description>This rune confers a 6+ Ward save. Two of these runes confer a 5+ Ward save, but three cannot be taken, because only the-Master Rune of Spite can bind such huge power</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Stone</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>5</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Description>This rune adds +1 to the character's Armour save. The Rune of Stone is an exception to the normal Rule of Pride which forbids the same combination of runes to be used on several items, so a single Rune of Stone may be inscribed onto any character's armour. The Rune of Stone is also an exception in that it cannot be used more than once on the same item, so it is not possible to give two or three Runes of Stone to the same character</Description>
				</Additional>
			</ArmourRunes>
			<RunicStandards>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Master Rune of Valaya</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>125</Points>
					<Rule>+2 to all attempts to dispel</Rule>
					<Rule>Any spell which remains in play is dispelled automatically at the start of the Magic phase if the target it affects is within 12"</Rule>
					<Description>This rune adds +2 to all attempts to dispel made by the Dwarf player. Any spell which remains in play is dispelled automatically at the start of the Magic phase if the target it affects is within 12" of the standard. For example, a Wall of Fire will be dispelled if it is within 12" of the standard</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Master Rune of Stromni Redbeard</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="1"/>
					<Description>The Battle Standard adds a further +1 to the combat result of all Dwarf units within 12" of it</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Master Rune of Taunting</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Rule>Nominate one enemy unit within 12" when it is time for the enemy to declare charges: the enemy unit must either declare a charge against the unit or must flee in the Compulsory Movement phase as if it had failed a panic test</Rule>
					<Description>Nominate one enemy unit within 12" when it is time for the enemy to declare charges. The unit must be able to charge according to the normal rules. The enemy unit must either declare a charge against the unit with the banner, or must flee in the Compulsory Movement phase as if it had failed a panic test. This rune has no effect on units that are Immune to Psychology</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Master Rune of Fear</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Fear/>
					<Description>The unit causes fear exacdy as described in the psychology rules. A unit which causes fear is not affected by fear itself</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Master Rune of Groth One-Eye</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Description>The unit is stubborn</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Rune of Courage</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Description>The unit is Immune to Psychology</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Rune of Kadrin</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Reroll>ToHit(1)</Reroll>
					<Description>The unit re-rolls all rolls of 1 to hit when shooting and in close combat. Multiple runes have no further effect</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Rune of Slowness</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Any foes charging the unit subtract D6" from their charge distance</Rule>
					<Description>Any foes charging the unit subtract D6" from their charge distance. If the unit fails to make contact then all the usual rules for a failed charge apply. If multiples of this rune are used, the charge reduction is not added up, instead roll a D6 for each rune and choose the best score</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Rune of Battle</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="1"/>
					<Description>The unit adds a further +1 to its combat result score. A banner cannot have multiple Runes of Battle</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Rune of Sanctuary</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>+1 dice to any dispel attempt against enemy spells cast against the unit</Rule>
					<Description>Each rune adds one dice to any dispel attempt against enemy spells cast against the unit</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Rune of Sanctuary</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>+2 dice to any dispel attempt against enemy spells cast against the unit</Rule>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Rune of Sanctuary</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Rule>+3 dice to any dispel attempt against enemy spells cast against the unit</Rule>
				</Banner>
			</RunicStandards>
			<EngineeringRunes>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Defence</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>All incoming missiles (including magic missiles) hit the machine itself on a 1-5 and the crew only on a 6</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Disguise</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>Until it moves or shoots, the machine cannot be seen</Rule>
					<Description>Until it moves or shoots, the machine cannot be seen, and cannot therefore be targeted with spells, shot at, or charged. Once the machine has moved fired, or if an enemy unit moves to within 3" of it, the machine is revealed and can be Seen and attacked as normal for the rest of the battle</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Immolation</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>The Dwarf player can cause the machine to explode at any time (large circular template, all models under the template suffer a Strength 4 hit, models partially covered are hit on the roll of a 4+</Rule>
					<Description>The Dwarf player can cause the machine to explode at any time. If the machine explodes, place the large circular template on the machine. The machine is destroyed and all models under the template suffer a Strength 4 hit (models partially covered are hit on the roll of a 4+)</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Skewering</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>Once per game the Bolt Thrower hits on a 2+ with no modifiers</Rule>
					<Description>This rune may only be inscribed on a Bolt Thrower. Once per game the Bolt Thrower hits on a 2+ with no modifiers. You must choose to use this rune before rolling to hit</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Forging</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>Allows to re-roll Artillery dice when he rolls a Misfire</Rule>
					<Description>Can only be placed on a cannon. Allows Dwarf player to re-roll Artillery dice when he rolls a Misfire. If you roll a Misfire when rolling Artillery dice either to hit or to bounce, then you can roll again. You are bound by the second roll even if it's another Misfire. Multiples have no effect</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Reloading</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>Can shoot every turn, as long as there is at least one crewman left</Rule>
					<Description>Cannon can shoot every turn, as long as there is at least one crewman left, even if the machine has rolled a 2-3 on the Misfire table in the previous turn. Multiples have no effect</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Accuracy</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>May re-roll the Scatter dice</Rule>
					<Description>May only be put on a Stone Thrower. The Dwarf player may re-roll the Scatter dice if he wishes, enabling the machine to shoot more accurately. If you re-roll the dice, you must accept the result of the second roll. Multiples have no effect</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Fortune</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>May re-roll a dice rolled on the machine's Misfire chart</Rule>
					<Description>If a machine has the Rune of Fortune the player may re-roll a dice rolled on the machine's Misfire chart. For example, you can re-roll a result on the Cannon Misfire chart, or the Misfire chart for Stone Throwers. However, you must accept the result of the second dice roll. Multiples have no effect</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Valiant Rune</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<Description>As long as their war machine is not destroyed, the war machine crew are Unbreakable</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Penetrating</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>The Strength of a hit from the war machine increases by +1</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Penetrating</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>The Strength of a hit from the war machine increases by +2</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Penetrating</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>The Strength of a hit from the war machine increases by +3</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Flakkson's Rune of Seeking</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>+1 to hit rolls against targets with the Fly special ability</Rule>
					<Description>Each rune adds +1 to the bolt thrower's to hit rolls against targets with the Fly special ability</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Flakkson's Rune of Seeking</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>+2 to hit rolls against targets with the Fly special ability</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Flakkson's Rune of Seeking</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>+3 to hit rolls against targets with the Fly special ability</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Stalwart Rune</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="1"/>
					<Description>This rune adds +1 to the crew's combat resolution score</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Stalwart Rune</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="2"/>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Stalwart Rune</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="3"/>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Burning</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>5</Points>
					<Only>Engineering</Only>
					<Rule>Flaming Attacks</Rule>
					<Description>The war engine makes flaming attacks</Description>
				</Additional>
			</EngineeringRunes>
			<TalismanicRunes>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Kingship</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<Stubborn/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Description>This rune may only be engraved on the crown of a Dwarf Lord. The Lord and the unit he leads are stubborn and completely immune to fear and terror</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Balance</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Only>Runesmith</Only>
					<Rule>Remove one dice from the opponent's pile of Power dice and add it to his own Dispel dice pile</Rule>
					<Description>During the enemy's Magic phase, this rune allows the Dwarf player to remove one dice from the opponent's pile of Power dice and add it to his own Dispel dice pile</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Spellbinding</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Only>Runesmith</Only>
					<Rule>+1 to all attempts to dispel</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Spite</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					<Description>This rune confers a 4+ Ward save</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Master Rune of Dismay</Name>
					<MasterRunic/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>Once per battle, at the end of the Dwarf player's turn, all enemy units on the field which are not Immune to Psychology must take a Leadership test, if they fail, they are so dismayed that they may not declare a charge in their following turn's Movement phase</Rule>
					<Description>The horn may be sounded once per battle, at the end of the Dwarf player's turn. All enemy units on the field which are not Immune to Psychology must take a Leadership test. If they fail, they are so dismayed that they may not declare a charge in their following turn's Movement phase. Units that move in the compulsory Movement phase are not affected</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Spelleater Rune</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Only>Runesmith</Only>
					<Rule>Once per battle, may automatically dispel one enemy spell, roll of a 4+ the enemy spell is lost and can't be cast again for the rest of the game</Rule>
					<Description>This rune may only be used once per battle, and will stop enemy magic instantly. The rune may be played to automatically dispel one enemy spell - there is no need to roll. This rune won't help against spells cast with Irresistable Force. Also, when the enemy spell is cancelled, roll a dice. On the roll of a 4+ the enemy spell is lost and can't be cast again for the rest of the game</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Fate</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<WardForFirstWound Val="2"/>
					<Description>The model has a 2+ Ward save against the first wound suffered</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Spellbreaking</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Runesmith</Only>
					<Rule>Once per battle, may automatically dispel one enemy spell</Rule>
					<Description>This rune may only be used once per battle, and will stop enemy magic instantly. The rune may be played to automatically dispel one enemy spell - there is no need to roll. This rune won't help against spells cast with Irresistable Force</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Luck</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>May re-roll any 1 dice roll during the game</Rule>
					<Description>This rune allows its bearer to re-roll any single dice roll once during the game</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Luck</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>May re-roll any 2 dice roll during the game</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Luck</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Rule>May re-roll any 3 dice roll during the game</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Warding</Name>
					<Runic Val="1"/>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>+1 dice to any attempt to dispel enemy spells cast against the character or the unit he is with</Rule>
					<Description>This rune adds a dice to any attempt to dispel enemy spells cast against the character or the unit he is with</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Warding</Name>
					<Runic Val="2"/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>+2 dice to any attempt to dispel enemy spells cast against the character or the unit he is with</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of Warding</Name>
					<Runic Val="3"/>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Rule>+3 dice to any attempt to dispel enemy spells cast against the character or the unit he is with</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of the Furnace</Name>
					<Runic/>
					<Points>5</Points>
					<Rule>Immune to fire and cannot be affected by fire attacks</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer of this rune is immune to fire and cannot be affected by fire attacks (including magical fire, the flames of a Skaven warpfire thrower, etc)</Description>
				</Additional>
			</TalismanicRunes>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Thorek Ironbrow</Name>
				<Points>505</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Mount>Anvil of Doom</Mount>
				<Description>Thorek Ironbrow is a Runelord like unto those of legend. In the best of his moods, he is fiercely irate and a living terror to his apprentices in the weapons shops of Karak Azul, where he has ruled for centuries on end. A traditionalist in every sense, Thorek cannot abide new technology, and takes every opportunity to speak his mind on "new inventions". Fortunately, he lends not just his council, but also his strong arm to Thorgrim Grudgebearer. Like his High King, Thorek too longs to reclaim the Dwarf Empire of old, but he also has a personal quest — he seeks lost relics of the ancient days. For this reason, Thorek is extremely active and can be found aiding throngs from many different clans and holds.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='6' BS='4' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='3' A='2' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Rune of Doom</Rule>
						<Rule>Assistant at the forge</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Klad Brakak</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
						<Rule>If the victim suffers one or more unsaved Wounds, any magic armour, magic helmets and magic shields they were equipped with are destroyed and cannot be used for the remainder of the game</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Thorek's rune-armour</Name>
						<ArmourTo Val="1"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>King Alrik Ranulfsson</Name>
				<Points>425</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Mount>Anvil Guards</Mount>
				<Description>Alrik is the current King of Karak Hirn, and a heavy traditionalist even by Dwarf standards. King Alrik doesn't allow his armies to include more Thunderers than Quarrellers.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='7' BS='4' S='4' T='5' W='5' I='4' A='6' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<General/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Shield Bearers</Rule>
						<Rule>Friendly Dwarfs within 18" of him may use his Leadership value, rather than those within 12" as normal</Rule>
						<Rule>Gyrocopters, Flame Cannons and Organ Guns cost twice the points they do normally, army cannot have more models armed with a handgun than a crossbow</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Axe of Retribution</Name>
						<Rule>Nominate one enemy character or monster at the beginning of the game: the model may re-roll misses in close combat when attacking this enemy model</Rule>
						<Rule>If character scores a hit against an enemy with a magic weapon, the enemy's magic weapon is destroyed immediately</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Hrappi-klad</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="4"/>
						<Rule>2+ Ward save against missile attacks only</Rule>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Kurgaz's Shield</Name>
						<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Helm of Eagles</Name>
						<Rule>At the start of each Dwarf turn, Alrik may gaze at one enemy unit: opponent must reveal any hidden troops within the unit as well as all magic items carried by models within the unit</Rule>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Karak-Hirn's Book of Grudges</Name>
						<Rule>In battle, this has the effect of allowing friendly units within 12" of King Alrik to re-roll failed break tests, just like an army standard</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Lord</Name>
				<Points>135</Points>
				<Description>Dwarf Lords are those Thanes who have been promoted to lead a dwarf throng into battle as the supreme commander. When a Dwarf King sends an army to defeat the enemies of the dwarf race, defend his hold, or to send missions and expeditions, the King appoints several clans and their extended families to answer the call of battle. Among the Thanes of every clan who were given the task, they will appoint one of their number to be the helm. Each of these dwarfs must not only be a capable warrior but also a leader, a tactician, credible, and have the longest beard outside of the greybeards. The lord's level of equipment depends on his clan's standing; wealthy clan thanes wear suits of gromril Armour, the strongest Armour known to dwarf kind, and use powerful rune weapons, while poorer clan thanes use iron armour and a potent rune weapon. Most dwarf throngs are led by those from the royal clan, related to the king, these dwarfs hold the actual title of "lord" but Thanes more often than not will become or rather take the role of "lord" if need be.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='7' BS='4' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='4' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="125" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Pistol Points="10" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Crossbow Points="15" Dependency="Range"/>
					<DwarfHandgun Points="21" Dependency="Range"/>
					<LightArmour Points="3" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="6" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<GromrilArmour Points="12" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Runelord</Name>
				<Points>140</Points>
				<Group>Runesmith</Group>
				<Description>Revered by their holds, the Runelords are the greatest of all the Runesmiths. As custodians of ancient lore, they are naturally suspicious and jealously guard the secrets and rituals of their hammercraft. On the battlefield, Runelords dampen and channel the magic of their foes, rending it harmless. They alone have the ability to forge magical items using powerful runes – a skill passed on to a worthy relation, or taken to the grave.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='6' BS='4' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='3' A='2' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="150" Type="Hero"/>
					<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6"/>
					<LightArmour Points="3" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="6" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<GromrilArmour Points="12" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
					<Option>
						<Name>Anvil of Doom</Name>
						<Points>200</Points>
						<AddToWard Val="5"/>
						<Mount/>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Daemon Slayer</Name>
				<Points>130</Points>
				<Description>Not all who hunt Dragons find their death. Of those few that survive, most do so simply because Dragons are so rare that they despair of ever finding one. These survivors, more convinced than ever that the Ancestor Gods have denied them the release of death, choose to follow in Grimnir's footsteps. They go to the far north, to the Chaos Wastes, and embark upon the path of the Daemon Slayer. At this point, most Slayers now believe that their inability to find honourable death has an entirely deeper meaning: Grimnir has found them worthy to help him close the warp gate.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='7' BS='3' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='5' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<NotALeader/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="6" Dependency="Weapon"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Thane</Name>
				<Points>55</Points>
				<Description>Thanes are the patriarchs of a dwarf clan. In times of war, Thanes lead their clan to battle in every dwarf army. In a dwarf throng, thanes will lead their forces to victory by advising the Lord (also a fellow thane) what course of action to take, although the final battlefield decision will fall to the lord. Thanes fight at the front of their clan leading his friends and family behind him. Some clans have their own personal heraldry and colours and these will be carried by Thanes as battle standards of their clan.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='6' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='3' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Pistol Points="7" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Crossbow Points="10" Dependency="Range"/>
					<DwarfHandgun Points="14" Dependency="Range"/>
					<LightArmour Points="2" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<GromrilArmour Points="8" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Runesmith</Name>
				<Points>70</Points>
				<Group>Runesmith</Group>
				<Description>Runesmiths are the closest thing Dwarfs have to magic users in their culture. Runesmiths learn the ancient crafts of working metal and magic into Runes of power. The oldest and most respected of them are the Runemasters. The Runesmiths are members of the Guild of Runesmiths, which is said to have its origins in the days of the Ancestor God Grungni. The Guild claims descent from his son Morgrim, and it is for this reason they sometimes refer to themselves as the "Clan of Morgrim", though they are not the only clan who claim descent from the mighty god. All Runesmiths are kin, although the relation is often somewhat remote. Each family hands down its craft through the generations. When a Runesmith feels that the time is right, he will take one of his young relatives as an apprentice, teaching him all he knows about the art of Rune making. However, Runesmiths are so protective of their knowledge that many of them fail to find a worthy successor, and end up taking their art with them to the grave. The Guild of Runesmiths has great respect in their society. At the very least a Runesmith will have endured hundreds of years of harsh tutelage from their masters, and older Runemsiths will have centuries of runecraft and gathering of lost secrets reflected in the length of their beards and their tough, cantankerous demeanour.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='5' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='2' A='2' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="75" Type="Hero"/>
					<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4"/>
					<LightArmour Points="2" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<GromrilArmour Points="8" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Engineer</Name>
				<Points>65</Points>
				<Group>Engineering</Group>
				<Description>Engineers, as the name suggests, are the Dwarfen masters of technology and gadgets, continuing a long tradition of engineering craftsmanship. They employ their expertise to great effect in combat, shooting blunderbusses, throwing grenades at the enemy and even calling down artillery bombardments. In the melee, they employ even more explosives or pummel their foes into submission using their engineering spanners and other assorted tools.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='4' W='2' I='2' A='2' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Artillery Master</Rule>
						<Rule>Extra crewman</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Pistol Points="7" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<BracePistols Points="14" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<DwarfHandgun Points="14"/>
					<LightArmour Points="2" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<GromrilArmour Points="8" Dependency="Armour"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Dragon Slayer</Name>
				<Points>65</Points>
				<Description>Those Dwarfs who survive their careers as Giant Slayers become convinced that their disgrace is so terrible that the Ancestor Gods have denied them an honourable death. They engage in a ritual that involves self-inflicted scarring. As well as giving expression to the Slayer's growing sense of self-loathing, the scarring ritual symbolises the Slayer's dedication to following the mythical exploits of Grimnir. Through this ritual, they become Dragon Slayers.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='6' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='4' A='3' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<NotALeader/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Anvil of Doom</Name>
				<Profile M='3' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='2' A='4' Ld='10' AS='4'/>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Warriors</Name>
				<Points>7</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Warriors will form the backbone of every Dwarf clan and every throng in every engagement. These uncompromising warriors hail from one of the many clans within a Hold, which consist mostly of youths barely a hundred years of age. When in combat, these warriors will form within a regiment of the same Clan and are often put at the very front of the fighting. Determined and arrogant in equal measure, Dwarf warriors make the most steadfast of fighters in the Old World.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Dwarfs always have the Hatred Orcs, Goblins and Skaven</Rule>
						<Rule>Do not need to pass a Leadership test in order to march, regardless of the proximity of enemy</Rule>
						<Rule>+1 bonus to any Parry save in a turn in which unit is charged</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightNativeArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<HeavyArmour PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<GreatWeapon PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Veteran"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Crossbowmen</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Since the Dwarfs first came to the Worlds Edge Mountains the crossbow has been the dwarf's favourite ranged weapon. It will easily beat the goblin's weak bows, and it is even capable of dropping a heavily armoured Black Orc dead in its track. The number of Dwarfs that use crossbow has fallen some in recent time as more and more started taking up handguns, but the crossbow will never disappear entirely. The Quarrellers that remain are a stubborn bunch, preferring to trust their own eyes over those new-fangled sights. If nothing else, many begrudge the cost of gunpowder when all a crossbow takes is a little bit of elbow grease and a determined eye.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Crossbow/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Veteran"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Thunderers</Name>
				<Points>14</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Although some more old fashion or traditional dwarfs still regard the handgun with some suspicion, it has become a common sight, almost as common as the crossbow. The Dwarfs who specialise themselves in using the handgun have become known as Thunderers. Being methodical as well as mechanically gifted, they will simply keep on loading and firing in a disciplined manner, even when the enemy is right up close, rarely suffering the misfires that would afflict less-disciplined troops. Many Thunderers will have crafted their own handguns, incorporating personal preferences and additional improvements of their own. There are a lot of rivalries between Thunderers as to who has the most accurate handgun, which has resulted in the Dwarf handguns being the most precise weapons of their kind in the world.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<DwarfHandgun/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Veteran"/>
						<DwarfPistols Points="2" For="Veteran"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Miners</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>10-20</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Description>When a Dwarf hold goes to war, many mining clans will send their warriors to battle. As a gesture of pride in their profession, they will tend to carry picks rather than axes, but such is their skill with them that this is no disadvantage. There are many benefits to having such troops in an army, notably, they can use their skills to tunnel beneath the enemy and gain the advantage of surprise. Equipped with deadly explosives, these Dwarfs can be devastating when fighting a formation of enemy troops.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>Underground Advance</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Pick</Name>
						<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
						<HitLast/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Prospector"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Rangers</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>10-20</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Description>Rangers are Dwarfs who serve as scouts and hunters to a Dwarf Karak. Rangers spend most of their time on the surface to keep constant vigil over the Karak's borders, hunt game, and map the land, eventually becoming a Dwarf King's eyes and ears to the events that happen in the outside world. Dwarfs are a mountain race and expert miners, and as such the common dwarf will treat a ranger with suspicion and distrust. Rangers are considered the first line of defence, holding the enemy back by harassing them with hit and run tactics using well-placed traps and bolt fire until an allied army arrives.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Scouts/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Foresters</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Crossbow PointsPerModel="5"/>
					<ThrowingAxe PointsPerModel="3"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Veteran"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Hammerers</Name>
				<Points>14</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Description>Hammerers are forged in battle and selected for their bold and courageous nature. Renowned for their elite fighting skills and steadfast loyalty, Hammerers are the preferred bodyguards for many Thanes and Lords. As their name suggests, these warriors are equipped with massive Warhammer that is imbued with Runes, making their swings and attacks all the more powerful.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>Bodyguard</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Gate Keeper"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Longbeards</Name>
				<Points>14</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>A Dwarf Longbeard is the oldest, most experienced warrior within a Dwarf Throng, a fact evidenced by the length of their beards. These ensure that they receive the proper respect from other Dwarfs, who have been taught quite rightly to always respect their elders. Longbeards have fought in more wars, beaten more enemies, and endured greater hardships than any young Dwarf could possibly imagine. They constantly grumble about how today's Goblins are far smaller and weaker than they used to be, and how nothing is as well made as it was in their day. No young Dwarf would dare argue with them, for they indeed have the experience and the beard to prove it. In battle, Longbeards are able to demonstrate their time-won skills, showing disdain for even the smallest shifts in fortune that would throw less experienced warriors into confusion. Forming into their own regiments, these are considered the veterans within a Dwarf army.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Greatbeard"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Ironbreakers</Name>
				<Points>13</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>In a labyrinth of tunnels the Ironbreakers stand guard. The protectors of all that is sacred, the Ironbreakers battle tirelessly to prevent the desecration of their homes. These mighty warriors are unparalleled in their fighting capability, where their smalls numbers are often compensated with full suits of high-quality Gromril weapons and armour, the strongest metal in the world. Impervious, implacable and immovable, these warriors are legendary tunnel fighters.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<GromrilArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Ironbeard"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Slayers</Name>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Size>10-30</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Description>Slayers seek death in combat in order to atone for some wrongdoing. Although they seek death, Dwarfs are incapable of deliberately fighting to lose, and so always enter the fray to win. Therefore Slayers spend as much time as possible for improving their warrior skills. Slayers deliberately seek uneven combat, for example by entering a Goblin stronghold alone. Trolls are considered the ideal opponents, as the Dwarf's death is almost assured. Their way of life weeds out all but the toughest and most determined warriors so that those Slayers who survive for any period time are invariably exceptionally tough, violent, and extremely dangerous.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Unbreakable/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12"/>
						<Champion Points="15" Name="Giant Slayers"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Cannon</Name>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<ModelsInPack Val="4"/>
				<Description>The most common cannon within the Dwarf's arsenal, these cannons are reliable and crewed by Dwarfs with many years of military experience. Though these cannons are noticeably smaller than their human counterparts, they are nonetheless just as deadly but far more accurate.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<WarMachine/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Bolt Thrower</Name>
				<Points>45</Points>
				<ModelsInPack Val="4"/>
				<Description>Bolt Throwers are simply larger versions of the crossbow, able to fire heavier bolts over greater distances. The Bolt Thrower remains an important part of the Dwarf arsenal because it can be built and maintained cheaply and is accurate enough to bring down monsters such as Wyverns or Trolls with a well-judged shot.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<WarMachine/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Stone Thrower</Name>
				<Points>85</Points>
				<ModelsInPack Val="4"/>
				<Description>This siege-equipment were originally simple stone-throwers, used previously to defend the approaches to Dwarf holds from enemy invasion. It was after the outbreak of the War of Vengeance, that the Dwarfs took to engraving their grudges onto the stones they fired. Ever since then, it is an almost commonplace for these stones to be engraved with runes that magnify its destructive power.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<WarMachine/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Organ Gun</Name>
				<Points>125</Points>
				<ModelsInPack Val="4"/>
				<Description>Should the enemy prove far too numerous for a single cannon-ball to topple, the Dwarfs will sometimes aim their array of Organ Guns at the enemy. Able to fire several smaller cannon-balls at once, this weapon can decimate whole regiments of enemy infantry in very close range.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<WarMachine/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Flame Cannon</Name>
				<Points>140</Points>
				<ModelsInPack Val="4"/>
				<Description>These experimental cannons were one of the latest inventions put into field-testing by the Engineers Guild of Zhufbar. Having the ability to belch white-hot alchemic fire into tightly-knotted groups of enemy formations, these weapons have gained a fearsome reputation in the eyes of their enemies.</Description>
				<Profile M='3' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='2' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<WarMachine/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Gyrocopter</Name>
				<Points>140</Points>
				<Description>Designed by the Engineers Guild and inspired by combining dragon and drilling machine the original Gyrocopter design took centuries to gain acceptance. The Gyrocopter is a small yet nimble war machine. It can be equipped with either a steam gun or the dragon-headed brimstone gun.</Description>
				<Profile WS="4" S="3" T="5" W="3" I="2" A="1" Ld="9" AS="4"/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fly/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Dwarfs always have the Hatred Orcs, Goblins and Skaven</Rule>
						<Rule>Crashes</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Steam gun</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>