<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Imprint>
			<Army>Vampire Counts</Army>
			<Edition>7</Edition>
			<Released>2008</Released>
			<Authors>Gav Thorpe</Authors>
			<Description>The Vampire Counts are amongst the most legendary factions of Vampires to have ever terrorised the civilised lands of the Old World, all of whom are members of the unholy Von Carstein bloodline. From the Imperial government and the patriotic citizenry of the Empire, the Vampire Counts are considered by many to be fiends without equal. They seek only to topple the civilisations of the living and supplant them with an Undead Empire that will reign forever as Lords of the Night. The Vampire Counts are powerful necromancers as well as warriors, given supernatural enhancements to their strength, cunning, beauty, and ambition. However, these vampires, for all their power and cunning, are ultimately base, selfish creatures driven by the same motivations as the mortals they deem themselves superior to. They are remorseless in their advance, killing without thought of mercy or compassion, and whose motives are entirely based on their own selfish desires. For all their refinement, these vampires are nothing but rotting corpses held together by Dark Magic and the horrific consumption of mortal blood</Description>
		</Imprint>
		<Styles>
			<Colors>
				<Front>000000</Front>
				<Back>3e3e3e</Back>
				<Grid>d9d9d9</Grid>
				<Tooltip>a2a2a2</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>b1b1b1, 9e9e9e, 777777</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<Images>
				<Files>
					<Cover/>
					<Symbol/>
					<Illustration/>
				</Files>
				<Folders>
					<Units/>
				</Folders>
			</Images>
		</Styles>
		<Naming>
			<Internal>Vampires</Internal>
			<MagicItems>Artefacts of Death</MagicItems>
			<MagicPowers>Vampiric Powers</MagicPowers>
		</Naming>
		<Magic>
			<Name>Lore of the Vampires</Name>
			<Options>Lore of Death</Options>
			<Magic>
				<Spell Name="Invocation of Nehek" Cast="4"/>
				<Spell Name="Raise Dead" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Vanhel's Danse Macabre" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Gaze of Nagash" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Curse of Years" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Wind of Undeath" Cast="12"/>
				<Spell Name="Summon Undead Horde" Cast="12"/>
			</Magic>
			<Enemy>The Empire, Lore of Fire</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Fireball" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Flaming Sword of Rhuin" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="The Burning Head" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Fiery Blast" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Conflagration of Doom" Cast="13"/>
				<Spell Name="Wall of Fire" Cast="14"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<Local>
			<SpecialRules>
				<Vampire/>
				<Ethereal/>
				<MayUseInvocation>The Vampire may use Invocation of Nehek to increase units of Skeleton Warriors beyond their starting size, and adds +1 to his casting roll when casting Invocation of Nehek on these units</MayUseInvocation>
				<FlamingAttacks/>
			</SpecialRules>
			<Options>
				<Barding>
					AddToArmour: 6
				</Barding>
			</Options>
		</Local>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<VampirePowers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Spectral Form</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>The Vampire is Ethereal. However, it may not join non-Ethereal units, nor may it be mounted or take any magic items</Rule>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Ghoulkin</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>If your army contains any Vampires with this power, your units of Crypt Ghouls (and accompanying characters) may make a march move before the game. This move is made after deployment, but before the dice roll for first turn.</Rule>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Supernatural Horror</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Terror/>
					<Description>The Vampire causes Terror</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Master of the Black Arts</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>The Vampire generates an additional 2 Power dice for itself in each of its own Magic phases</Rule>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Forbidden Lore</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>In addition to Invocation of Nehek the Vampire knows all of the spells from either the Lore of the Vampires or any one of the Lores of Magic</Rule>
					<Description>In addition to Invocation of Nehek the Vampire knows all of the spells from either the Lore of the Vampires or any one of the Lores of Magic in the Warhammer rulebook (except Lore of Life!)</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Dark Acolyte</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToCast Val="1"/>
					<AddToWizard Val="1"/>
					<Description>This Vampire has an additional Magic level</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Flying Horror</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>Fly</Rule>
					<Description>This Vampire has the Fly special rule</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Infinite Hatred</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Reroll>ToHit</Reroll>
					<Description>The Vampire Hates all enemies and may re-roll failed rolls to hit in every round of close combat</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Hunter in the Dark</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Scout/>
					<Only>Infantry</Only>
					<Description>If on foot, the Vampire has the Scout special rule</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Red Fury</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<PredatoryFighter/>
					<Description>For each unsaved wound that the Vampire causes it gets to immediately make an additional attack. These additional attacks do not benefit from the Red Fury rule. The Red Fury ability cannot be combined with a great weapon</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Avatar of Death</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
					<Description>The Vampire wears heavy armour and is armed with either a great weapon, hand weapon and shield or two hand weapons</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Dread Knight</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Lance/>
					<ArmourTo Val="2"/>
					<Description>The Vampire has a lance, heavy armour, a shield and rides a barded Nightmare</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Aura of Dark Majesty</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>All enemy units within 6" of one or more Vampires with Aura of Dark Majesty suffer a -1 penalty to their Leadership (cumulative with any other modifiers)</Rule>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Walking Death</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="1"/>
					<Description>The presence of one or more Vampires with this power in a combat adds +1 to their side's combat resolution</Description>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Beguile</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>At the beginning of the Close Combat phase, after challenges, select one model in contact with the Vampire. The Vampire may re-roll to Wound against the chosen model unless the target passes a Leadership test with a -3 modifier</Rule>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Lord of the Dead</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<MayUseInvocation/>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Summon Creatures of the Night</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<MayUseInvocation/>
				</Powers>
				<Powers>
					<Name>Summon Ghouls</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<MayUseInvocation/>
				</Powers>
			</VampirePowers>
			<CommonMagicItems>
				<SwordOfStriking Points="15"/>
				<SwordOfBattle Points="15"/>
				<SwordOfMight Points="15"/>
				<BitingBlade Points="5"/>
				<EnchantedShield Points="15"/>
				<TalismanOfProtection Points="15"/>
				<StaffOfSorcery Points="35"/>
				<DispellScroll Points="25"/>
				<PowerStone Points="20"/>
				<WarBanner Points="25"/>
			</CommonMagicItems>
			<MagicWeapons>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Frostblade</Name>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<AutoDeath/>
					<Description>If a model suffers one or more Wounds from the Frostblade (after saves, etc) they are slain outright and lose all remaining Wounds</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Dreadlance</Name>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Lance/>
					<AutoHit/>
					<Description>Lance. Attacks with the Dreadlance hit automatically</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Black Axe of Krell</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Only>Wight King</Only>
					<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
					<MultiWounds Val="D3"/>
					<HitLast/>
					<Test Bet="Wound" Context="Wound" Profile="Toughness"/>
					<Description>Great weapon. The Black Axe does D3 Wounds. Any model wounded by die Black Axe but not slain must pass a Toughness test at the start of each of its subsequent turns or suffer an additional Wound</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Blood Drinker</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Only>Vampire</Only>
					<Rule>For each unsaved wound inflicted by the Blood Drinker, the wielder (or unit he is with) immediately regains a single Wound suffered earlier in the battle, as if Invocation of Nehek had been cast on them</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Skabscrath</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Terror/>
					<Description>The bearer causes Terror</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Sword of Kings</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<Description>This weapon has the Killing Blow special rule. If given to a Wight King it scores a Killing Blow on a 5+</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Tomb Blade</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>If the bearer is in a unit of Skeleton Warriors, for each model he slays in close combat an extra model is added to the unit following the rules given in the Invocation of Nehek spell. Newly created models arc equipped the same as the rest of the unit</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Balefire Spike</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Lance/>
					<FlamingAttacks/>
					<Description>Lanee. Attacks with the Balefire Spike are flaming</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</MagicWeapons>
			<MagicArmours>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Walach's Bloody Hauberk</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="4"/>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Description>The wearer has a 4+ armour save that may be combined with steeds, shield, etc. Walach's Bloody Hauberk also confers a 5+ ward save</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>The Accursed Armour</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<AddToToughness Val="1"/>
					<AddToWeaponSkill Val="-3"/>
					<AddToInitiative Val="-3"/>
					<Description>Heavy armour. The wearer has +1 Toughness, but suffers -3 Weapon Skill and -3 Initiative</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>The Flayed Hauberk</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<ArmourTo Val="2"/>
					<Description>The Flayed Hauberk grants the wearer a 2+ armour save that cannot be improved by any means (shield, mount and so on)</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Night</Name>
					<Only>Infantry</Only>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Rule>Enemies suffer a -2 to hit penalty</Rule>
					<Description>Models on foot only. Heavy armour. As long as the wearer is on his own, enemies suffer a -2 to hit penalty when shooting at him</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Nightshroud</Name>
					<Only>Infantry</Only>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Rule>Enemy models lose all charging bonuses, lose the Always Strikes First rule</Rule>
					<Description>Light armour. Enemy models wishing to attack the wearer lose all charging bonuses, lose the Always Strikes First rule (if diey have it) and have their Initiative reduced to 1</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>The Cadaverous Cuirass</Name>
					<Only>Vampire</Only>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<NoKillingBlow/>
					<ImmuneToPoison/>
					<Description>Heavy armour. Killing Blow and/or Poisoned Attacks have no additional effect against the wearer</Description>
				</Armour>
			</MagicArmours>
			<EnchantedItems>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Hand of Dust</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Bound Spell (power level 3). When successfully used, this item inflicts 2D6 Strength 5 hits on one unit in base contact with the bearer, distributed as shooting hits. Roll a dice each time the Hand is used. On a 1, the power is exhausted and it cannot be used again during the battle</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rod of Flaming Death</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Bound Spell (power level 3). When used, this item casts a magic missile with a range of 18" that inflicts D6 Strength 4 hits. Any unit taking one or more wounds from this attack must immediately take a Panic test. Roll a dice each time the Rod of Flaming Death is used. On a 1, the power is exhausted and the Rod of Flaming Death cannot be used again during the battle</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Helm of Commandment</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>If the wearer is not in combat, one friendly Undead unit within 12" (not mounts) may use his Weapon Skill instead of their own for that Close Combat phase</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Cursed Book</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>For one round of combat, enemy models are reduced to WS 1 when rolling to hit the bearer</Rule>
					<Description>One Use Only. For one round of combat, enemy models are reduced to WS 1 when rolling to hit the bearer</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Talisman of the Lycni</Name>
					<Only>Vampire</Only>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<MovementTo Val="9"/>
					<Description>A Vampire with the Talisman of the Lycni has a Movement value of 9</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</EnchantedItems>
			<Talismans>
				<Additional>
					<Name>The Carstein Ring</Name>
					<Only>Vampire</Only>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Rule>The first time the wearer of this ring is slain roll a D6 at the end of the phase. On a score of 2+ the vampire is immediately returned to 'life' with a single Wound</Rule>
					<Description>The first time the wearer of this ring is slain roll a D6 at the end of the phase. On a score of 2+ the vampire is immediately returned to 'life' with a single Wound. The returning model must be placed in the front rank of a friendly unit anywhere on the battlefield (even one in close combat). If there is no unit for the Vampire to join, it is removed as a casualty</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Crown of the Damned</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					<Stupidity/>
					<Description>Grants the bearer a 4+ ward save, but the bearer is subject to Stupidity</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Wristbands of Black Gold</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>3+ ward save against ranged attacks of any kind (including war machines, templates, magic missiles, etc)</Rule>
					<Description>Grants the bearer a 3+ ward save against ranged attacks of any kind (including war machines, templates, magic missiles, etc)</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>The Gem of Blood</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<WardForFirstWound Val="2"/>
					<Description>When the wearer suffers its first wound in close combat (before saves, Killing Blow, multiple Wounds, etc), the gem activates. Roll a dice. On a roll of a 1 the wearer suffers the Wound as normal, and an additional Wound with no armour save allowed. On a 2+ the Wound is saved, and is rebounded onto the model that caused it, with no armour save allowed</Description>
				</Additional>
			</Talismans>
			<ArcaneItems>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Skull Staff</Name>
					<Points>65</Points>
					<Rule>The bearer receives +1 to casting and dispelling rolls</Rule>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Staff of Damnation</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>Bound Spell (power level 3). When the spell is successfully cast, friendly Undead models (and their mounts) within 12" of the bearer and in close combat each make a single attack. Any wounds caused are not counted for combat resolution in the subsequent Close Combat phase. Roll a dice each time the Staff of Damnation is used. On a 1, the power of the Staff is exhausted and it cannot be used again during the battle</Rule>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>The Book of Arkhan</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>Bound Spell (power level 3). This item casts the spell Vanhel's Danse Macabre. Roll a dice each time the Book of Arkhan is used. On a 1, its power is exhausted and cannot be used again during the battle</Rule>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Sceptre de Noirot</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>The bearer raises D3+9 Zombies with each successful casting of Raise Dead</Rule>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Crimson Gem of Lahmia</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>At any time in the Magic phase, the bearer may sacrifice a Wound to gain one power dice</Rule>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Black Periapt</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>The Black Periapt allows the bearer to save one of his own unused power dice or one of the army's unused dispel dice at the end of any Magic phase, and then add it to his side's power or dispel dice pool in the next Magic phase</Rule>
					<Description>The Black Periapt allows the bearer to save one of his own unused power dice or one of the army's unused dispel dice at the end of any Magic phase, and then add it to his side's power or dispel dice pool in the next Magic phasee</Description>
				</Arcane>
			</ArcaneItems>
			<MagicStandards>
				<Banner>
					<Name>The Drakenhof Banner</Name>
					<Points>125</Points>
					<Regeneration/>
					<Description>All models in the unit have Regeneration</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>The Flag of Blood Keep</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Rule>4+ Ward save against ranged attacks of any kind</Rule>
					<Description>Grants the unit a 4+ Ward save against ranged attacks of any kind (including war machines, templates, magic missiles, etc)</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of the Barrows</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<Rule>All Grave Guard, Black Knights and Wight Kings in the unit (not mounts) receive +1 to hit in close combat</Rule>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Screaming Banner</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>Enemy units taking a Fear test caused by the unit carrying this banner must roll one extra dice for their test and discard the one with the lowest result</Rule>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Royal Standard of Strigos</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Hate/>
					<Description>All models in the unit Hate all enemies</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Icon of Vengeance</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>The unit carrying this standard never takes casualties as a result of the general's death</Rule>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of the Dead Legion</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Treat the unit carrying the banner as having twice the unit strength it actually does</Rule>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Cursed Pennant of Mousillon</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>If the enemy capture this standard they immediately suffer D6 Strength 4 hits, distributed as shooting hits. The unit also suffer an additional D6 Strength 3 hits at the start of each of its turns</Rule>
					<Description>If the enemy capture this standard they immediately suffer D6 Strength 4 hits, distributed as shooting hits. The unit also suffer an additional D6 Strength 3 hits at the start of each of its turns. The unit may abandon the Cursed Pennant at any time, in which case it suffers no further hits, but the standard is lost and so will not bestow any victory points for being captured</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of the Endless Nightmare</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>The unit carrying this banner may add up to +4 to its combat resolution score for additional ranks, rather than the usual +3 bonus</Rule>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Standard of Hellish Vigour</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Description>The unit carrying the standard may make march moves, as if it were within 6" of a Vampire</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Standard of Everlasting Death</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>If the unit with this standard loses a combat, roll a D6. On a 4+, the unit suffers one less casualty than normal</Rule>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of Hellfire</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<FlamingAttacks/>
					<Description>All close combat attacks by models in the unit (not mounts) are magical flaming attacks</Description>
				</Banner>
			</MagicStandards>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Vlad von Carstein</Name>
				<Points>490</Points>
				<Group>Vampire</Group>
				<Character/>
				<Wizard>3</Wizard>
				<Image>VladCarstain</Image>
				<Description>Vlad von Carstein was the first and greatest of the Vampire Counts of Sylvania. A master swordsman and skilled general with no small aptitude in the magical arts, it was he who tainted the aristocracy of Sylvania with the curse of vampirism, and in so doing, created an Undead kingdom in the heart of the Empire.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='7' BS='5' S='5' T='5' W='3' I='7' A='5' Ld='10' Ward=''/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<Undead/>
					<Reroll>ToWound</Reroll>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="1"/>
					<Original>Enemy within 6" are at -1 Ld</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Blood Drinker</Name>
						<Rule>Each Wound restores one wound on Vlad or his unit</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Carstein Ring</Name>
						<Rule>The first time the wearer of this ring is slain roll a D6 at the end of the phase. On a score of 2+ the vampire is immediately returned to 'life' with a single Wound</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Count Mannfred</Name>
				<Points>475</Points>
				<Group>Vampire</Group>
				<Character/>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Image>Mannfred</Image>
				<Description>While Vlad von Carstein was the most physically powerful of the Vampire Counts, Mannfred was the most cunning. When Vlad was slain, Mannfred did not involve himself in the infighting that would see Konrad rise to prominence. Instead, he travelled far and wide, seeking to deepen his knowledge of necromantic lore. He made an unholy pilgrimage to the ancient tombs of Nehekhara and the ancient city of Lahmia, where he wrested the secrets of the Liche Priests from bone dry papyrus and scrolls made from human skin.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='7' BS='5' S='5' T='5' W='3' I='7' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Reroll>ToWound</Reroll>
					<MagicItems Count="2" Type="Hero"/>
					<Original>Vampiric Powers</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Sword of Unholy Power</Name>
						<Rule>For each unsaved Wound gains an extra dice in the Magic phase</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Armour of Templehof</Name>
						<AddToWounds Val="2"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Mount Name="Nightmare" Points="20"/>
					<Mount Name="Hellsteed" Points="30"/>
					<Mount Name="Abyssal Terror" Points="135"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Vampire Lord</Name>
				<Points>205</Points>
				<Group>Vampire</Group>
				<Wizard>2</Wizard>
				<Description>Vampire Lords are amongst the most powerful Vampires within a Vampiric bloodline. To be a Vampire Lord is to obtain a position from which would've seen lesser Vampires perished, for within Vampiric hierarchy, it is well known that only the strongest individual within their numbers are given the right to rule over others of their kind.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='7' BS='5' S='5' T='5' W='3' I='7' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<MagicPowers>100</MagicPowers>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="3" Points="50"/>
					<Mount Name="Nightmare" Points="20"/>
					<Mount Name="Hellsteed" Points="30"/>
					<Mount Name="Abyssal Terror" Points="135"/>
					<Mount Name="Zombie Dragon" Points="275"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Mannfred the Acolyte</Name>
				<Points>185</Points>
				<Group>Vampire</Group>
				<Character/>
				<Wizard>2</Wizard>
				<Description>This is Mannfred as he was during the reign of Vlad. Although not as accomplished in the Black Art as he would become, Mannfred the Acolyte is still a skillful and formidable Necromancer.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='4' S='5' T='4' W='2' I='6' A='3' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<MagicItems Count="1" Type="Hero"/>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="1"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Sword of Unholy Power</Name>
						<Rule>For each unsaved Wound gains an extra dice in the Magic phase</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Mount Name="Nightmare" Points="20"/>
					<Mount Name="Abyssal Terror" Points="135"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Konrad von Carstein</Name>
				<Points>145</Points>
				<Group>Vampire</Group>
				<Character/>
				<Image>KonradCarstain</Image>
				<Description>There are few things more dangerous than a violent lunatic, but one of them is an immortal violent lunatic with the strength and speed of a Vampire. Adding a literal thirst for blood to Konrad's figurative one did little for the noble's stretched sanity. The first of the von Carsteins had considered this as a potential advantage, and Konrad was one of the last of the von Carsteins to be embraced into the family.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='7' BS='4' S='5' T='4' W='2' I='6' A='3' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Hate/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Gets +1 attack for each wound inflicted</Rule>
						<Rule>One Bar Short of a Belfry</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Sword of Waldenhof</Name>
						<MultiWounds Val="2"/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Isabella von Carstein</Name>
				<Points>90</Points>
				<Group>Vampire</Group>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Daughter of the mad Count Otto von Drak, Isabella was much like many of her noble counterparts. She was vain, immoral and selfish, and cared little for anything that did not affect her personal comfort and standing. Though very intelligent, she had a classical, rather than practical, education. She was considered somewhat strange for her love of some of the more male pursuits, such as hunting and falconry, over needlework and music.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='4' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='6' A='2' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>May re-rolls to wound agains one enemy unless it pass a Ld test at -3</Rule>
						<Rule>Beloved of Vlad</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Blood Chalice of Bathori</Name>
						<Rule>At the start of each friendly Magic phase may regains a single wound lost earlier in the battle</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Necromancer</Name>
				<Points>55</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Description>Necromancers are widely regarded as twisted and corrupt individuals who are obsessed with death and the avoidance of it at all costs. They are used by those magically inept Vampires to animate the broken corpses of their servants and return them to battle. To learn such dark magic, these desperate men will seek out a Necromancer or a Vampire to teach them, though this task is not without its own dangers and many aspirants have found themselves dying a grim death at the hands of their would-be tutor. Those that do survive invariably become powerful spell-casters, though their sanity is forever broken by the horrors they have witnessed.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Wizard"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Mount Name="Nightmare" Points="15"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Vampire</Name>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<Group>Vampire</Group>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Description>Vampires are incredibly powerful Undead creatures. Unlike most of the Undead, Vampires retain all of their intelligence and will, and hence all of their ambition and desire. This makes them very dangerous indeed, for they can continue to grow and learn, spending eternity perfecting their skills and honing their plans and schemes. Vampires serve as the lieutenants of an Undead army, whose combat prowess and adequate skills in Necromancy can help determine the outcome of a battle.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='4' S='5' T='4' W='2' I='6' A='3' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<MagicPowers>50</MagicPowers>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Mount Name="Nightmare" Points="8"/>
					<Mount Name="Hellsteed" Points="20"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Wight King</Name>
				<Points>75</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Group>Wight King</Group>
				<Description>Wight Kings were once ancient and immensely powerful Human Warlords that have once occupied the lands of present-day Sylvania in the days before the founding of the Empire. When imbued with Dark Magic, these ancient warlords rise from their crypts as Wight Kings, eyes glowing with unnatural life. The merest touch of their blade can drain the life from their foes, or slice through flesh and bone with effortless ease. Clad in heavy armour, their bodies are virtually invulnerable to damage, making them a common choice amongst many Undead factions as front-line field commanders.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='0' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='4' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="10"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="8" Only="Infantry"/>
					<Lance Points="12" Only="Mount"/>
					<Mount Name="Skeletal Steed" Points="15"/>
					<Barding Points="5" For="Skeletal Steed"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Skeletal Steed</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='2' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='4'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Hellsteed</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Nightmare</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='3'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Abyssal Terror</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='4' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='4' I='2' A='3' Ld='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeTarget/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Zombie Dragon</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='4' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='4' I='2' A='3' Ld='4' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Terror/>
					<Fly/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Pestilential Breath</Rule>
						<Rule>Cloud of Flies</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Zombie Horde</Name>
				<Points>4</Points>
				<Size>20+</Size>
				<Image>Zombies</Image>
				<Description><Description>Zombies are simple corpses raised by a Necromancer to be used against the enemy as simple infantry. The armaments of these unliving are extremely diverse, for any who have died on the field of battle are instantly amongst their ranks. Some might have been recently slain Imperial troopers with magnificent weapons and armour, while others may consist of simple peasants with rusted pitchforks and kitchen knives. Whatever their origins, these unliving are still used extensively by the Vampire Counts.</Description></Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='1' BS='0' S='2' T='2' W='1' I='1' A='1' Ld='2'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Shambling Horde</Rule>
						<Rule>The Newly Dead</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="4"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="8"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Skeleton Warriors</Name>
				<Points>8</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>SkeletonWarrior</Image>
				<Size>10-30</Size>
				<Description>Skeletons form the mainstay of the Vampire Counts armies, and unlike Zombies, have the ability to go head-to-head against other enemy infantry. These skeletons are warriors raised from times long ago, having been slain in combat and buried with both their weapons and armour still intact. Although these warriors bare rusted swords and rotting wooden shields, these Skeletons still have a flicker of light within their sockets that indicates their spirits still linger within them, whose souls still remain trapped within the material realm.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='2' BS='2' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='2' A='1' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Spear PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="8" Name="Champion"/>
						<Musician Points="4"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="8" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Crypt Ghouls</Name>
				<Points>8</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Crypt Ghouls, or simply just Ghouls, are malformed humans whom have devolved themselves into a primitive existence due to the horrible consumption of dead flesh. Unlike the Undead, these still living creatures do not engage their enemy head-on and would rather attack from the shadows where they could use their adept hunting instincts and their poisonous claws to great effect.</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='2' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<PoisonAttack/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Filth-encrusted claws</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="8" Name="Crypt Chast"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Dire Wolves</Name>
				<Points>8</Points>
				<Size>5-20</Size>
				<Image>DireWolfs</Image>
				<Description>Dire Wolves are the arisen corpses of Giants Wolves that were brought back to serve the will of a Necromancer. Like in their former life, these Dire Wolves serve as horrific pack animals that hunt the enemies of his master like the hounds of the living.</Description>
				<Profile M='9' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<NoSlotsOfCore/>
					<FastCavalry/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Slavering jaws</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Doom Wolf"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Bat Swarm</Name>
				<Points>35</Points>
				<Size>3-20</Size>
				<Image>BatSwarms</Image>
				<Profile M='1' WS='3' BS='0' S='2' T='2' W='4' I='1' A='4' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<NoSlotsOfCore/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
					<Original>Flying move is restricted to a maximum of 10"</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Teeth and claws</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Corpse Cart</Name>
				<Points>75</Points>
				<Profile M='4' WS='2' BS='0' S='2' T='4' W='3' I='1' A='2D6' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<NoSlotsOfCore/>
					<Regeneration/>
					<Original>Bound spell with power level 5, all friendly Undead unit within 6" have the Always Strike First until next Magic phase</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Grasping hands</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Balefire</Name>
						<Points>25</Points>
						<Dependency/>
						<Rule>For each Corpse Cart with Balefire within 24" enemy wizard suffer a -1 modifier to casting</Rule>
					</Option>
					<Option>
						<Name>Unholy Lodestone</Name>
						<Points>25</Points>
						<Dependency/>
						<Rule>If friendly unit within 6" is target by Invocation of Nehek, the unit gain an additional wound</Rule>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Grave Guard</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Wight Blade</Name>
						<KillingBlow/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Seneschal"/>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Black Knight</Name>
				<Points>24</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Skeletal Steed</Mount>
				<Image>BlackKnights</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='6' AS='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Wight Blade</Name>
						<KillingBlow/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Lance/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
					<Original>Insubstantial Steed</Original>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Skeletal Steed barding</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
						<PointsPerModel>4</PointsPerModel>
					</Option>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="16" Name="Hell Knight"/>
						<Musician Points="8"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="16" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Fell Bats</Name>
				<Points>20</Points>
				<Size>3-10</Size>
				<Profile M='1' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='3' A='2' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Teeth and claws</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Spirit Host</Name>
				<Points>65</Points>
				<Size>3-10</Size>
				<Profile M='6' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='4' I='1' A='4' Ld='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Ethereal/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Ethereal Blade</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Varghulf</Name>
				<Points>175</Points>
				<Profile M='8' WS='5' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='4' I='2' A='5' Ld='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<Undead/>
					<Regeneration/>
					<Hate/>
					<Vampire/>
					<Original>Bestial Fury</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Massive fangs and talons</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Cairn Wraiths</Name>
				<Points>50</Points>
				<Size>3-10</Size>
				<Profile M='6' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='2' A='3' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<Undead/>
					<Regeneration/>
					<Hate/>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<Ethereal/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="25" Name="Tomb Banshee"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Blood Knight</Name>
				<Points>55</Points>
				<Size>4-20</Size>
				<Mount>Nightmare</Mount>
				<Image>BloodKnights</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='5' BS='3' S='5' T='4' W='1' I='4' A='2' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Undead/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<Vampire/>
					<Original>Martial Honour</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="20" Name="Kastellan" Magic="Type: Hero, Points: 25"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="20" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 75"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Black Coach</Name>
				<Points>200</Points>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='5' T='6' W='4' I='2' A='3' Ld='5' AS='3' Ward='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<Undead/>
					<Vampire/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Evocation of Death</Rule>
						<Rule>Chariot</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>