<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Imprint>
			<Army>High Elves</Army>
			<Edition>6</Edition>
			<Released>2001</Released>
			<Authors>Jake Thornton and Space McQuirk</Authors>
			<Description>The High Elves, or the Asur, as they call themselves, are one of the most ancient and powerful mortal civilisations within the Warhammer World. Hailing from a mighty mist-shrouded island-continent located within the centre of the Great Ocean, the High Elves of Ulthuan are a proud and mighty nation of masterful warriors, peerless mages and lords of the sky and sea. They are an ancient race with powerful armies and even grander magic, building a grand and all-mighty civilisation who, alongside the Dwarfs, fought a long-forgotten, apocalyptic war which saw some of the greatest and most powerful mortal heroes battle against the great darkness that tried to consume the world many thousands of years ago. At the zenith of their power, the world was truly theirs for the taking</Description>
		</Imprint>
		<Styles>
			<Colors>
				<Front>155599</Front>
				<Back>0c3359</Back>
				<Grid>bbd1e6</Grid>
				<Tooltip>daecfd</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>8599ac, 54708a, 244769</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<Images>
				<Files>
					<Cover/>
					<Symbol/>
					<Illustration/>
				</Files>
				<Folders>
					<Units/>
				</Folders>
			</Images>
		</Styles>
		<Naming>
			<Internal>HighElves</Internal>
			<MagicItems>Vaul's Forge</MagicItems>
		</Naming>
		<Magic>
			<Name>High Magic Spells</Name>
			<Options>Any of eight Lore of Battle Magic</Options>
			<Magic>
				<Spell Name="Walk Between Worlds" Cast="4"/>
				<Spell Name="Curse of Arrow Attraction" Cast="6"/>
				<Spell Name="Fortune is Fickle" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Fury of Khaine" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Flame of the Phoenix" Cast="11"/>
				<Spell Name="Vaul's Unmaking" Cast="12"/>
			</Magic>
			<Enemy>Dark Elves, Dark Magic</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Nagaelythe the Chillwind" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Doombolt of Kharaidon" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Chroesh Word of Pain" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Anchan-Rogar the Soul Stealer" Cast="11"/>
				<Spell Name="Lamehk's Dominion" Cast="12"/>
				<Spell Name="Arnizipal's Black Horror" Cast="14"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<Local>
			<SpecialRules>
				<ThreeRanks>Fight in three ranks with spears</ThreeRanks>
				<BreatheFire/>
			</SpecialRules>
			<Options>
				<DragonArmour>
					AddToArmour: 5
					Rule: Immune to all breath and all Flaming attacks
				</DragonArmour>
				<SwapSpears>
					Name: Swap spear for bow
				</SwapSpears>
			</Options>
		</Local>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<CommonMagicItems>
				<SwordOfStriking Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfBattle Points="20"/>
				<SwordOfMight Points="15"/>
				<BitingBlade Points="10"/>
				<EnchantedShield Points="10"/>
				<TalismanOfProtection Points="10"/>
				<DispellScroll Points="25"/>
				<PowerStone Points="20"/>
				<StaffOfSorcery Points="40"/>
				<WarBanner Points="20"/>
			</CommonMagicItems>
			<Honours>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Pure of Heart</Name>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Honours/>
					<Description>This Honour MUST be given to exactly one high Elf character. It costs no points.\n\nThe character, and any unit he joins, is Immune to Panic. If the Pure of Heart character is killed, the High Elf player loses 100 Victory points from his total at the end of the battle. If the scenario does not use Victory points then the demise of the Pure of Heart character has no effect</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Lion Guard</Name>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<Honours/>
					<Description>The character comes equipped with a lion cloak. The character and any unit he leads is Stubborn. If you have a character with Lion Guard, then White Lions become a Special Choice for your army (but remain 0-1)</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Loremaster</Name>
					<WizardTo Val="1"/>
					<AddToCast Val="1"/>
					<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Honours/>
					<Description>The character is a Level 1 Wizard. Note that he may not cast spells if he is wearing armour (remember that barding for his steed will not affect his spell casting)</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Swordmaster</Name>
					<WizardTo Val="1"/>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
					<Dependencies>
						<Off>Great weapon</Off>
					</Dependencies>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Honours/>
					<Description>The character is equipped with a Great weapon and may not take a magic weapon. Instead of striking last in any turn he does not charge, the character will strike in initiative order. The character also has the killing blow special rule</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Seer</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Honours/>
					<Rule>May choose his spells instead of rolling for them</Rule>
					<Description>Mage only. May choose his spells instead of rolling for them</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Channeller</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Honours/>
					<Rule>May cast with a maximum of +1 more Power dice than normal</Rule>
					<Description>Mage only. May cast with a maximum of +1 more Power dice than normal. For example, a Level 3 Mage may use up to five Power dice in an attempt to cast a spell (instead of the usual four)</Description>
				</Arcane>
			</Honours>
			<MagicWeapons>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Blade of Leaping Gold</Name>
					<AddToAttacks Val="3"/>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Description>The blade confers +3 Attacks on the character wielding it</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Bow of the Seafarer</Name>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Rule>Resolve each bow hit like a single bolt from a Bolt Thrower</Rule>
					<Description>Treat the Bow of the Seafarer as a normal longbow with the following exception. Resolve a hit from this like a single bolt from a Bolt Thrower. Note that you may stand and shoot with the Bow of the Seafarer</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Sword of Hoeth</Name>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<AutoHit/>
					<Description>All hits wound automatically. Armour saves are modified by the Strength of the bearer</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Blade of Darting Steel</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<HitFirst/>
					<AddToHit Val="1"/>
					<Description>The wielder always strikes first, even if his opponent charged that turn. If both models have this ability, roll off to see who strikes first in each Close Combat phase. In addition, the wielder adds +1 to his rolls to hit</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Reaver bow</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>Longbow with Strength 5, multiple shot x3</Rule>
					<Description>Treat the Reaver Bow as a normal longbow with the following exceptions: the bearer may shoot three times at the same target in each ot his Shooting phases and any hits are resolved at Strength 5</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Blade of Sea Gold</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<NoArmour/>
					<Description>No armour saves may be taken against wounds caused by the Blade of Sea Gold</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Foe Bane</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>All hits on a target with 3 or more Wounds on its starting profile will always wound on a 2+</Rule>
					<Description>All hits on a target with 3 or more Wounds on its starting profile will always wound on a 2+. Armour saves are modified by the Strength of the bearer</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</MagicWeapons>
			<MagicArmours>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Protection</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					<Description>Counts as light armour (armour save 6+) which can be combined with other equipment normally. If the wearer fails his armour save he may make a 4+ Ward save</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Shield>
					<Name>Golden Shield</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<SubOpponentToHit Val="1"/>
					<Description>This shield confers a 6+ armour save which can be combined with other equipment normally. In addition, all attempts to hit the bearer in close combat suffer a penalty of -1</Description>
				</Shield>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Stars</Name>
					<Only>Infantry</Only>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Rule>After any unsaved wound model is instantly teleported 3D6" in a random direction</Rule>
					<Description>May only be worn by a model on foot. Counts as light armour (armour save 6+) which can be combined with other equipment normally. If the wearer suffers an unsaved wound then one of the gems will burst into brilliant white light as he is instantly teleported 3D6" in a random direction.\n\nNote that this means that he can only suffer 1 unsaved wound in a round of close combat as he will be teleported away before the second can strike him. However, if he was struck by a Killing Blow or a weapon that does multiple wounds per hit (such as a cannon ball) then he would still suffer the instant death or multiplied wounds as normal before teleporting away.\n\nIf the model is teleported into another model or impassable terrain then simply carry on moving it along in the same direction until it is 1" beyond. If the model teleports off the table then treat it as having pursued off</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Heroes</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Test Bet="Pass" Context="Round" Profile="Leadership"/>
					<Description>Counts as heavy armour (armour save 5+) which can be combined with other equipment normally. In order to allocate close combat attacks against the wearer, an opponent must first pass a Leadership test. Test each Close Combat phase. If the test is failed, the enemy may attack another model in base contact instead. Models who are Immune to Psychology are immune to this effect also</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Shadow Armour</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Scout/>
					<Description>Counts as heavy armour (armour save 5+) which can be combined with other equipment normally. In addition, if the wearer is an independent character on foot then he has the Scout special rule. He may choose to deploy either at the same rime as the other characters, or as a Scout (including setting up with a unit of Shadow Warriors)</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Helm of Fortune</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Reroll>ToArmour</Reroll>
					<Description>This helm confers a 6+ armour save which can be combined with other equipment normally. The wearer may re-roll failed armour saves</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Shield>
					<Name>Dragonscale Shield</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<AddToWard Val="6"/>
					<Description>This shield confers a 5+ armour save which can be combined with other equipment normally. Also gives the bearer a 6+ Ward save</Description>
				</Shield>
			</MagicArmours>
			<Talismans>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Vambraces of Defence</Name>
					<Points>55</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					<Reroll>ToArmour</Reroll>
					<Description>Gives the wearer a 4+ Ward save. In addition, the wearer may re-roll failed armour saves</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Golden Crown of Atrazar</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<FirstWoundDiscount/>
					<Description>Discount the first wound suffered. One use only</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Loremaster's Cloak</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>2+ Ward save against wounds caused by spells</Rule>
					<Description>Gives the wearer and the unit he is with a 2+ Ward save against wounds caused by spells. It has no effect against shooting or close combat attacks</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Talisman of Saphery</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>The magical weapons of enemy models will have no special effects whilst they are in base contact</Rule>
					<Description>The magical weapons of enemy models will have no special effects whilst they are in base contact with the bearer of the talisman. Treat the magic weapon as a normal one of its type, eg, a Sword of Battle would count as a hand weapon, Porko's Pigstikka would count as a spear, etc</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Sacred Incense</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>All shooting at the bearer or the unit he is with suffers a -1 to hit penalty</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Guardian Phoenix</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Description>Gives the wearer a 5+ Ward save</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Amulet of Fire</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<MagicResistance Val="1"/>
					<Rule>Cannot be harmed by Flaming Attacks</Rule>
					<Description>Gives the wearer Magic Resistance (1). In addition, the wearer cannot be harmed by fire-based attacks, eg, Skaven Watpfire Throwers, Dwarf Flame Cannons, or fire balls, etc</Description>
				</Additional>
			</Talismans>
			<ArcaneItems>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Book of Hoeth</Name>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<Rule>Irresistible Force on any successful casting roll which includes any double, except a Miscast</Rule>
					<Description>Any spell cast by the mage with this book will be cast with Irresistible Force on any successful casting roll which includes any double, except a Miscast</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Annulian Crystal</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>During the enemy's Magic phase, the Crystal allows the High Elf player to remove one dice from the opponent's pile of Power dice and add it to his own Dispel dice pile</Rule>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Starwood Staff</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>+1 to all casting attempts</Rule>
					<Description>Gives +1 to all casting attempts made by the wizard carrying it</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Sigil of Asuryan</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>Automatically dispels one enemy spell, in addition, roll a D6: on a 4+ the spell is destroyed and the casting Wizard cannot use it for the duration of the battle, one use only</Rule>
					<Description>Automatically dispels one enemy spell. In addition, roll a D6. On a 4+ the spell is destroyed and the casting Wizard cannot use it for the duration of the battle. One use only</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Staff of Solidity</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>Mage immune to the effects of his first Miscast</Rule>
					<Description>This staff makes the Mage immune to the effects of his first Miscast. Note that a miscast spell still fails regardless of the actual dice score rolled</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Jewel of the Dusk</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<AddToCast Val="1"/>
					<Description>The jewel gives the Mage +1 Power dice in each of his own Magic phases. Only he may use this dice</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Silver Wand</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Rule>One more spell than is normal for level</Rule>
					<Description>The wearer knows one more spell than is normal for his level</Description>
				</Arcane>
			</ArcaneItems>
			<EnchantedItems>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Null Stone</Name>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<Rule>No Wizard within 6" ot the hearer may cast any spells. No other magic item or rune item within 6" of the hearer will work</Rule>
					<Description>No Wizard within 6" ot the hearer may cast any spells. No other magic item or rune item within 6" of the hearer will work. Treat them as normal weapons, banners, etc, of the appropriate type. Note that this applies to all friendly wizards and magic items as well as enemy ones</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Healing Potion</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>May immediately restores all wounds lost at the start of any phase in either player's turn, one use only</Rule>
					<Description>The character or any character in base contact may drink this at the start of any phase in either player's turn. It immediately restores all wounds lost by the character during the battle so far. Obviously, if the character is dead at the start of the phase then he can't drink the potion. One use only</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Radiant Gem of Hoeth</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<WizardTo Val="1"/>
					<AddToCast Val="1"/>
					<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
					<Description>The wearer counts as a Level 1 High Elf Mage. However, the wearer may still cast spells whilst wearing armour. This has no effect on characters who are already Wizards</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Cloak of Beards</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>Dwarfs both Hate and Fear the wearer of the Cloak</Rule>
					<Rule>Eeach model in base contact with the wearer loses all the runes from one of their runic items</Rule>
					<Description>Dwarfs both Hate and Fear the wearer of the Cloak. In addition, for the duration of each Close Combat phase, each model in base contact with the wearer loses all the runes from one of their runic items (determined randomly). Treat the item as a normal one of its kind</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Ring of Corin</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, Power level 4, one use only: Vaul's Unmaking spell</Rule>
					<Description>Bound spell (Power level 4). One use only. The Ring of Corin may cast its Bound spell in the Magic phase like an ordinary spell. The spell requires no Power dice to cast, all the power required is provided by the ring itself. The Ring of Corin contains the Vaul's Unmaking spell</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Ring of Fury</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, Power level 3, contains the Fury of Khaine spell</Rule>
					<Description>Bound spell (Power level 3). This ring may cast its Bound Spell once per Magic phase like an ordinary spell. The spell requires no Power dice to cast, all the power required is provided by the ring itself. The Ring of Fury contains the Fury of Khaine spell. After each use, even if it was dispelled, roll a D6. On a roll of a 1 the power of the Ring has been exhausted and it may not be used for the rest of the battle</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Blessed tome</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>All High Elf units within 6" get +1 Leadership</Rule>
					<Description>The character with the tome recites the stirring words of heroes of old as battle is joined. All High Elf units within 6" of the bearer get +1 Leadership (up to a maximum of 10)</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Amulet of the Purifying Flame</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>Spells that target the character or the unit he is with subtract -3 from their casting roll</Rule>
					<Description>Spells that target the character or the unit he is with subtract -3 from their casting roll. It has no effect on spells cast with Irresistible Force</Description>
				</Additional>
			</EnchantedItems>
			<MagicBanner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Battle Banner</Name>
					<Points>80</Points>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="D6"/>
					<Description>The unit may add +D6 to the combat resolution of any close combat in which it is involved</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of the World Dragon</Name>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Rule>The unit is completely immune to all spell effects, whatever their source</Rule>
					<Description>The unit is completely immune to all spell effects, whatever their source. This includes friendly spells, bound items, and spells with areas of effect that were cast on nearby units, etc. Spells which are cast on another unit, such as the Flaming Sword of Rhuin, will work as normal, as will all magic weapons used to attack them</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of Sorcery</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>+D3 Power dice to pile in each Magic phases</Rule>
					<Description>The banner adds +D3 Power dice to pile in each of your own Magic phases</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Standard of Balance</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Description>The unit carrying the Standard of Balance, and any enemy unit in base contact with it, is completely immune to all Psychology. Note that troops with frenzy lose it, just as if they had lost a round of combat</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of Arcane Protection</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<MagicResistance Val="2"/>
					<Rule>Any Undead or Daemon model touching the unit will suffer 1 Wound (saves as normal) at the start of each of the bearer's Magic phases</Rule>
					<Description>The unit gets Magic Resistance (2). In addition, any Undead or Daemon model touching the unit carrying the banner will suffer 1 Wound (saves as normal) at the start of each of the bearer's Magic phases. Note that this does not count as a close combat attack</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Lion Standard</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Immune to fear and terror</Rule>
					<Description>The unit is immune to fear and terror</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of Ellyrion</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>The unit treats difficult ground as open ground for purposes of movement</Rule>
				</Banner>
			</MagicBanner>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Imrik</Name>
				<Points>675</Points>
				<Mount>Minaithnir</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Prince Imrik, Crown Prince of Caledor and Lord of Dragons is the last descendant of the first archmage Caledor Dragontamer. He is amongst the few who can rouse the slumbering drakes in times of strife, and is acclaimed as the greatest warrior upon Ulthuan, save for Prince Tyrion. Though he knows it not, his bloodline's fate is intertwined with the elven species. If Imrik should die, his entire race will follow soon after.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='8' BS='6' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='9' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero, Hero</Slots>
					<Original>No Dragons will fight Imrik, if they are in base contact with other models (and not in a challenge) then they light them instead, otherwise they may do nothing</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Star Lance</Name>
						<ChargeStrengthBonus Val="3"/>
						<Rule>On the turn he charges, Imrik gets +3 Strength with no armour saves allowed</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Armour of Caledor</Name>
						<ArmourTo Val="2"/>
						<Rule>Immune to all breath and all Flaming attacks</Rule>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Dragonhorn</Name>
						<Rule>Once per battle, at the start of any of his own turns, Imrik may sound the Dragonhorn: until the start of his next turn, all friendly High Elf units may re-roll any Leadership-based tests</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Tyrion</Name>
				<Points>585</Points>
				<Mount>Malhandir</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Prince Tyrion, Heir of Aenarion, Champion of the Everqueen, and Defender of Ulthuan is the greatest living High Elven warrior of this age. So valiant and skilled is he that the bards of Ulthuan sing that he is nothing less then Aenarion reborn — a tale that is given credence far beyond Ulthuan's shores. Since Tyrion's meteoric rise to fame, many have whispered of his destiny to lead the High Elves towards a glorious future, and perhaps one day to take the Phoenix Crown. If Tyrion hears such gossip, he pays it no heed, for he is unswervingly loyal to Finubar. Thus does Tyrion concern himself only with the twin duties of protecting Ulthuan and its Everqueen, the beloved Alarielle.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='9' BS='7' S='4' T='3' W='4' I='10' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<General/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Parries the first enemy hit against him per Close Combat phase and it has no effect</Rule>
						<Rule>May re-roll any failed rolls to hit on the first turn of each close combat</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Sunfang</Name>
						<AddToStrength Val="3"/>
						<Rule>Once per battle in his own Magic phase, Tyrion may use Sunfang to cast the bound spell Fury of Khaine (power level 6), the spell requires no Power dice to cast, all the power required is provided by Sunfang itself</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Dragon Armour of Aenarion</Name>
						<Rule>Immune to all breath and all Flaming attacks</Rule>
						<ArmourTo Val="1"/>
						<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Heart of Avelorn</Name>
						<Rule>If Tyrion is slain, Heart of Avelorn returns Tyrion to life with 1 Wound, obviously it will only work once</Rule>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Curse of Aenarion</Name>
						<WardForLastWound Val="2"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Teclis</Name>
				<Points>630</Points>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Prince Teclis, High Loremaster of Hoeth and Warden of the White Tower, is considered by many to be one of the greatest and most powerful spellcasters the world has ever known. Teclis is the twin brother of Tyrion, the famous Elven Hero, and the widely-proclaimed Defender of Ulthuan. Being of the line of Aenarion, each of his descendants are destined for greatness amongst the Ten Kingdoms. This has made Tyrion a masterful warrior and general, and in turn, this greatness makes Teclis one of the most powerful living mages in the world.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='2' T='2' W='3' I='5' A='1' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Any spell cast by Teclis will be cast with Irresistible Force on any successful casting roll which includes a double, except a Miscast</Rule>
						<Rule>Use High Magic know all six spells, regardless ot his current level</Rule>
						<Rule>May re-roll all dice for spell effects</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Sword of Teclis</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<WoundOn Val="2"/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Curse of Aenarion</Name>
						<WardForLastWound Val="2"/>
					</Armour>
					<Arcane>
						<Name>Potions of Inner Strength</Name>
						<WeaponSkillTo Val="6"/>
						<BallisticSkillTo Val="4"/>
						<StrengthTo Val="3"/>
						<InitiativeTo Val="6"/>
						<AttacksTo Val="3"/>
					</Arcane>
					<Arcane>
						<Name>The Moon Staff of Lileath</Name>
						<AddToCast Val="1"/>
						<Rule>Once per battle, Moon Staff may granted D6 extra dice to cast, but no more additional dice for the rest of the battle</Rule>
					</Arcane>
					<Arcane>
						<Name>Scroll of Hoeth</Name>
						<Rule>One use only, same as Dispel scroll, in addition, both Teclis and the caster roll a D6: if Teclis scores higher, the spell cannot be reused by caster</Rule>
					</Arcane>
					<Arcane>
						<Name>The War Crown</Name>
						<Rule>Any spell which is normally limited to a specific range in inches is now of unlimited range</Rule>
					</Arcane>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Prince</Name>
				<Points>125</Points>
				<Description>The High Elven Princes of Ulthuan are the greatest and most skillful generals, strategist and warriors this world will ever see. Depending on their wealth and the kingdom of their birth, the princes of Ulthuan fight in many different ways. Those of Tiranoc typically do battle from the back of swift-wheeled chariots, while the lords of Lothern often stand, spear and bow in hand, amidst the ranks of the Sea Guard. Those with the greatest wealth might ride upon a Great Eagle or Griffon or, in the case of the mightiest princes of Caledor, upon a Dragon. Such steeds are invariably a symbol of status, as well as lending a brutal advantage in the midst of battle.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='7' BS='6' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='8' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Lance Points="6" Only="Mount"/>
					<Spear Points="6"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6"/>
					<Halberd Points="6"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="6" Only="Infantry"/>
					<Longbow Points="10"/>
					<LightArmour Points="3" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="6" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<DragonArmour Points="8" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="18"/>
					<Mount Name="Barded Elven Steed" Points="24"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Eagle" Points="50"/>
					<Mount Name="Griffon" Points="200"/>
					<Mount Name="Dragon" Points="320"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Archmage</Name>
				<Points>220</Points>
				<Wizard>3</Wizard>
				<Description>High Elf Mages are aspirants to the Magical arts, but due to their natural affinity to the Winds of Magic, they are far more powerful then even the most experience Imperial Battle Wizard. By lineage and inclination, the Elves are a magical race. They are fascinated by the secrets of sorcery, and their mages' nimble minds can embrace a deeper understanding of its subtleties and whims than other wizards. It is well that this is so, for without the magics of the High Elf Mages, Ulthuan would have long since have slipped beneath the waves or been overwhelmed by the black sorceries of Naggarothi sorcerers.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='3' I='5' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Wizard"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="4" Points="35"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="18"/>
					<Mount Name="Barded Elven Steed" Points="26"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Eagle" Points="50"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Commander</Name>
				<Points>70</Points>
				<Description>High Elf Nobles are the leaders of their own respected armies and companies, warriors whose skill at arms and years of experience far surpass those of any other mortal race. The noble families of Ulthuan have led the High Elves through times of peace and conflict for thousands of years. They pride themselves on a deep sense of honour, as well as the mastery of both diplomacy and war as art forms.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='6' S='4' T='3' W='2' I='7' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Lance Points="4" Only="Mount"/>
					<Spear Points="4"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4"/>
					<Halberd Points="4"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="4" Only="Infantry"/>
					<Longbow Points="10"/>
					<LightArmour Points="2" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<DragonArmour Points="6" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="12"/>
					<Mount Name="Barded Elven Steed" Points="5"/>
					<Mount Name="Great Eagle" Points="50"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Mage</Name>
				<Points>95</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Description>High Elf Mages are aspirants to the Magical arts, but due to their natural affinity to the Winds of Magic, they are far more powerful then even the most experience Imperial Battle Wizard. By lineage and inclination, the Elves are a magical race. They are fascinated by the secrets of sorcery, and their mages' nimble minds can embrace a deeper understanding of its subtleties and whims than other wizards.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Wizard"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="2" Points="35"/>
					<Mount Name="Elven Steed" Points="12"/>
					<Mount Name="Barded Elven Steed" Points="17"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Elven Steed</Name>
				<Profile M='9' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Barded Elven Steed</Name>
				<Profile M='9' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5' AS='6'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Malhandir</Name>
				<Profile M='10' WS='4' BS='0' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='5' A='2' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Great Eagle</Name>
				<Profile M='2' WS='5' BS='0' S='5' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Griffon</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='5' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='4' I='5' A='4' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
					<LargeTarget/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Dragon</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='0' S='6' T='6' W='6' I='3' A='5' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Fly/>
					<BreatheFire/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Scaly skin</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="3"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Minaithnir</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='7' BS='0' S='6' T='6' W='7' I='3' A='5' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Fly/>
					<BreatheFire/>
					<Original>If Imrik is slain, will become subject to the rules for frenzy, but will otherwise remain under the control of the High Elf player</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Scaly skin</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="3"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Archers</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>High Elf Archers are disciplined, keen-eyed citizen-militia that serves the armies of Ulthuan as part of their civic duties to protect their kingdom against all threats. As a result of Phoenix King Morvael's introduction of the levy system, over a thousand years ago the majority of Ulthuan's armies are composed of citizen militia. This system made it so all Elves receive military training, whether it be a craftsman, tradesman or artist, they all must fight in defense of Ulthuan in times of war.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Longbow/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<LightArmour PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Champion"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Spearman</Name>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>High Elf Spearmen are the elite, second-tier citizen-militia within Ulthuan's armies, acting as a disciplined line of warriors that puts even the most battle-hardened Human warrior to shame. It is only after a decade or more of fighting as an Archer and once his worth is proven, does a high Elf then becomes a spearmen. After years of training a regiment of High Elf Spears becomes a finely honed killing machine.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ThreeRanks/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Spear/>
					<LightArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Champion"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Lothern Sea Guard</Name>
				<Points>15</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Image>SeaGuard</Image>
				<Description>The Lothern Sea Guard are the specialised citizen-militia of the Kingdom of Eataine, fighting as effectively on land as at sea, and are equally resolute when defending the walls and fields of Lothern as they are when battling on the deck of a ship. These dangerous duties require the Sea Guard to maintain a flexible armoury. The vast majority are well-trained in the use of spear, shield and bow — the better to combine the finest aspects of the spear and archer regiments of other cities and realms. Indeed, it is a point of pride in Lothern that the discipline of their warriors far surpasses that of any found elsewhere in Ulthuan.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ThreeRanks/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Spear/>
					<Bow/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14"/>
						<Champion Points="14" Name="Champion"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Silver Helms</Name>
				<Points>19</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Barded Elven Steed</Mount>
				<Description>The Silver Helms are seen as the perfect exemplars of mounted martial grace and valor to which young Elves should aspire. Dragon Princes are too distant and aloof, Ellyrian Reavers perhaps a touch too wild and uncivilized; Silver Helms are proud without being haughty, and brave without being undisciplined. Thus, Ulthuan's legends more often center around the deeds of its Silver Helms than any other warriors within the ten realms.</Description>
				<Profile M='9' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8' AS='5'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<LightNativeArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<HeavyArmour PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14"/>
						<Champion Points="14" Name="Champion"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Ellyrian Reavers</Name>
				<Points>18</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Elven Steed</Mount>
				<Description>The Ellyrian Reavers, or Reaver Knights, are a famous formation of elite Ellyrian horsemen who are famous for their abilities as swift and agile horse archers. In the time of Caledor I, all Ulthuan was in turmoil and the armies of Malekith roamed freely, destroying and slaying at will. With his armies already stretched to the limit, the Phoenix King called for brave young horsemen to ride the troubled land.</Description>
				<Profile M='9' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8' AS='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<FastCavalry/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Spear/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Bow PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Range"/>
					<SwapSpears PointsPerModel="2" Dependency="Range"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="7" Name="Harbinger"/>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Dragon Princes of Caledor</Name>
				<Points>26</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Mount>Barded Elven Steed</Mount>
				<Image>DragonPrinces</Image>
				<Description>The Dragon Princes of Caledor are amongst the greatest and most noble Knights the world has ever known. Long ago, Ulthuan was dominated by the valorous deeds and wise rule of Caledor's Dragon Princes. Now, the royal bloodline has faded, and the power of the Dragons has diminished, but Caledor's pride still shines bright. The princes of Caledor once rode Dragons, but today they ride to war upon swift horses. Both mount and rider wear crested ithilmar armour whose style echoes that of the heart of Vaul's Anvil, where ancient enchantments are bound into the cooling ithilmar, ensuring that no lesser flame than the fires of Vaul can offer harm to the armour or its wearer.</Description>
				<Profile M='9' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='6' A='1' Ld='9' AS='5'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<DragonArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="9"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="18" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="18" Name="Drakemaster" Magic="Type: Hero, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Swordmasters of Hoeth</Name>
				<Points>13</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Image>Swordmasters</Image>
				<Description>The Swordmasters of Hoeth are exemplars of the martial arts. Each has studied warfare and personal combat for decades, or even centuries. It is even said that highest masters of the order can slay a foe with but a touch, or kill with a single precisely-pitched whistle. When Ulthuan marches to war, none go more eagerly than the Swordmasters of Hoeth, for only in war can they truly unleash the full extent of their deadly art. As the Swordmasters advance, their blades blur and weave, knocking aside arrows in mid-flight and leaving trails of bloody spray wherever Hoeth-forged steel tastes flesh.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>Swordmasters</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Bladelord" Magic="Type: Hero, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Shadow Warriors</Name>
				<Points>15</Points>
				<Size>5-15</Size>
				<Description>The Shadow Warriors are an elite band of scouts, warriors and assassins, who are the descendants of loyalist Elves from the Kingdom of Nagarythe during the time of the great Sundering. The Shadow Warriors are masters of ambush and guerrilla warfare, elite warriors even among other Elves. They strike swiftly and noiselessly from concealment with deadly accurate volleys from their longbows, before charging forth to slay any survivors with a flurry of blades. At some point, every race has felt the wrath of the Shadow Warrior, for they go before the armies of the Asur wherever they fight, slaughtering the enemy's scouts and clearing a path for the main force.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<Scouts/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Hate Dark Elves</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Longbow/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="14" Name="Shadow-walker"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Tiranoc Chariot</Name>
				<Points>85</Points>
				<Chariot>2</Chariot>
				<Mount>Barded Elven Steed</Mount>
				<Description>The Tiranoc Charioteers fight with incredible skill, deft reactions complementing the speed of their straining Elven steeds. Thus do they find passage where lesser mortals could not hope to do so: they weave between enemy units at full speed, raining arrows onto unprotected flanks and raking enemy lines with steel-tipped spears. Only when the enemy is sufficiently weakened do the Tiranoc Charioteers crash into the press of melee in a glorious massed charged, the steeds biting and kicking, the riders thrusting their spears into the black hearts of their foes.</Description>
				<Profile M='9' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='4' W='4' I='5' A='2' Ld='8' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<ImpactHit Val="D6"/>
					<Original>Chariot</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Spear/>
					<Bow/>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Phoenix Guard</Name>
				<Points>15</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Description>The Phoenix Guard are the guardians of the Shrine of Asuryan, the great pyramid temple in the Sea of Dreams. Deep within lies the Chamber of Days. On its ancient walls, it is said, are the histories of past, present and future, etched in words of fire. Legend tells that any who behold the wall shall forever be cursed with knowledge of their own death. The Phoenix Guard do not utter a word. It is forbidden for those who have seen the secrets of time to speak of them, and all who do so take a magical vow of silence from which they can never be released.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='6' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Halberd/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Keeper of the Flame" Magic="Type: Hero, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Repeater Bolt Thrower</Name>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<Description>The Eagle Claw Bolt Thrower, or the Repeater Bolt Throwers are elegant repeating ballistas used extensively by the armies of the High Elves and their sea-faring fleets.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='7' W='3' I='5' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>Repeater Bolt Thrower</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>White Lions</Name>
				<Points>13</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Description>The White Lions have served as the personal guard of the Phoenix King since the time of Caledor the First. Whilst hunting in Chrace, Caledor received news that he was to be next Phoenix King. He immediately took the road to the Shrine of Asuryan, but was intercepted by Dark Elf Assassins. He would surely have died, but for the intervention of a party of Chracian woodsmen who swept out of the forest to defend him. The Chracians slew the Dark Elves and, thereafter, saw Caledor safely to the Phoenix Shrine, employing every iota of their woodcraft to avoid further Dark Elf ambushes that lay in their path. Caledor's first act, once crowned as Phoenix King, was to form the Chracians into an official bodyguard based in Lothern.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Original>Woodsmen</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Great axes</Name>
						<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
					<Additional>
						<Name>Lion cloak</Name>
					</Additional>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="14" Name="Guardian" Magic="Type: Hero, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Great Eagle</Name>
				<Points>50</Points>
				<Description>Great Eagles are the largest birds of prey in the Empire, with a wingspan that measures over thirty feet and having razor-sharp talons. They are an ancient race that has dwelled in the mountains of the Old World since long before the coming of Man. Most of them nest in the Grey Mountains, though a few live along the Worlds Edge Mountains. They are exceedingly intelligent and a few of their eldest are even rumoured to be capable of speaking in the tongues of other races, though they seem to prefer most often to deal with Elves.</Description>
				<Profile M='2' WS='5' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>