<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Info>
			<Army>Bretonnia</Army>
			<Edition>6</Edition>
			<Released>2003</Released>
			<Authors>Anthony Reynolds</Authors>
			<Description>The Kingdom of Bretonnia, also known as the Land of Chivalry, is a highly martial feudal kingdom that lies between the lands of the Grey Mountains and the Great Ocean. Bretonnia is second only in size to that of the Empire, both their chief rival and closest ally, having a culture and society that revolves around the ideals of nobility, social birthright, and the upholding of a strictly enforced code of chivalry.\n\nRuled by a Royarch, the nation of Bretonnia has been known throughout the kingdoms of man for having the greatest Knights in the entire Old World, even surpassing that of the Knightly Orders of the Empire. A proud and honourable kingdom, the armies of Bretonnia are comprised mostly of knights and noblemen, who ride into battle with lance, horse, and sword, seeking glory and rooting out injustice wherever they go. The Knights of Bretonnia are trained to fight from childhood, and even the lowliest Knights Errant are considered superior to ordinary warriors. Their skills are further enhanced through constant training, battles and tournaments. It is not only Bretonnia's knights who are famed, however, for the kingdom also boasts the finest human sailors in the World. With their great sails billowing in the wind, Bretonnia's mighty fleets are a majestic sight on the high seas. Due to this regime, the combined military might of Bretonnia has surpassed that of even the greatest armies in history</Description>
		</Info>
		<Styles>
			<Images>
				<Cover>Bretonnia6ed.png</Cover>
				<Symbol>Bretonnia.png</Symbol>
				<Illustration>Bretonnia6ed.jpg</Illustration>
				<Units>6edition</Units>
			</Images>
			<Colors>
				<Front>000080</Front>
				<Back>a11806</Back>
				<Grid>f6d3cf</Grid>
				<Tooltip>b0bae2</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>c67469, b34637, aa2f1e</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<MagicItems>Blessed Heirlooms</MagicItems>
		</Styles>
		<Internal>Bretonnia</Internal>
		<Magic>
			<Name>The Lore of Light</Name>
			<Options>Lore of Beasts, Life, Heavens</Options>
			<Magic>
				<Spell Name="Pha's Illumination" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Burning Gaze" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Dazzling Brightness" Cast="6"/>
				<Spell Name="Healing Hand" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Guardian Light" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Blinding Light" Cast="9"/>
			</Magic>
			<Enemy>Vampire Counts, The Black Art</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Invocation of Nehek" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Hand of Dust" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Hellish Vigour" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Gaze of Nagash" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Vanhel's Danse Macabre" Cast="11"/>
				<Spell Name="Curse of Years" Cast="12"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<LocalSpecialRules>
			<LeadershipOfKnight>May use the Leadership of any non-fleeing Knight within 6" of them; unit Standards do not confer any additional Victory Points if they are captured</LeadershipOfKnight>
		</LocalSpecialRules>
		<LocalOption>
			<QuestingVow Name="Questing Vow">
				Group: QuestingVow;
				HitLast;
				AddToStrength: 2;
				Rule: May re-roll any failed Psychology tests
			</QuestingVow>
			<GrailVow Name="Grail Vow">
				Group: GrailVow;
				ImmuneToPsychology;
				AddToWard: 6;
				Rule: 5+ Ward save versus attacks with Strength 5 or higher
			</GrailVow>
			<MorningStar Name="Morning star">
				Flail
			</MorningStar>
			<Barding Name="Barding for Warhorse">
				AddToArmour: 6
			</Barding>
			<Braziers/>
		</LocalOption>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<Group Name="Virtues of the Chivalric Knight">
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of the Penitent</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Description>The Knight is Stubborn, though he may never join any friendly units. He may not take any magic items, nor may he ride a Hippogryph or a Royal Pegasus</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Knightly Temper</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>For each attack that the Knight hits and wounds with on the charge (before Saves etc,), he may make an additional attack</Rule>
					<Description>For each attack that the Knight hits and wounds with on the charge (before Saves etc,), he may make an additional attack. For example, if a Paladin hits and wounds with two attacks he can make two additional attacks immediately. Extra attacks are not generated if these additional attacks also hit and wound. A character with this Virtue may not use magic weapons</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Heroism</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<HeroicKillingBlow/>
					<Description>Against Large Targets, and if armed with a non-magical weapon, the Knight has the Killing Blow special ability. This overrides the normal limitation of Killing Blow only affecting man-sized models</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Stoicism</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>May re-roll failed Break tests</Rule>
					<Description>The Knight (and any unit he has joined) may re-roll failed Break tests</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of the Ideal</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<NotALeader/>
					<AddToWeaponSkill Val="2"/>
					<AddToInitiative Val="1"/>
					<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
					<Description>The Knight gains the following bonuses to his profile: +2 Weapon Skill, +1 Initiative, +1 Attack. He may not be the army's General (even if he has the highest Leadership) and any friendly unit (including other Knightly characters, or units using a Knight's Leadership) taking any form of Leadership test within 6" of this model suffers a -1 penalty to their Leadership</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of the Impetuous Knight</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>+D6" for the first charge</Rule>
					<Description>The Knight, and any mounted unit he is with, adds +D6" for the first charge that they declare (roll after declaring the charge). If the charge is failed the unit will not add this extra D6" to their failed charge movement</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Audacity</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>May re-roll any failed rolls to hit and to wound against enemies with a higher Strength than himself (before modifications from weapons etc)</Rule>
					<Description>Against enemies with a higher Strength than himself (before modifications from weapons etc), the Knight may re-roll any failed rolls to hit and to wound</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Duty</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<NotALeader/>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="1"/>
					<Description>One per army. May not be taken by the General. For as long as the General is alive, the model with this Virtue adds +1 to the combat resolution of any fight of which he is a part</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of the Joust</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>May re-roll failed rolls to hit when charging and using a lance</Rule>
					<Description>The Knight may re-roll failed rolls to hit when charging and using a lance (including magical lances)</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Confidence</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Reroll>ToHit;ToWound</Reroll>
					<Description>The Knight must always issue challenges, and will always accept them if possible. In challenges, the Knight may re-roll all failed rolls to hit and to wound</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Noble Disdain</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Hate/>
					<Description>The Knight hates all enemies using missile weapons including war machine crews. In addition, any unit the Knight has joined never takes Panic tests caused by suffering 25% casualties (eg, shooting, magic, etc)</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Purity</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Description>The Knight will always start the game with the Blessing of the Lady, even if the army did not pray. In addition, the Ward save which the Knight gains from the Blessing is always 5+, regardless of the Strength of the attack</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Discipline</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>The enemy never gets a +1 combat resolution bonus for outnumbering in any combat that the character is involved in</Rule>
					<Description>The enemy never gets a +1 combat resolution bonus for outnumbering in any combat that the character is involved in. Note, however, that he and any unit he has joined will still flee automatically if beaten by a fear-causing enemy that outnumbers them, as per the normal rules</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Virtue of Empathy</Name>
					<Virtue/>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Rule>Peasant units within 12" of him may use his Leadership</Rule>
					<Description>The Knight may be fielded on foot. In addition, if he is not the army's General, Peasant units within 12" of him may use his Leadership, rather than the normal distance of 6"</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Common magic items">
				<SwordOfStriking Points="30"/>
				<SwordOfBattle Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfMight Points="20"/>
				<BitingBlade Points="10"/>
				<EnchantedShield Points="10"/>
				<TalismanOfProtection Points="15"/>
				<StaffOfSorcery Points="50"/>
				<DispellScroll Points="25"/>
				<PowerStone Points="25"/>
				<WarBanner Points="25"/>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Magic Weapons">
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Silver Lance of the Blessed</Name>
					<Points>65</Points>
					<Only>Mount</Only>
					<Lance/>
					<Rule>If the model has the Blessing of the Lady, then all attacks with the Silver Lance Of the Blessed automatically hit</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer has +2 Strength on the charge when mounted. If the model has the Blessing of the Lady, then all attacks with the Silver Lance Of the Blessed automatically hit</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Sword of the Quest</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<OnlyGroup>QuestingVow</OnlyGroup>
					<NoArmour/>
					<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
					<HitLast/>
					<Rule>May be used a hand weapon or a great weapon, decided at the start of combat as normal</Rule>
					<Description>May be used as either a hand weapon or a great weapon, decided at the start of combat as normal. No Armour saves may be taken against the Sword of the Quest</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Sword of the Lady's Champion</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Only>GrailVow</Only>
					<NoArmour/>
					<WoundOn Val="3"/>
					<Description>The character always counts their Strength as one higher than their target's Toughness, unless their Strength would normally be more than this. In effect this means that they will always wound opponents on at least a 3+. This modified Strength is also used to calculate Armour save modifiers</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Sword of Heroes</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>+1 Strength and D3 wounds against enemies that have Toughness 5 or greater</Rule>
					<Description>Against enemies that have Toughness 5 or greater, the bearer gets +1 Strength and each unsaved wound caused by the Sword of Heroes becomes D3 wounds rather than 1</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Heartwood Lance</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Only>Mount</Only>
					<Lance/>
					<Reroll>ToWound</Reroll>
					<Description>The bearer has +2 Strength on the charge when mounted. The Heartwood Lance allows the bearer to re-roll all failed rolls to wound</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Birth-sword of Carcassonne</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
					<Reroll>OpponentToArmour</Reroll>
					<Description>The sword acids +1 Strength to the bearer. Enemies wounded by the sword must re-roll any successful Armour saves</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Morning Star of Fracasse</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Flail/>
					<Rule>For each hit on a close combat opponent, roll a D6. On a 4+, if the opponent has a magic weapon, it is destroyed</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer has +2 Strength in the first round of combat. For each hit on a close combat opponent, roll a D6. On a 4+, if the opponent has a magic weapon, it is destroyed</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Lance of Artois</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Mount</Only>
					<Lance/>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<Description>The bearer has +2 Strength on the charge when mounted. In addition, the lance confers the Killing Blow special rule onto the bearer, but only on turns during which the character charges</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Wyrmlance</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Only>Mount</Only>
					<Lance/>
					<Rule>Flaming attacks</Rule>
					<Rule>Once per game, may make a breath attack from the tip of the lance at Strength 3 provided he is not in close combat</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer has +2 Strength on the charge when mounted. In addition, once per game, the model wielding the Wyrmlance may make a breath attack from the tip of the lance at Strength 3 provided he is not in close combat. Furthermore, all attacks made by the Wyrmlance count as flaming attacks</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Magic Armour">
				<Armour>
					<Name>Gilded Cuirass</Name>
					<Points>55</Points>
					<Only>GrailVow</Only>
					<Regeneration/>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Description>Character with the Grail Vow only. This armour replaces the Knight's heavy armour, and gives a 5+ Armour save that can be combined with other equipment as normal. In addition, the wearer has Regeneration</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of the Midsummer Sun</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<Rule>Opponents suffer a -1 penalty to all rolls to hit the wearer and his mount with missile weapons and in close combat</Rule>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Description>This armour replaces the Knight's heavy armour, and gives a 5+ Armour save that may be combined with other armour as normal. Opponents suffer a -1 penalty to all rolls to hit the wearer and his mount with missile weapons and in close combat</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Shield>
					<Name>The Grail Shield</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Only>GrailVow</Only>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					<Description>The shield provides a 6+ Armour save which may be combined with other armour as normal. The bearer's Ward save gained from the Blessing of the Lady is increased to 4+ against attacks of any Strength. If the model loses the Blessing, they lose this Ward save as normal</Description>
				</Shield>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Gromril Great Helm</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Reroll>ToArmour</Reroll>
					<Description>Gives a 6+ Armour save and may be worn in addition to normal armour. The wearer may re-roll failed Armour saves</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Agilulf</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="4"/>
					<WeaponSkillTo Val="10"/>
					<Description>This armour replaces the Knight's heavy armour and includes a shield, giving a 4+ Armour save. The shield must be used at all times - so the wearer cannot use a weapon that requires two hands. In addition, the armour confers Weapon Skill 10 (which cannot be altered with other items. Virtues, etc) to whoever is wearing it</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Cuirass of Fortune</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Reroll>ToWound</Reroll>
					<Description>This armour replaces the Knight's heavy armour, and gives a 5+ Annour save which may be combined with other armour as normal. When rolling to wound in close combat, the Knight may re-roll any dice rolls of 1</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Shield>
					<Name>Orcbane Shield</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Rule>Any unengaged Ore or Goblin unit within 12" that must take an Animosity test fails it on a 1-2 instead of a 1</Rule>
					<Description>Gives a 6+ Armour save and may be combined with other armour as normal. Any unengaged Ore or Goblin unit within 12" that must take an Animosity test fails it on a 1-2 instead of a 1</Description>
				</Shield>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Talismans">
				<Additional>
					<Name>Sirienne's Locket</Name>
					<Points>55</Points>
					<NoMultiWounds/>
					<Description>A Knight with Sirienne's Locket can never suffer more than one-wound in any one phase from non-magical attacks - even multiple wound weapons (including war machines) can only cause a single wound. After the first wound in that phase is suffered, all subsequent wounds suffered during that phase are ignored. The bearer can still be run down by pursuing enemies as normal, and may still be affected as normal by Killing Blow</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Token of the Damsel</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<WardForFirstWound Val="2"/>
					<Description>Against the first wounding hit suffered, the Knight gains a 2+ Ward save</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Insignia of the Quest</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Only>QuestingVow</Only>
					<WardForLastWound Val="3"/>
					<Description>If the hearer is ever reduced to 1 Wound, then the Knight instantly gains a 3+ Ward save. If the character suffers multiple wounds that would kill him hefore he has gained this Ward save (eg, if he has more than one wound left and is hit by a cannon ball), he will be reduced to 1 Wound, then may attempt his 3+ Ward save to stay alive and nullify any further wounds caused by the same hit</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Braid of Bordeleaux</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>One use only: until the beginning of the next Bretonnian turn, the character's Leadership value is increased by 1</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. The Braid may be used at the start of any Bretonnian turn. Until the beginning of the next Bretonnian turn, the character's Leadership value is increased by 1. In addition, once the Braid has been used, until the start of the next Bretonnian turn, the model bearing the Braid and any unit he is with can move over marsh, rivers, lakes or any other water features without penalty and will benefit from soft cover while in such terrain</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Dragon's Claw</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Description>The bearer's Ward save gained from the Blessing of the Lady is increased to 5+ against attacks of any Strength. If the model loses the Blessing, then it loses this Ward save as normal. In addition, as long as the bearer has the Blessing, he is immune to lire based attacks (such as Dragon's breath. Warp-fire Throwers and spells from the Lore of Fire)</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Mantle of Damsel Elena</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<NoKillingBlow/>
					<ImmuneToPoison/>
					<Description>Poisoned attacks do not wound automatically against a character with the Mantle. In addition, the special rules for Killing Blow-have no effect on the character</Description>
				</Additional>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Enchanted Items">
				<Additional>
					<Name>Falcon-horn of Fredemund</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<Rule>Until the start of the next Bretonnian turn, no enemy unit may fly, one use only</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. The Horn may he sounded at the start of any Bretonnian turn. Until the start of the next Bretonnian turn, no enemy unit may fly - they are forced to use their ground movement. Note that this may also alter the enemies flee/pursuit distance</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Holy Icon</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>Magic Resistance (3)</Rule>
					<Description>The Holy Icon gives the character Magic Resistance (3)</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>The Ruby Goblet</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>This magic item will start to take effect at the end of the first phase during which the bearer or his unit suffers an unsaved wound; from that moment on, the bearer (and any unit he is with) cannot be wounded on better than a 3+ from any non-magical source</Rule>
					<Description>This magic item will start to take effect at the end of the first phase during which the bearer or his unit suffers an unsaved wound. From that moment on, the bearer (and any unit he is with) cannot be wounded on better than a 3+ from any non-magical source</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>The Mane of the Purebreed</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Dependencies>
						<On>Barded Warhorse</On>
					</Dependencies>
					<Rule>+1 Strength to the character's Warhorse and those of any unit he is with the first time they charge</Rule>
					<Description>Character on Warhorse only. The Mane confers +1 Strength to the character's Warhorse and those of any unit he is with the first time they charge</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Antlers of the Great Hunt</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>The Knight (and any unit he is with) may roll an additional dice when pursuing and choose the highest three (two if on foot)</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Tress of Isoulde</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>Nominate one enemy model at the beginning of any Close Combat phase: the bearer hits that model on a 2+ for that Close Combat round, regardless of other modifiers</Rule>
					<Description>Nominate one enemy model at the beginning of any Close Combat phase. The bearer hits that model on a 2+ for that Close Combat round, regardless of other modifiers</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Gauntlet of the Duel</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Rule>Any challenge issued cannot be refused</Rule>
					<Description>Any challenge issued by the bearer of the Gauntlet of the Duel cannot be refused</Description>
				</Additional>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Arcane Items">
				<Arcane>
					<Name>The Silver Mirror</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>May be used with the exact same effects as a Dispel Scroll, in addition, the enemy Wizard who cast the spell suffers an immediate Strength 6 hit, one use only</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. May be used with the exact same effects as a Dispel Scroll. In addition, the enemy Wizard who cast the spell suffers an immediate Strength 6 hit</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Sacrament of the Lady</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>At the start of any Bretonnian Magic phase, the hearer may use the Sacrament: the model generates double its usual number of Power dice, but may not cast any spells that turn, each time the Sacramente are used, roll a dice: on a 1 the model has run out of wafers and after that turn the Sacrament cannot be used for the remainder of the game</Rule>
					<Description>At the start of any Bretonnian Magic phase, the hearer may use the Sacrament. The model generates double its usual number of Power dice, but may not cast any spells that turn. Each time the Sacramente are used, roll a dice. On a 1 the model has run out of wafers and after that turn the Sacrament cannot be used for the remainder of the game</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>The Verdant Heart</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>Any wood or forest that the bearer is within counts as very difficult terrain as long as the character remains wholly within the terrain feature</Rule>
					<Rule>In addition, the bearer gains +1 to cast spells from the Lore of Life</Rule>
					<Description>Any wood or forest that the bearer is within counts as very difficult terrain as long as the character remains wholly within the terrain feature. In addition, the bearer gains +1 to cast spells from the Lore of Life</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Prayer Icon of Quenelles</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>One use only: the bearer and the unit she is with are immediately granted the Blessing of the Lady</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. The Prayer Icon can be revealed at any time. The bearer and the unit she is with are immediately granted the Blessing of the Lady. This can allow a unit that has lost the blessing to regain it</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Chalice of Malfleur</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>At the start of the opponent's Magic phase, may drink from the Chalice: if she does so, on the roll of a 1 she suffers a wound with no saves allowed, including Ward saves. On a roll of 2-6, an extra Dispel dice is added to the player's pool</Rule>
					<Description>At the start of the opponent's Magic phase, the bearer may drink from the Chalice. If she does so, on the roll of a 1 she suffers a wound with no saves allowed, including Ward saves. On a roll of 2-6, an extra Dispel dice is added to the player's pool</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Potion Sacre</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Rule>This is used before rolling the dice to cast or dispel a spell: after the dice are rolled, the player may add +1 to the result of one dice, one use only</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. This is used before rolling the dice to cast or dispel a spell. After the dice are rolled, the player may add +1 to the result of one dice. This may cause Irresistible Force or prevent a Miscast</Description>
				</Arcane>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Magic Banners">
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of the Lady</Name>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<Rule>All enemy units with al least one model in base contact with the bearer of the Banner of the Lady get no combat bonus for ranks</Rule>
					<Description>Model on foot or on Bretonnian Warhorse only. All enemy units with al least one model in base contact with the bearer of the Banner of the Lady get no combat bonus for ranks</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Valorous Standard</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<ColdBlooded/>
					<Description>Knights unit only. The unit rolls 3D6 for all Leadership based tests (including Break tests) and discards the highest</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of Defence</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>As long as the unit is affected by the Blessing of the Lady, all models in a unit with the Banner gain a 4+ Ward save against all missiles (including magic missiles) with Strength 5 or more</Rule>
					<Description>As long as the unit is affected by the Blessing of the Lady, all models in a unit with the Banner gain a 4+ Ward save against all missiles (including magic missiles) with Strength 5 or more. If the Blessing of the Lady is lost, then the Banner loses this ability</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Twilight Banner</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>One use only: in the Remaining Moves section of the turn unit suffer no movement penalties for moving over difficult terrain or obstacles, or from any other reductions to movement, they can move through buildings just as easily, but cannot move through other units</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. The Twilight Banner can only be used in the Remaining Moves section of the turn (so a unit cannot use it on the turn it charges). They suffer no movement penalties for moving over difficult terrain or obstacles, or from any other reductions to movement. They can move through buildings just as easily, but cannot move through other units. In addition, they cannot end their move inside impassable terrain. These effects work only for that one Movement phase</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Conqueror's Tapestry</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Every enemy standard captured is worth 200 Victory Points instead of 100</Rule>
					<Description>Every enemy standard captured by the unit possessing the Conqueror's Tapestry is worth 200 Victory Points instead of 100. If an enemy unit captures the Conqueror's Tapestry, the enemy gains 200 Victory Points rather than 100</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Errantry Banner</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>All Knights Errant in the unit get a +1 Strength bonus on any turn they charge</Rule>
					<Description>Knights Errant only. All Knights Errant in the unit get a +1 Strength bonus on any turn they charge (no effect on steeds or characters). However, a unit with this banner suffers -2 to its Ld for any Impetuous tests</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of Chalons</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Rule>The enemy cannot choose the stand and shoot reaction</Rule>
					<Description>The enemy cannot choose the stand and shoot reaction against the unit carrying the Banner</Description>
				</Banner>
			</Group>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Green Knight</Name>
				<Points>275</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Mount>The Shadow Steed</Mount>
				<Description>The Green Knight, the champion of the Lady of the Lake</Description>
				<Profile M='4' WS='7' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='6' A='4' Ld='9' AS='5' Ward='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<Undead/>
					<Original>He suffers no movement penalties for moving over or through any kind of terrain; He never suffers any movement penalties, even from such things as magical effects</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>The Dolorous Blade</Name>
						<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
						<Rule>The Dolorous Blade may be used in one of two ways. Either the Green Knight can use the Blade to gain +D6 Attacks, or it can be used to add +2 to his Strength. The Green Knight may change which method he is using to attack with in each Close Combat phase if he wishes to.</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Fay Enchantress</Name>
				<Points>545</Points>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Mount>Silvaron</Mount>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='3' I='5' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<Fear/>
					<Test Bet="Wound" Context="Round" Profile="Initiative"/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>One model in the Bretonnian army may be given the Favour of the Fay, this model may add +1 on all rolls to hit in close combat; however, if the model loses the Blessing of the Lady, then both the Favoured model and the Fay Enchantress take a wound that cannot be saved by Armour or Ward saves</Rule>
						<Rule>Bretonnian army does not need to pray at the start of the game to gain the Blessing of the Lady</Rule>
						<Rule>Ward save gained from the Blessing of the Lady is increased to 5+ against any attack</Rule>
						<Rule>The Fay Enchantress may be accompanied by 2-8 Grail Guardians, the Fay Enchantress can never choose to leave this unit</Rule>
						<Rule>Against Skaven, Ores and Goblins and all Beasts of Chaos she causes Terror</Rule>
						<Rule>Magic Resistance (3)</Rule>
						<Rule>May use any of the eight lores</Rule>
						<Rule>+2 to cast Lore of Life spells</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Girdle of Gold</Name>
						<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					</Armour>
					<Arcane>
						<Name>The Chalice of Potions</Name>
						<Rule>At any point during each Bretonnian Magic phase, the Fay Enchantress may peer into the Chalice and stir up magical power to use against her foes: roll a D6 each time the Chalice is used, the number refers to which spell is automatically cast from the Lore of Heavens as a Bound Spell (at the Power Level equal to the minimum casting level for the spell)</Rule>
					</Arcane>
					<Arcane>
						<Name>The Toad Familiar</Name>
						<AddToCast Val="1"/>
						<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
					</Arcane>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>King Louen</Name>
				<Points>728</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Mount>Beaquis</Mount>
				<Description>King Louen Leoncoeur</Description>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='7' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='7' A='5' Ld='9' Ward=''/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Reroll>ToHit;ToWound</Reroll>
					<Regeneration/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>If Louen is removed as a casualty, all Bretonnian units must take a Panic test; Such is the determination to reclaim their fallen ruler that all Bretonnian troops count as stubborn for the rest of the battle</Rule>
						<Rule>The 0-1 restriction on Grail Knights is lifted, Men-at-arms and Bowmen become Special choices</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>The Sword of Couronne</Name>
						<AddToStrength Val="1"/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Lance/>
					<Armour>
						<Name>The Crown of Bretonnia</Name>
						<Rule>Friendly troops may use Louen Leoncoeur's Leadership characteristic when he is within 18" instead of the usual 12"; Any unit with line of sight to him is immune to panic</Rule>
					</Armour>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Armour>
						<Name>The Lion's Shield</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
						<Rule>Louen has a Magic Resistance value equal to the total number of dice used in the casting of any spell that affects him</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Bretonnian Lord</Name>
				<Points>110</Points>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='6' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='6' A='4' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyNativeArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<QuestingVow Points="12" Dependency="Vow"/>
					<GrailVow Points="28" Dependency="Vow"/>
					<MorningStar Points="6"/>
					<Lance Points="6" Only="Mount" Dependencies="Off: Questing Vow"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6" Dependencies="Off: Questing Vow"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
					<Mount Name="Barded Warhorse" Points="21"/>
					<Mount Name="Royal Pegasus" Points="50"/>
					<Mount Name="Hippogryph" Points="200"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Prophetess of the Lady</Name>
				<Points>190</Points>
				<Wizard>3</Wizard>
				<Image>Prophetess</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='3' I='3' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Wizard"/>
					<Original>Magic Resistance (2)</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="4" Points="35"/>
					<Mount Name="Horse" Points="15"/>
					<Barding Points="6" For="Horse"/>
					<Mount Name="Royal Pegasus" Points="50"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Paladin</Name>
				<Points>60</Points>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='5' A='3' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyNativeArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<QuestingVow Points="8" Dependency="Vow"/>
					<GrailVow Points="21" Dependency="Vow"/>
					<MorningStar Points="2"/>
					<Lance Points="4" Only="Mount" Dependencies="Off: Questing Vow"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4" Dependencies="Off: Questing Vow"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
					<Mount Name="Barded Warhorse" Points="14"/>
					<Mount Name="Royal Pegasus" Points="50"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Damsel of the Lady</Name>
				<Points>70</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Image>Damsel</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Wizard"/>
					<Original>Magic Resistance (2)</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="2" Points="35"/>
					<Mount Name="Horse" Points="10"/>
					<Barding Points="4" For="Horse"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Horse</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Barded Warhorse</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>The Shadow Steed</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='4' BS='0' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Silvaron</Name>
				<Profile M='10' WS='5' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='5' A='2' Ld='8' Ward=''/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ChargeStrengthBonus Val="2"/>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Royal Pegasus</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Beaquis</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='5' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='4' I='6' A='4' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
					<LargeTarget/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Hippogryph</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='4' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='4' I='4' A='4' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Fly/>
					<LargeTarget/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Knights Errant</Name>
				<Group>Knights</Group>
				<Points>20</Points>
				<Size>5-15</Size>
				<Mount>Barded Warhorse</Mount>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>After charges have been declared, if unit did not declare a charge but are within charge range of an enemy, then they must take a Leadership test to restrain themselves from charging; if this test is failed, they are forced to charge; if the test is passed, they may move normally; in addition, so reckless are the Knights Errant, that whenever they charge, the unit and any characters that have joined them are Immune to Psychology for the rest of that turn</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Name="Cavalier"/>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Knights of the Realm</Name>
				<Group>Knights</Group>
				<Points>24</Points>
				<Size>5-15</Size>
				<Mount>Barded Warhorse</Mount>
				<Image>KnightsRealm</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='8' AS='5'/>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Lance/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Name="Gallant"/>
						<Musician Points="8"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="16" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Men-at-arms</Name>
				<Points>5</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>MenAtArms</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='2' BS='2' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LeadershipOfKnight/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Pole-arm</Name>
						<AddToStrength Val="1"/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<LightArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Spears/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Yeoman Warden"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Peasant Bowman</Name>
				<Points>6</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>Bowman</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='2' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LeadershipOfKnight/>
					<Original>No unit gains any charge bonus when they charge the unit's front</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Longbow/>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Defensive stakes</Name>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<LightArmour PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Skirmishers PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Braziers Points="5"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="5" Name="Villein"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Questing Knights</Name>
				<Group>QuestingVow</Group>
				<Points>28</Points>
				<Size>5-12</Size>
				<Mount>Barded Warhorse</Mount>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='8' AS='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>May re-roll any failed Psychology tests</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Name="Paragon"/>
						<Musician Points="9"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="18" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Pegasus Knights</Name>
				<Group>Knights</Group>
				<Points>55</Points>
				<Size>3-10</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Mount>Royal Pegasus</Mount>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='2' I='4' A='1' Ld='8' AS='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<FlyingCavalry/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Lance/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Name="Gallant"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="20"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Mounted Yeomen</Name>
				<Points>15</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Horse</Mount>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LeadershipOfKnight/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Spear/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Bow/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<LightArmour PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="14" Name="Warden"/>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Grail Knights</Name>
				<Group>GrailVow</Group>
				<Points>38</Points>
				<Size>3-12</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Mount>Barded Warhorse</Mount>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='2' Ld='8' AS='5' Ward='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>5+ Ward save versus attacks with Strength 5 or higher</Rule>
						<Rule>Every model in a unit of Grail Knights can issue and accept challenges as if they were a Champion</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Lance/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="20" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Field Trebuchet</Name>
				<Points>90</Points>
				<Mount>Peasant</Mount>
				<Image>Trebuchet</Image>
				<Profile M='4' WS='2' BS='2' S='3' T='7' W='4' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<LeadershipOfKnight/>
					<Original>Field Trebuchet</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Yeoman Craftsman"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>