<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Imprint>
			<Army>Skaven</Army>
			<Edition>6</Edition>
			<Released>2006</Released>
			<Authors>Alessio Cavatore and Anthony Reynolds</Authors>
			<Description>The Skaven, sometimes known as the Ratmen, the Ratkin or the Children of the Horned Rat, are a malevolent and diabolical race of large humanoid rat-creatures that inhabit a massive inter-continental underground empire known in their tongue simply as the Under-Empire, where at the very heart of Skavendom lies the horrific city of Skavenblight, the species capital city and the probable birthplace of the Skaven race. The Skaven as a whole are a cruel, treacherous, and highly numerous species that have since spread their loathsome corruption to the farthest corners of the Warhammer World. From deep below the earth, these scavengers have built a vast Empire, whose military power and incomprehensible numbers have the potential to smother the kingdoms of the Old World in a seething tide of violence and anarchy. It is believed by all of Skaven-kind that the world is destined to be theirs, for they consider themselves the Supreme Master Race, undeniably superior in every way to all the other races of the World</Description>
		</Imprint>
		<Styles>
			<Colors>
				<Front>fbba78</Front>
				<Back>7b4611</Back>
				<Grid>ffe6cc</Grid>
				<Tooltip>fbdab8</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>c19a72, ad7843, a3672c</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<Images>
				<Files>
					<Cover/>
					<Symbol/>
					<Illustration/>
				</Files>
				<Folders>
					<Units/>
				</Folders>
			</Images>
		</Styles>
		<Naming>
			<Internal>Skaven</Internal>
			<MagicItems>Tools of Supremacy</MagicItems>
			<Buttons>
				<Add>add-add</Add>
				<Drop>drop-drop</Drop>
			</Buttons>
		</Naming>
		<Magic>
			<Name>Skaven Spell List</Name>
			<Magic>
				<Spell Name="Skitterleap" Cast="4"/>
				<Spell Name="Warp Lightning" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Vermintide" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Pestilent Breath" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Death Frenzy" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Plague" Cast="13"/>
			</Magic>
			<Enemy>High Elves, High Magic Spells</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Walk Between Worlds" Cast="6"/>
				<Spell Name="Curse of Arrow Attraction" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Fortune is Fickle" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Fury of Khaine" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Flame of the Phoenix" Cast="13"/>
				<Spell Name="Vaul's Unmaking" Cast="14"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<Local>
			<SpecialRules>
				<MixedUnit/>
				<LossOfPackmaster>Loss of Packmaster</LossOfPackmaster>
				<Scirmishers/>
			</SpecialRules>
			<Options>
				<WarplockPistol/>
				<Whip/>
				<Warpblades>
					Name: Warp-blades
					AddToStrength: 1
				</Warpblades>
				<UpgradedCondenser>
					Name: Upgraded warp-energy condenser
				</UpgradedCondenser>
				<Accumulator>
					Name: Supercharged warp-power accumulator
					AddToCast: 1
				</Accumulator>
				<SmokeBombs/>
				<PlagueRats>
					PoisonAttack
				</PlagueRats>
				<Slings/>
				<ThrowingStars/>
				<PoisonedWeapons>
					Name: Poisoned hand weapons
					PoisonAttack
				</PoisonedWeapons>
				<PoisonedThrowingStars/>
				<TunnellingTeams>
					Rule: Tunnelling rule
				</TunnellingTeams>
			</Options>
		</Local>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<CommonMagicItems>
				<SwordOfStriking Points="30"/>
				<SwordOfBattle Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfMight Points="20"/>
				<BitingBlade Points="10"/>
				<EnchantedShield Points="10"/>
				<TalismanOfProtection Points="15"/>
				<DispellScroll Points="25"/>
				<PowerStone Points="25"/>
				<StaffOfSorcery Points="50"/>
				<WarBanner Points="25"/>
			</CommonMagicItems>
			<MagicWeapons>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Fellblade</Name>
					<Points>85</Points>
					<StrengthTo Val="10"/>
					<MultiWounds Val="D6"/>
					<Rule>Wound wielder with no armour save at the end of each turns on a 3+</Rule>
					<Description>The Fellblade's wielder has Strength 10. Each unsaved wound is multiplied into D6 wounds. Roll a dice at the end of the wielder s turn: on a 3+ there is no effect; on a roll of 1-2 the wielder suffers 1 wound with no armour save allowed</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Gouger</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<NoArmour/>
					<Description>No armour saves are allowed against wounds caused by the Gouger</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Blade of Black Fury</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<AddToAttacks Val="2"/>
					<Description>The sword confers +2 Attacks to the wielder</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Warpstone stars</Name>
					<Only>Eshin</Only>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>As many Warpstone Stars in a single Shooting phase as Attacks on profile, Strength 5 and each unsaved wound multiplies into D3 wounds</Rule>
					<Description>The model can throw as many Warpstone Stars in a single Shooting phase as it has Attacks on its profile (all against the same target). Treat them as normal throwing stars, but with a range of 10" and Strength 5. Each unsaved wound is multiplied into D3 wounds</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Weeping Blade</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="1"/>
					<MultiWounds Val="D3"/>
					<Description>The wielder has +1 Strength. Each unsaved Wound is multiplied into D3 wounds</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Cursed Blade of Delirium</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<WeaponSkillTo Val="10"/>
					<Description>The wielder's Weapon Skill is raised to 10</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Headsplitter</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<WoundOn Val="2"/>
					<NoArmour/>
					<Description>This is treated as a normal sling, but against models with Toughness 5 or more, it always wounds on a 2+ with no armour saves allowed</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Desolate Blade</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
					<Description>The sword confers +2 Strength to all close combat attacks made by the wielder</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Dwarf-slayer</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>Wounds on a 2+ against Dwarfs</Rule>
					<Rule>Armour saves suffer a -3 against Dwarfs</Rule>
					<Description>Against Dwarfs, the wielder always wounds on a 2+. Armour saves suffer a -3 modifier, regardless of the wielder s Strength</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Blade of Corruption</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Only>Pestilens</Only>
					<Rule>Once an enemy has suffered an unsaved wound, he must roll a dice at the beginning of each of his turns, on 1-3 he will suffer one wound, with no armour save allowed</Rule>
					<Description>Once an enemy has suffered an unsaved wound from this weapon, he must roll a dice at the beginning of each of his turns. On a roll of 1-3 he will suffer one wound, with no armour save allowed</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Languisher Sword</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<HitFirst/>
					<Description>The wielder of the sword always strikes first in close Combat, even before enemies that have charged. If the wielder is fighting another enemy who is also entitled to strike first (because of spells, special abilities, etc), then resolve attacks in Initiative order. It both combatants' Initiative values are equal, roll a dice to determine who strikes first</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Death Globes</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Only>Skryre</Only>
					<Rule>Death Globe</Rule>
					<Description>The character can throw one Globe per shooting phase. Place the small round template with its centre nywherc within 8" of the character. Scatter the template and resolve hits as you would for a Stone Thrower template. All models hit suffer a wound on the result of a 4+ with no armour save allowed. If you roll a Misfire, centre the template on the model throwing the globe</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Blade of Nurglitch</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>Enemy lose 1 point of Toughness for each unsaved wound</Rule>
					<Description>Enemy models lose 1 point of Toughness from their profile for each unsaved wound they suffer, to a minimum of Toughness 1</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Things-Catcher</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Only>Moulder</Only>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<Description>This weapon requires two hands to use and comers the Killing Blow special ability</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</MagicWeapons>
			<MagicArmours>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Rust Armour</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Rule>If the wearer is wounded by a hit with a Strength sufficiently high to completely cancel his armour save (or a hit that does not allow armour saves), the wound is discounted but the armour falls to pieces and is destroyed</Rule>
					<Description>Gives a 5+ Armour save that can be Combined with other armour as normal. In addition, if the wearer is wounded by a hit with a Strength sufficiently high to completely cancel his armour save (or a hit that does not allow armour saves at all, such as from a cannon ball), the wound is discounted but the armour falls to pieces and is destroyed</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Warpstone Armour</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="4"/>
					<Rule>Strength 4 hit against enemy for each successful armour save</Rule>
					<Description>Warpstone Armour gives its wearer a 4+ armour save. For each successful armour save made by the bearer in close combat, the armour immediately inflicts a Strength 4 hit against the model that struck the blow</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Cautious Shield</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Rule>Can force one model in base contact to lose 1 Attack (2 Attack if decide not to attack enemy)</Rule>
					<Description>Gives a 6+ armour save rhat can he combined with other armour as normal. The bearer can force one model in base contact to lose 1 Attack (he can choose which Attack in the case of opponents with different Attacks, such as cavalry models).\n\nIn addition, the model can decide not to attack at all, but to wield the shield with jwo hands and concentrate on defence. If he decides to do this, the chosen enemy will lose 2 Attacks. The player must declare which way the shield will be used at the beginning of each Close Combat phase, before any side strikes blows</Description>
				</Armour>
			</MagicArmours>
			<Talismans>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Twisted Crown of the Horned Rat</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Regeneration/>
					<Description>The Twisted Crown gives the wearer the Regeneration ability</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Tenebrous Cloak</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>3+ Ward save against normal and magical missiles</Rule>
					<Description>This item confers a 3+ Ward save to the wearer against normal and magical missiles</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Foul Pendant</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Description>The pendant confers a 5+ Ward save to the bearer</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Warpstone Amulet</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					<Rule>At the end of the game roll a D6: on the result of 1, the character counts as a casualty</Rule>
					<Description>The Amulet confers to the bearer a 4+ Ward save. At the end of the game roll a D6. On the result of 1, the character succumbs to the mutating power of the warpstone and counts as a casualty for the purposes of allocating Victory points, and cannot contest table quarters. No re-rolls are allowed for this final roll</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Ring of Darkness</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					<MagicResistance Val="1"/>
					<Description>The bearer and the unit he is with have Magic Resistance (1). Also, when a spell, magic item or any other scrying magic would force the Skaven player to reveal magic items or any other 'hidden' presence in the unit, the Skaven player must only reveal the presence of this ring. Everything else remains hidden</Description>
				</Additional>
			</Talismans>
			<EnchantedItems>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Cloak of Shadows</Name>
					<Only>Eshin</Only>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>In order to shoot or cast a spell, enemy units first need to roll a 5 or 6 on a D6</Rule>
					<Description>In order to shoot or cast a spell against the bearer, enemy units first need to roll a 5 or 6 on a D6. If they fail, they can choose a different target, choose to cast a different spell, etc. It the bearer is inside a unit or is engaged in close combat, the cloak has no effect</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Skalm</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Once at the beginning of any phase may cures of any wounds</Rule>
					<Description>Use once, at the beginning of any phase (own or enemy's). Skalm cures all wounds suffered so far by the bearer</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Brass Orb</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Test Bet="Death" Context="Round" Repeat="Once" Profile="Initiative"/>
					<Description>Once per battle, the user can throw the orb exactly like a Death Globe. Models hit must take an Initiative test or be destroyed, with no saves (of any kind) allowed. Remember that a 6 is always a failure, but characters are allowed a 'Look Out Sir!' roll as normal. An Empire Steam Tank hit by the orb suffers 3D6 points Of damage</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Skavenbrew</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Skavenbrew</Rule>
					<Description>A character can feed Skavenbrew to the unit he is with at the beginning of the battle. The Skavenbrew will have no effect on other characters in the unit. Roll a D6 to determine the effect of the Skavenbrew:\n\nD6    Result\n\n1      No effect.\n\n2-3    The unit and the character are frenzied.\n\n4-5    The unit and the character bate all enemies.\n\n6   The unit and the character are frenzied and hate all enemies (despite being immune to psychology due to frenzy). In addition, the unit suffers D3 wounds from overexertion at the end of every Skaven turn (distribute them as missile hits, no armour save allowed)</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Liber Bubonicus</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Only>Pestilens</Only>
					<AddToWizard Val="1"/>
					<AddToCast Val="1"/>
					<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
					<Rule>Skavenbrew</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer is a Level 1 Wizard, but has no Warpstone tokens. He knows the Pestilent Breath spell</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Bands of Power</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, Power Level 4, Once per Magic phase doubles the model's basic Strength value until the beginning of his side's following Magic phase</Rule>
					<Description>Once per Magic phase, the user can cast the spell bound within the bracers. The spell requires no Power dice to cast as all the power is provided by the bands. The spell doubles the model's basic Strength value until the beginning of his side's following Magic phase</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Warpstone Charm</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>May re-roll any single dice roll once during the game</Rule>
					<Description>This item allows its bearer to re-roll any single dice roll once during the game. This can even be used to effectively cancel a Miscast or cause Irresistible-Poire</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</EnchantedItems>
			<ArcaneItems>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Warpstorm Scroll</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, Power Level 5, All flying units, flying monsters and their riders within 24" suffer D6 Strength 6 hits, one use only</Rule>
					<Description>All units ol flyers within 24" of the caster suffer D6 Strength 6 hits. Flying monsters and their riders within range also suffer D6 Strength 6 hits, randomised like shooting hits</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Warp Scroll</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, Power Level 5, One Strength 3 hit on every model in the unit (Panic test if the unit suffers any casualties), one use only</Rule>
					<Description>The scroll's spell has a range of 24" and can be cast on any unit which is visible to the bearer. The spell contained in the scroll inflicts one Strength 3 hit on every model in the unit. If the unit suffers any casualties, it must take a Panic test</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Storm Daemon</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, Power Level 4, Once in each Magic phases, cast the Warp Lightning spell (the weakest version only), roll a D6 even time it is used: on a 1 the Storm Daemon cannot be used for the rest of the battle</Rule>
					<Description>Once in each of his own Magic phases, the bearer can cast the Warp Lightning spell (the weakest version only). The spell requires no Power dice to Cast as all the power is provided by the Storm Daemon itself.\n\nRoll a D6 even time it is used. On a 1 the Storm Daemon runs out of power and cannot be used for the rest of the battle</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Eye of The Horned Rat</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Roll a D6: on 2-6 add one Power dice to the Power dice pool, if a 1 is rolled one dice is removed from the pool</Rule>
					<Description>The Wizard can decide to activate the Eye at the beginning of each of his Magic phases. On a result of 2-6 add one Power dice to the Power dice pool. If a 1 is rolled, no dice are added to the pool and instead one dice is removed from the pool</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Warpstone Tokens</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Rule>Warpstone Tokens</Rule>
					<Description>In a similar way to scrolls, all Skaven wizards in the army can buy as many Warpstone tokens as they can afford within the limit of the points they can spend on magic items. Buying one or more tokens does not count taking Arcane item</Description>
				</Arcane>
			</ArcaneItems>
			<MagicStandards>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Storm Banner</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Rule>No flying movement is allowed</Rule>
					<Rule>Missile fire is at -2 to hit</Rule>
					<Description>The banner can be activated at the beginning of any player’s turn. No flying movement is allowed across the entire battlefield and missile fire is at -2 to hit. All non-magical missile attacks that don’t use BS to hit their target need to roll a 4+ on a D6 before they can fire. Roll a D6 at the beginning of each following player turn - the effects of the banner will end on a D6 roll of 1 or 2</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Sacred Banner of the Horned Rat</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Fear/>
					<Description>All models in the unit cause fear</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Umbranner</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>4+ Ward save against all normal and magical missiles with Strength 4 or less</Rule>
					<Description>All models in the unit carrying the banner receive a 4+ Ward save against all normal and magical missiles with Strength 4 or less</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of The Four Black Winds</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>Flying-models must use their ground movement value to charge the unit</Rule>
					<Description>Flying-models wishing to charge the unit carrying the banner must use their ground movement value and cannot use their flying movement to charge</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of burning hatred</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Hate/>
					<Description>The unit hates all enemies, even if the unit is normally immune to psychology because of frenzy. Roll a Do6 at the beginning of each of the unit's Movement phases if the unit is not declaring a charge. On a roll of 1-3 the unit has to move as fast as it can towards the closest enemy it can see</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of the Swarm</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>Outnumber bonus +2 instead of the normal +1</Rule>
					<Description>If the unit carrying the banner is fighting in a combat where its side outnumbers the enemy, the "outnumber enemy' bonus is +2 instead of the normal +1</Description>
				</Banner>
			</MagicStandards>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Gray Seer Thanquol</Name>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Points>560</Points>
				<Mount>Boneripper</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Image>Thanquol</Image>
				<Description>Grey Seer Thanquol is arguably one of the most cunning, devious and perhaps the most ambitious Skaven Sorcerer to have ever lived, having worked previously as High Emissary in the service of the tyrannical Council of Thirteen. Considered by himself as being one of the most talented and ingenious minds the Under-Empire has ever known, Thanquol has served many roles within the Skaven hierarchy, having worked as a skilled diplomat and politician for many powerful Warlords and Generals. This prestigious role has garnered him an immense fortune in both wealth and magical power.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='3' I='6' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Can re-roll the dice by Warpstone token then rolls a 1</Rule>
						<Rule>13 Warpstone Tokens</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Staff of the Horned One</Name>
						<Rule>Additional spell</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Rule>Blessed by the Horned Rat</Rule>
						<AddToWard Val="4"/>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Amulet of the Horned One</Name>
						<Rule>At the beginning of each turns regains a single Wound on roll of 5+</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Screaming Bell</Name>
						<Points>200</Points>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Throt</Name>
				<Group>Moulder</Group>
				<Points>285</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Throt the Unclean is one of the most twisted and ingenious Master Mutators of Clan Moulder and has exploited that success to position himself as one of the nine Lords of Hell Pit. The effects of a lifetime's work with warpstone can be seen, as bone spines protrude out of Throt's back and a third arm sprouts out of his bloated but powerful frame.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='3' I='7' A='4' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Regeneration/>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Re-roll any single dice roll once during the game</Rule>
						<Rule>Master Controller</Rule>
						<Rule>May never pursue a fleeng enemy they have broken in combat</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Creature-killer</Name>
						<KillingBlow/>
						<Rule>D3 wounds for large creatures</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Dominatator</Name>
						<AddToAttack Val="1"/>
					</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Warlord</Name>
				<Points>90</Points>
				<Description>To hold the title of Warlord is to rule supreme. In battle these brutal, back-stabbing commanders will do anything for victory, leading from the back, a nice safe place where he can watch the flow of battle and decide where his sword arm is needed most.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='7' A='4' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="6"/>
					<Halberd Points="6"/>
					<WarplockPistol Points="15"/>
					<LightArmour Points="3" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="6" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Gray Seer</Name>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Points>235</Points>
				<Description>The Grey Seers are powerful sorcerers, capable of channeling eldritch energies in destructive ways - levelling armies with lightning, or summoning ravening swarms of rats. As chief agents for the Horned Rat, Grey Seers wield tremendous influence amongst the warlord clans, and only a fool would ignore their council.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='3' I='5' A='1' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Wizard"/>
					<Original>4 Warpstone tokens</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Mount Name="Screaming Bell" Points="200"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Chieftain</Name>
				<Points>45</Points>
				<Description>Skaven Chieftains, or Clan Chieftains, are among the highest ranking warriors within a Skaven Clan, who are often given control over a smaller segment of the Clan to rule as they see fit.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='6' A='3' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="2"/>
					<Halberd Points="4"/>
					<LightArmour Points="2" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Plague Priest</Name>
				<Group>Pestilens</Group>
				<Points>70</Points>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='5' W='2' I='5' A='3' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<Frenzy/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Option>
						<Name>Plague Censer</Name>
						<Flail/>
						<Test Bet="Wound" Context="Round" Profile="Toughness"/>
						<Points>16</Points>
					</Option>
					<Flail Points="4"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="4"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Master Moulder</Name>
				<Group>Moulder</Group>
				<Points>65</Points>
				<Profile M='6' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='6' A='3' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<Original>Beastmaster</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Whip Points="6"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4"/>
					<LightArmour Points="3"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Warlock Engineer</Name>
				<Group>Skryre</Group>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Points>45</Points>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Wizard"/>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
					<Original>1 Warpstone tokens</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<WarplockPistol Points="10"/>
					<Warpblades Points="15"/>
					<UpgradedCondenser Points="10"/>
					<Accumulator Points="15"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Assassin</Name>
				<Group>Eshin</Group>
				<Points>105</Points>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='5' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='8' A='3' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<PoisonAttack/>
					<NotALeader/>
					<Scout/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Hidden</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
					<RangeWeapon>Throwing stars</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<SmokeBombs Points="20"/>
				</Options>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Screaming Bell</Name>
				<Profile M='0' WS='0' BS='0' S='5' T='6' W='6' I='0' A='0' Ld='0' Ward=''/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<MagicResistance Val="2"/>
					<AddToCast Val="2"/>
					<ImpactHit Val="D6"/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Ringing the Bell</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<WeaponTeam/>
				<Name>Warpfire Thrower</Name>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='2' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<WeaponTeam/>
				<Name>Ratling Gun</Name>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='2' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Boneripper</Name>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='3' I='1' A='4' Ld='10' AS='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Original>Bodyguard of Thanquol</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Razor sharp talon</HandWeapon>
					<RangeWeapon>Warpfire Thrower</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Clanrats</Name>
				<Points>5</Points>
				<Size>20+</Size>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Spear PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Crew Name="Warpfire Thrower" Points="75"/>
					<Crew Name="Ratling Gun" Points="55"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Clawleader"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Stormvermin</Name>
				<Points>8</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Halberd/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Crew Name="Warpfire Thrower" Points="75"/>
					<Crew Name="Ratling Gun" Points="60"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="100" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Fangleader"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Rat Swarm</Name>
				<Points>45</Points>
				<Size>1-5</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Profile M='6' WS='3' BS='0' S='2' T='2' W='5' I='1' A='5' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Swarm</Rule>
						<Rule>Small</Rule>
						<Rule>Expendable</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<PlagueRats PointsPerModel="20"/>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Giant Rats</Name>
				<Points>30</Points>
				<Size>1+</Size>
				<ModelsInPack Val="6"/>
				<Profile M='6' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
					<MixedUnit/>
					<LossOfPackmaster/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Night Runners</Name>
				<Points>5</Points>
				<Size>5-20</Size>
				<Image>Runners</Image>
				<Profile M='6' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
					<Scirmishers/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<Slings PointsPerModel="4"/>
					<ThrowingStars PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Nightleader"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Clanrat slaves</Name>
				<Points>2</Points>
				<Size>20+</Size>
				<Image>Slaves</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='2' BS='2' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='2'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
					<Original>Expendable</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Spear PointsPerModel="1" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Slings PointsPerModel="2" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="4"/>
						<Champion Points="8" Name="Pawleader"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Poisoned Wind Globadiers</Name>
				<Points>10</Points>
				<Size>2-10</Size>
				<Image>Globadiers</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
					<Skirmishers/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Poisoned wind globes</RangeWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Gutter Runners</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>5-15</Size>
				<Image>Gutters</Image>
				<Profile M='6' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
					<Scirmishers/>
					<Scouts/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Slings PointsPerModel="5"/>
					<ThrowingStars PointsPerModel="3"/>
					<PoisonedWeapons PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<PoisonedThrowingStars PointsPerModel="1" Dependencies="On: Throwing stars"/>
					<TunnellingTeams PointsPerModel="3"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Black Skaven"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Warplock Jezzails</Name>
				<Points>20</Points>
				<Size>3-10</Size>
				<Image>Jezzails</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='2' A='2' Ld='5' AS='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<Original>Reliable</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RangeWeapon>Jezzail</RangeWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Pavise</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Sharpshooter"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Plague Monks</Name>
				<Group>Pestilens</Group>
				<Points>6</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>Monks</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Frenzy/>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="2"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Deacon"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Rat Ogres</Name>
				<Points>50</Points>
				<Size>1+</Size>
				<ModelsInPack Val="2"/>
				<Profile M='6' WS='3' BS='0' S='5' T='4' W='3' I='3' A='3' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
					<MixedUnit/>
					<LossOfPackmaster/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Plague Censer Bearers</Name>
				<Points>17</Points>
				<Size>5-10</Size>
				<Image>CenserBearers</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Frenzy/>
					<Hate/>
					<StrengthInNumbers/>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<Original>Disciples</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Plague censer</Name>
						<Flail/>
						<Test Bet="Wound" Context="Round" Profile="Toughness"/>
					</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Warp-Ligtning Cannon</Name>
				<Points>100</Points>
				<Image>Cannon</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='0' BS='0' S='0' T='6' W='3' I='1' A='0' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>War Machine</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>