<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Info>
			<Army>Beastmen</Army>
			<Edition>7</Edition>
			<Released>2010</Released>
			<Authors>Andy Hoare and Phil Kelly</Authors>
			<Description>The Beastmen, sometimes known as the Beastkin, the Cloven Ones, the Horned Ones, the Beast of Chaos or even the Children of Chaos, are a race of savage mutant humanoids that bear various traits of bestial appearance, such as cloven hooves, muscular human bodies, horned bestial heads and a malign primitive intelligence. Proud of their origins, it is said that they are the descendants of ancient humans corrupted and twisted by the influence of Chaos at the dawn of Chaos's coming into the world.\n\nFrom deep within the twisted forested woodlands of the Old World and beyond, the Beastmen are a violent, war-driven race that seek only to plague and destroy the civilisations of Mankind. They prey on the weak and defenseless, striking at lonely settlements without warning in a rampage of destruction before disappearing into the protective darkness of their dark wilderness, running away from the dire retribution that fails to follow</Description>
		</Info>
		<Styles>
			<Colors>
				<Front>441e14</Front>
				<Back>5c2212</Back>
				<Grid>f0e4dd</Grid>
				<Tooltip>e4b599</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>9d7a70, 7c4e41, 6c3829</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<Images>
				<Files>
					<Cover/>
					<Symbol/>
					<Illustration/>
				</Files>
				<Folders>
					<Units/>
				</Folders>
			</Images>
		</Styles>
		<Naming>
			<Internal>Beasts</Internal>
			<MagicItems>Gifts of Chaos</MagicItems>
		</Naming>
		<Magic>
			<Name>The Lore of The Wild</Name>
			<Options>Lore of Death, Shadow, Beasts</Options>
			<Magic>
				<Spell Name="Viletide" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Devolve" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Bray-scream" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Traitor-Kin" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Mantle of Ghorok" Cast="13"/>
				<Spell Name="Savage Dominin" Cast="16"/>
			</Magic>
			<Enemy>Wood Elves, The Lore of High Magic</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Apotheosis" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Hand of Glory" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Walk Between Worlds" Cast="7"/>
				<Spell Name="Drain magic" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Soul Quench" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Tempest" Cast="14"/>
				<Spell Name="Arcane Unforging" Cast="15"/>
				<Spell Name="Fiery convocation" Cast="21"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<Local>
			<SpecialRules>
				<PrimalFury/>
				<ManBane>Man-bane</ManBane>
				<Bloodgreed/>
				<BeastmanAmbush/>
			</SpecialRules>
			<Options>
				<PoisonedAttacks>
					PoisonAttack
				</PoisonedAttacks>
				<ScalySkin>
					Name: Scaly Skin
					AddToArmour: 6
				</ScalySkin>
				<ThrowingAxes/>
				<GreatWeaponSpecific>
					Name: Great weapon
					AddToStrength: 2
					AddToArmour: -1
					HitLast
				</GreatWeaponSpecific>
			</Options>
		</Local>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<Commons Name="Common magic items">
				<SwordOfStriking Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfBattle Points="20"/>
				<SwordOfMight Points="15"/>
				<BitingBlade Points="10"/>
				<EnchantedShield Points="15"/>
				<TalismanOfProtection Points="15"/>
				<StaffOfSorcery Points="40"/>
				<DispellScroll Points="25"/>
				<PowerStone Points="20"/>
				<WarBanner Points="25"/>
			</Commons>
			<Gifts Name="Gifts of Chaos">
				<Additional>
					<Name>Crown of Horns</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Lore>Occasionally, a beast that has earned the favour of his patron god sprouts a thick crown of long, jet-black horns from his skull. He is often acknowledged as the warberd's chieftain without a challenge; so obvious are the Dark Gods' blessings. Rivulets of blood constantly trickle from where the horns have pushed through his forehead, and it is obvious to all that the bearer has truly been marked for greatness.Such an individual is supremely confident in his position at the pinnacle of the warberd</Lore>
					<Description>The model and any unit he is with are Stubborn</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Slug-Skin</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Lore>This gift of the Chaos Gods causes the recipient's skin to ooze a constant aura of vile, toxic corruption</Lore>
					<Rule>Enemy models in base contact with the model at the start of any round of close combat suffer a Strength 3 hit before any blows are struck</Rule>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Many-Limbed Fiend</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
					<Lore>The Beastman has sprouted additional arms, allowing him to unleash yet more carnage upon the battlefield</Lore>
					<Description>The model may make a bonus attack in addition to his normal attacks. This bonus attack is always at the model's basic Strength and is never augmented by equipment or magic weapons</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Gouge-Tusks</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<ArmourPiercing Val="1"/>
					<Lore>The Beastman's lower incisors have grown into sharp or excessively large tusks</Lore>
					<Description>All of the model's close combat attacks are armour piercing</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Gnarled Hide</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Lore>The Beastman's skin has encysted, forming a layer of crusty natural armour as tough as chainmail</Lore>
					<Description>The model has a scaly skin save of 5+, which is cumulative with other armour as normal</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Rune of The True Beast</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<SubOpponentToHit Val="1"/>
					<Lore>The bearer was born with a rare and potent rune marked on his flesh, a sigil of pure savagery that marks the individual out as nothing more than a ravenous mass of muscle and fangs. Even the strongest beast will cower before the unbridled ferocity of this raging predator</Lore>
					<Description>Ridden monsters, monsters, the steeds pulling chariots, cavalry mounts and swarms suffer -1 To Hit the model bearing the Rune of the True Beast in close combat, although their riders may attack as normal</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Uncanny Senses</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<AddToInitiative Val="1"/>
					<Lore>The Dark Gods have gifted the Beastman with acute senses, additional eyes or even an extra bead, granting it unnaturally fast reactions</Lore>
					<Description>The model has +1 Initiative</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Shadow-Hide</Name>
					<Points>5</Points>
					<Lore>The bearer's ebon fur appears to absorb light and draw the shadows about it as a cloak of shadows</Lore>
					<Rule>When at least partially in cover, a further -1 To Hit modifier is applied when enemies shoot at the character</Rule>
				</Additional>
			</Gifts>
			<MagicWeapons>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Primeval Club</Name>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<Rule>When rolling To Wound, the character's Strength is treated as equal to the unmodified Leadership value of the target model</Rule>
					<Lore>Though in appearance it is little more than a gnarled great-club bound in cracked leather and infested with spiders and slugs, the Primeval Club was made from a bough of the legendary corpse-tree blessed by Morghur's fell touch. It has been stained red with blood since the dawn of civilisation and is the bane of all order and hope</Lore>
					<Description>When rolling To Wound, the owner's Strength is treated as equal to the unmodified Leadership value of the target model</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Axe of Men</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<Terror/>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<Lore>The Axe of Men is so-called because it hews men apart as easily as other, lesser axes hew timber. A single, mighty stroke from this fearsome axe can cut even the most powerful warrior clean in half - a sight which emboldens the bearer's followers and horrifies his enemies in equal measure</Lore>
					<Description>This weapon has the Killing Blow special rule. In addition, if the bearer kills an enemy character in a challenge, he and any unit he leads are Unbreakable and cause Terror so long as he leads them</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Stonecrusher Mace</Name>
					<Points>65</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="3"/>
					<Rule>When rolling To Wound against war machines and chariots or buildings, the character's Strength is increased to 10</Rule>
					<Lore>A great blunt weapon with an iron beast-head at its tip, the Stonecrusher Mace has become a symbol of the Beastmen's eternal desire to unmake that which Man has made, and cast down his civilisation so that no stone is left standing upon another</Lore>
					<Description>Stonecrusher Mace confers +3 Strength. When rolling To Wound against war machines and chariots (including War Altars, War Shrines, Steam Tanks and Corpse Carts, and so on) or buildings, the character's Strength is increased to 10</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Mangelder</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Terror/>
					<Rule>Any model wounded by this character loses 1 point of Leadership for each Wound it suffers</Rule>
					<Lore>The Mangelder is a weapon dreaded by the enemies of the Beastmen the length and breadth of the Old World. It saps strength of mind as well as of body, and those few who survive wounds inflicted by the weapon rarely fight again</Lore>
					<Description>The bearer causes Terror. In addition, any model wounded by this weapon loses 1 point of Leadership for each Wound it suffers</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Hunting Spear</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Terror/>
					<Rule>Spear can be thrown with a range of 24", resolve each hit like a single bolt from a bolt thrower</Rule>
					<Lore>Originally crafted to fell the mighty Mammuts of the far north, this thick-hafted spear bears enchantments allowing it to penetrate metres of flesh and muscle, skewering the foe through-and-through</Lore>
					<Description>The Hunting Spear counts as a spear in close combat. It can be thrown with a range of 24". Resolve each hit like a single bolt from a bolt thrower (see the main rule book). Note that you may shoot after moving (but not marching) and 'stand and shoot' with the Hunting Spear</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Axes of Khorgor</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Terror/>
					<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
					<Reroll>ToHit</Reroll>
					<Lore>One of the greatest Champions of the Beastmen ever to walk the Old World was a vicious brute named Khorgor. A vile thing, it's said he butchered hundreds of Humans. So wanton was he in his killing, he decorated his horns with the entrails of the dead. Whilst a great warrior in his own right, he was aided by a pair of blasphemous axes that could hew through armour and flesh with ease. So powerful was he when armed with these axes, no other Beastman could stand against him. But as with all things, Khorgor passed from this world and ownership of these terrible weapons changed hands many times, moving from successor to successor</Lore>
					<Description>Requires two hands. The bearer gains +1 Attack and may re-roll any missed To Hit rolls in close combat</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Steel-Claws</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<Rule>Extra D3 Attacks (roll at the beginning of each round of close combat)</Rule>
					<Lore>Made from the broken shards of enchanted Elven weapons, the Steel-claws are a set of splintered blades that fit over the wearer's own talons</Lore>
					<Description>Requires two hands. The Steel-Claws confer an extra D3 Attacks to the wielder (roll at the beginning of each round of close combat). If a 6 is rolled when determining the number of attacks, all the bearer's attacks that round will ignore armour saves</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>The Brass Cleaver</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>Bonus attack against each of the models in base contact with the bearer</Rule>
					<Lore>The Brass Cleaver is said to be an artefect from another realm. Ancient and terrible, its outline blurs with a barely restrained thirst for carnage</Lore>
					<Description>The Brass Cleaver confers a single bonus attack against each of the models in base contact with the bearer. In a challenge it confers one bonus attack and no more</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Everbleed</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Every time an enemy model suffers an unsaved wound from this weapon, roll a D6: on the result of a 6, the enemy loses an additional wound, with no saves of any kind allowed, and you must roll again</Rule>
					<Lore>Also known as Warrior's Bane, the much-feared blade Everbleed bares a potent blood magick. Even a slight cut will erupt into a geyser of gore that will not heal</Lore>
					<Description>Every time an enemy model suffers an unsaved wound from this weapon, roll a D6. On the result of a 6, the enemy loses an additional wound, with no saves of any kind allowed, and you must roll again. Keep on rolling as long as the result is a 6</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</MagicWeapons>
			<MagicArmours>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Blade-Blunter Armour</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Rule>At the end of each round of close combat, roll a D6 for each magic weapon that hit the wearer of the armour: on the result of a 2+, the enemy item loses its special rules and ceases to count as a magic weapon</Rule>
					<Lore>The Blade-Blunter Armour is encrusted with a vivid patina of corrosion and decay, cursed by a Bray-Shaman so that it spread to any blade that it strikes. Even the keenest weapon is blunted, dulled or shattered upon striking the armour</Lore>
					<Description>Heavy armour. At the end of each round of close combat, roll a D6 for each magic weapon that hit the wearer of the armour. On the result of a 2+, the enemy item loses its special rules and ceases to count as a magic weapon. Instead it will count as a normal weapon of its type for the remainder of the battle</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Trollhide</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Regeneration/>
					<Lore>The Trollhide confers some of the more gruesome abilities of its former occupant to the wearer</Lore>
					<Description>Light armour. The wearer gains the Regeneration rule</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Pelt of The Shadowgave</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Rule>All shooting attacks directed at the character or his unit are at -1 To Hit</Rule>
					<Rule>Spells that target the character or his unit deduct 2 from the casting roll</Rule>
					<Lore>The Pelt of the Shadowgave is shrouded in sorcerous tendrils of darkness that gather darkness to both the wearer and those Beastmen that walk in his dark-shrouded footsteps</Lore>
					<Description>Light armour. All shooting attacks directed at the bearer or his unit are at -1 To Hit. Spells that target the bearer or his unit deduct 2 from the casting roll</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Blackened Plate</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Rule>2+ Ward save against all flaming attacks</Rule>
					<Rule>Models in any unit that he is with have a 4+ Ward save against flaming attacks</Rule>
					<Lore>This battered suit of ramshackle plate mail, the Blackened Plate, is blackened with the soot of burning palaces and temples. It is said that the wearer can walk through the fiercest conflagration unharmed</Lore>
					<Description>Heavy armour. The wearer of the Blackened Plate has a 2+ Ward save against all flaming attacks. Models in any unit that he is with have a 4+ Ward save against such attacks</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Ramhorn Helm</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Rule>For every armour save he passes, the character may immediately make a bonus attack at his basic Strength</Rule>
					<Description>6+ armour save. This may be combined with other armour as normal. For every armour save he passes, the bearer may immediately make a bonus attack at his basic Strength</Description>
				</Additional>
			</MagicArmours>
			<EnchantedItems>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Shard of The Herdstone</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>After deployment zones have been agreed, but before the armies have been deployed, place an appropriate terrain piece to represent the herdstone in your deployment zone: at the start of your Magic phase each friendly Wizard within 6" of the herdstone generates an additional power dice</Rule>
					<Description>After deployment zones have been agreed, but before the armies have been deployed, place an appropriate terrain piece to represent the herdstone in your deployment zone. At the start of your Magic phase each friendly Wizard within 6" of the herdstone generates an additional power dice</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Horn of The Great Hunt</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Bound Spell, Power Level 3, it counts as the Bestial Surge spell, except that every friendly Beastman unit within 36" is affected</Rule>
					<Description>Bound Spell. Power Level 3. It counts as the Bestial Surge spell, except that every friendly Beastman unit within 36" is affected</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Horn of The First Beast</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>All Beastmen units within 36" can re-roll failed Primal Fury tests</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Stone of Spite</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, Power Level 5, one use only: every Arcane Item within 18" immediately explodes in the hands of its bearer (friend and foe), each bearer of an Arcane Item within range suffers D6 Strength 4 hits per item</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. Bound spell. Power Level 5. Every Arcane Item within 18" immediately explodes in the hands of its bearer (friend and foe). Each bearer of an Arcane Item within range suffers D6 Strength 4 hits per item. The items are immediately destroyed</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Skin of Man</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Scout/>
					<Description>The bearer of the Skin of Man has the Scout ability</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Cacophonous Dirge</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>Enemy musicians fighting in the same combat as the character have no effect.</Rule>
					<Description>Enemy musicians fighting in the same combat as the bearer have no effect</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</EnchantedItems>
			<Talismans>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Eye of Night</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<MagicResistance Val="2"/>
					<Rule>If an enemy Wizard within 24" attempts to cast a spell from the Lore of Life, the Lore of Heavens or the Lore of Light and suffers a miscast, you may force them to re-roll the result on the Miscast table</Rule>
					<Description>The Eye of Night grants the bearer Magic Resistance (2). In addition, if an enemy Wizard within 24" attempts to cast a spell from the Lore of Life, the Lore of Heavens or the Lore of Light and suffers a miscast, you may force them to re-roll the result on the Miscast table</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Chalice of Dark Rain</Name>
					<Points>40</Points>
					<Rule>Once per game, for the rest of the phase, all enemy missile units are at -1 To Hit, weapons or attacks that do not use Ballistic Skill may only fire on the roll of a 4+</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. At the beginning of the enemy Shooting phase, the bearer can summon a storm of mud and worms with which to blind his enemies. For the rest of the phase, all enemy missile units are at -1 To Hit. Weapons or attacks that do not use Ballistic Skill may only fire on the roll of a 4+</Description>
				</Additional>
			</Talismans>
			<Arcanes Name="Arcane items">
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Skull of Rarkos</Name>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<Rule>All friendly Beastman Wizards within 6" (including the character himself) add 1 to their casting results</Rule>
					<Description>All friendly Beastman Wizards within 6" (including the bearer himself) add 1 to their casting results</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Staff of Darkoth</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, Power Level 3, Viletide spell</Rule>
					<Description>Bound spell. Power Level 3. This item casts the Viletide spell</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Hagtree Fetish</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>Choose an enemy unit within 24" at the start of each Magic phase: any failed To Wound rolls made during the Magic phase against that unit may be re-rolled</Rule>
					<Description>Choose an enemy unit within 24" at the start of each Magic phase. Any failed To Wound rolls made during the Magic phase against that unit may be re-rolled</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Jagged Dagger</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Rule>Each model kept to the side in such a manner may be 'expended' in the Magic phase to allow the character to roll an additional power dice</Rule>
					<Description>Each model kept to the side in such a manner may be 'expended' in the Magic phase to allow the bearer to roll an additional power dice</Description>
				</Arcane>
			</Arcanes>
			<MagicBanners>
				<Banner>
					<Name>The Beast Banner</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<AddToStrength Val="1"/>
					<Rule>Unit have a +1 bonus to Strength</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer and any unit he has joined have a +1 bonus to their Strength</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Totem of Rust</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>All units in base contact with the unit, including the unit itself, treat their armour saves as two worse than it actually is instead</Rule>
					<Description>All units in base contact with the unit carrying the totem, including the unit itself, treat their armour saves as two worse than it actually is instead. This does not affect Scaly Skin saves!</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Manbane Standard</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>All enemy units within 6" suffer -1 to their Leadership characteristic</Rule>
					<Description>All enemy units within 6" of the Manbane Standard suffer -1 to their Leadership characteristic</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>The Banner of Outrage</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>Automatically passes Primal Fury tests</Rule>
					<Rule>Enemy units Hate the unit</Rule>
					<Description>The bearer's unit automatically passes Primal Fury tests (there is no need to roll). Enemy units Hate the bearer's unit</Description>
				</Banner>
			</MagicBanners>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Khazrak</Name>
				<Points>270</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Khazrak has plagued the Drakwald region for several years, descending without warning and then slipping away into the shadows once more. Khazrak has a unique ability to control and harness the unruly spirit of the herd and devise simple but effective battle plans. He is unlike most Beastmen, with a patient and cunning mind at odds with the normal headstrong nature of his kind. Khazrak's warband roams the Drakwald, terrorising the townships and roads, and never before has a Beastman leader proven so elusive to retribution. No one is spared in Khazrak's attacks, his superbly trained Warhounds chasing down the few who manage to escape the warherd itself.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='7' BS='1' S='5' T='5' W='3' I='5' A='4' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<Original>All units using the Beastman Ambush special rule in the same army as Khazrak may choose to re-roll the dice to see how and when they enter play</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Scourge</Name>
						<Rule>Instead of making normal attacks, Khazrak may choose to use his whip: in this case he has a number of attacks equal to the number of models in the front rank of one enemy unit that Khazrak is in base contact with, these attacks are distributed as per shooting</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>The Dark Mail</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="2"/>
						<Rule>The Dark Mail negates the power of any magic or runic weapons carried by models in base contact - treat them as ordinary non-magical weapons of their type</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Gorthor</Name>
				<Points>350</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Mount>Tuskgor Chariot</Mount>
				<Description>Gorthor was the greatest Beastlord ever to have lived. With strength of arm and animal cunning, he united all the tribes of the Middle Mountains. His, the largest horde of beasts ever seen, ravaged the Empire almost beyond recovery killing millions of Men and bringing two entire provinces to their knees. Gorthor claimed that the Dark Gods had selected him as their emissary. Though he had no true magical powers, he had something of the shaman about him, often being visited by nightmare visions of the future. Such was his fervour in battle that he was sometimes cloaked by coronas of dark energy, which protected him or struck out at his foes, a sure sign to other Beastmen that the gods truly favoured him.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='7' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='3' I='5' A='5' Ld='9' AS='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<ManBane/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Chariot</Rule>
						<Rule>At the start of each friendly Magic phase randomly generate a spell from the Lore of Death: Gorthor may use this spell during this Magic phase as a Bound Spell, with a Power Level equal to half the casting value of the spell, rounding up</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Impaler</Name>
						<KillingBlow/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Skull of Mugrar</Name>
						<Rule>When rolling for the chariot's impact hits, the Skull of Mugrar allows an extra dice to be rolled, and the highest result to be chosen</Rule>
					</Armour>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Cloak of the Beastlord</Name>
						<Rule>If Gorthor is the Army General, the range at which friendly units may use his Leadership characteristic is 18"</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Mount Name="Razorgor Chariot" Points="65"/>
				</Options>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Malagor</Name>
				<Points>200</Points>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Where Malagor treads, mayhem and destruction follow. The Beastmen believe that he is the doom of Mankind personified. A powerful Bray-Shaman, it is Malagor's whisperings that steer the course of the entire Beastmen race. The sight alone of Malagor has caused stout defenders to abandon otherwise impregnable walls and the mightiest of warriors to fall to their knees in abject defeat.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fly/>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Enemy units within 6" of Malagor may not use their General's Leadership, unless he is actually in the unit</Rule>
						<Rule>For every spell Malagor casts that is not dispelled he gets a cumulative +1 on subsequent casting attempts for the rest of the Magic phase</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Icons of Vilification</Name>
						<Rule>When making their Primal Fury tests, all friendly units within 6" of Malagor will become Frenzied on any roll of a double, as long as they have passed the test</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Taurox</Name>
				<Points>335</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Known as the Brass Bull, Taurox is a monstrous engine of destruction, formed of living brass in the shape of a terrible Doombull, dedicated solely to the spilling of blood in Khorne's name.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='3' S='6' T='6' W='5' I='5' A='6' Ld='8' AS='1'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<ImpactHit Val="D3+1"/>
					<Bloodgreed/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Any unit accompanied is also subject to Frenzy, but not to the Primal Fury rule</Rule>
						<Rule>If an enemy attack rolls a '6' To Hit and then a '6' To Wound then Taurox will be slain outright if he fails his saving throw</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Rune-tortured Axes</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<Rule>Flaming Attacks</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Beastlord</Name>
				<Points>145</Points>
				<Description>The Beastlords of the brayherds are hairy, muscle bound brutes possessed of a raw and savage might. Upon the battlefield a Beastlord is a force of untold destruction, gouging and butchering with horn, blade and claw. Their thick, hairy skulls are crowned with magnificent sets of horns as sharp and hard as any blade, and their robust and heavily-thewed bodies are covered with scar tissue and crudely rendered tattoos.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='3' S='5' T='4' W='3' I='5' A='4' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<ManBane/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="12" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="8" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<LightArmour Points="3" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
					<Mount Name="Tuskgor Chariot" Points="80"/>
					<Mount Name="Razorgor Chariot" Points="145"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Doombull</Name>
				<Points>235</Points>
				<Description>Doombulls are the strongest and most ferocious of their kind, towering bull-headed and cloven-hoofed beasts almost as broad as they are tall. Consumed by bloodgreed, Doombulls lay waste to their prey in an orgy of slaughter, maiming everything within reach of their gargantuan axes.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='3' S='6' T='5' W='5' I='5' A='5' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<ImpactHit Val="D3"/>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<Bloodgreed/>
					<Original>Any unit accompanied is also subject to Frenzy, but not to the Primal Fury rule</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="15" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="8" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<LightArmour Points="6" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="12" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="6"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Great Bray-shaman</Name>
				<Points>200</Points>
				<Wizard>3</Wizard>
				<Image>GreatBrayShaman</Image>
				<Description>Great Bray-Shamans are the greatest practitioners of magic within a Bray-herd. When the Beastmen go to war, the Great Bray-Shamans wield their powers to wreak terrible devastation upon the foe, their coruscating magic transforming soldiers into hideous new forms, summoning the creatures of the forest, both large and small, to bite and rend, or driving enemy mounts to buck their riders to the ground, to gore and trample their masters.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Wizard"/>
					<PrimalFury/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="4" Points="35"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="4"/>
					<Mount Name="Tuskgor Chariot" Points="80"/>
					<Mount Name="Razorgor Chariot" Points="145"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Braystaff</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Morghur</Name>
				<Points>280</Points>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Born almost three centuries ago, the creature known as Morghur was far from a human child. With tooth and horn, he ripped his mother apart in his gory entrance to the world, while her features mutated horribly. Her distraught husband reached forwards to strangle the twisted abomination, yet as his hands touched the foul creature, his body also was wracked with hideous mutation.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='3' S='4' T='5' W='2' I='4' A='4' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Cannot be harmed in any way by missile attacks or spells, unless the model which is the source of the attack is within 12" of him</Rule>
						<Rule>At the beginning of each round of close combat, all enemy models in base contact take a S3 hit with no armour save allowed</Rule>
						<Rule>At the beginning of your Magic phase, you must remove a friendly model within 12" from play, then roll a D6: on the roll of a 3+ you may place a Chaos Spawn within 3" of the spot vacated, provided there is space, and you have the appropriate model available</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Slugtongue</Name>
				<Points>190</Points>
				<Wizard>2</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Molokh Slugtongue, the Famine-Fiend, is a potent verbal sorcerer that specializes in turning lands barren to cause mass famine.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='2' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Regeneration/>
					<PoisonAttack/>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<Original>Immediately after deployment, each enemy unit within 36" must roll once on the table of Curse of the Famine-fiend</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Braystaff</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Moonclaw</Name>
				<Points>200</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Son of Morrslieb - an exceptionally hideous and insane Beastman born from an egg composed of warpstone from the chaos moon Morrslieb.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='2' I='3' A='3' Ld='7'/>
				<Options>
					<Mount Name="Umbralok" Points="35"/>
				</Options>
				<SpecialRules>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<MagicResistance Val="2"/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Every unit, friend or foe, within 12" of Moonclaw at the start of their turn must take a Stupidity test</Rule>
						<Rule>At the beginning of the game, secretly roll a D3 and record the number, in the turn that corresponds to this number, Morrslieb is full: for the entire duration of that turn Moonclaw has a +2 bonus to his casting rolls, he may make D3 shooting attacks resolved as if he were a stone thrower for that turn only, any results of a misfire cause a single wound upon Moonclaw that cannot be saved by any means</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Braystaff</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Wargor</Name>
				<Points>85</Points>
				<Description>Wargors are the leaders of the warherds, but they give no regard to the concerns of their tribe. They care not how their underlings are fed or how disputes are settled. The only thing the Wargors concern themselves with is battle. Day and night they brood and plot the myriad ways they will enact their race's hatred of Man, the violence they will wreak upon his flesh and the defilement they will heap upon his temples.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='3' S='4' T='5' W='2' I='4' A='3' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<ManBane/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<LightArmour Points="2" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25" Dependencies="Great axe, Additional weapon, Spear, Shield"/>
					<Mount Name="Tuskgor Chariot" Points="80"/>
					<Mount Name="Razorgor Chariot" Points="145"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Gorebull</Name>
				<Points>160</Points>
				<Description>Gorebulls are a much lesser yet not less ferocious leader of the Minotaur tribes. They are towering figures clad in large armour and wield hefty axes from which they could carve a path through the enemy and feast upon their flesh.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='5' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='4' I='4' A='4' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<ImpactHit Val="D3"/>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<Bloodgreed/>
					<Original>Any unit accompanied is also subject to Frenzy, but not to the Primal Fury rule</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<GreatWeapon Points="10" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="5" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<LightArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="8" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<Shield Points="4"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Bray-shaman</Name>
				<Points>75</Points>
				<Wizard>1</Wizard>
				<Image>BrayShaman</Image>
				<Description>Bray-Shamans are born into magic and they wield it with an instinctive ease. A miasma of fell sorcery surrounds then and, when their wrath is roused, reality itself becomes distorted and maimed.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='2' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Wizard"/>
					<PrimalFury/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="2" Points="35"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="2"/>
					<Mount Name="Tuskgor Chariot" Points="80"/>
					<Mount Name="Razorgor Chariot" Points="145"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Braystaff</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Tuskgor</Name>
				<Profile M='7' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='0' W='0' I='2' A='1' Ld='0'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Flail/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Umbralok</Name>
				<Profile M='7' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='3' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Flail/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Tuskgor Chariot</Name>
				<Chariot>2</Chariot>
				<Mount>Tuskgor</Mount>
				<Profile M='7' WS='4' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='4' I='3' A='2' Ld='7' AS='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ImpactHit Val="D6+1"/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Razorgor</Name>
				<Profile M='7' WS='3' BS='0' S='5' T='0' W='0' I='2' A='1' Ld='0'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Razorgor Chariot</Name>
				<Chariot>2</Chariot>
				<Mount>Razorgor</Mount>
				<Profile M='7' WS='4' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='2' Ld='7' AS='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<ImpactHit Val="D6+1"/>
					<Original>Thunderous Charge</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Gor herd</Name>
				<Points>7</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Gors form the great mass of the brayherds. Their appearance varies but all combine bestial features with those of a man. They have the savage fangs of a wolf and muscular bodies both well suited to enacting the violence and warfare that they crave. To face a horde of Gors is to face anarchy and mayhem. Rowdy and undisciplined, they bray, bark and bawl an unceasing cacophony that fills the hearts of Men with dread.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='3' S='3' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<BeastmanAmbush/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon PointsPerModel="1" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Foe-render"/>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Ungor herd</Name>
				<Points>5</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Ungors are more dexterous than Gors and possessed of a wiry strength that makes them more than a match for most Men. They live to murder and despoil all that is wholesome and are extremely cruel and spiteful creatures. Ungors take to the field in large herds, arming themselves with stout spears with which to impale their prey, and crude shields to protect their grotesque bodies.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<BeastmanAmbush/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Spear PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Command>
						<Option>
							<Name>Halfhorn</Name>
							<Dependency/>
							<Command/>
							<Points>6</Points>
						</Option>
						<Option>
							<Name>Ungrol Four-Horn</Name>
							<Dependency/>
							<Command/>
							<OnlyOneInArmy/>
							<Points>75</Points>
						</Option>
						<Musician Points="3"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="6"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Ungor raiders</Name>
				<Points>6</Points>
				<Size>5-10</Size>
				<Description>Ungor Raiders are those Ungors tasked with the role of hunting out enemies for the warherds to prey upon. They have knowledge of the wilderness that is unsurpassed by even the most intelligent Gor, and it is they who sow the seeds of mayhem that soon blossom into full-blown destruction as the rest of the warherd falls upon their victims.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<BeastmanAmbush/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<ShortBow/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="6" Name="Halfhorn"/>
						<Musician Points="3"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Tuskgor Chariot</Name>
				<Points>80</Points>
				<Chariot>2</Chariot>
				<Mount>Tuskgor</Mount>
				<Description>The chariots of the Beastmen are ramshackle constructions, built from heavy pieces of lumbar scavenged from the ruins of Man's buildings. Drawn by Tuskgors, whose brute strength and ferocity far outmatch that of mere horses, a Beastmen chariot inflicts terrible damage as it charges into the foe.</Description>
				<Profile M='7' WS='4' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='4' I='3' A='2' Ld='7' AS='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ImpactHit Val="D6+1"/>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<Original>Chariot</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<Spear/>
				</Equipments>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Chaos Warhounds</Name>
				<Points>6</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Brutish and bloodthirsty beasts, the Warhounds of Chaos are tireless hunters built of little more than muscle and fang. On the field of battle, the Beastmen release these feral beasts to intercept the forward elements of the enemy army. Packs of Chaos Warhounds will hunt down and pounce upon enemy skirmishers and scouts, bearing them to the ground and ripping them to pieces in their desperate desire to kill.</Description>
				<Profile M='7' WS='4' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<NoCoreSlot/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<PoisonedAttacks PointsPerModel="3"/>
					<ScalySkin PointsPerModel="1"/>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Minotaurs</Name>
				<Points>55</Points>
				<Size>3+</Size>
				<Description>Minotaurs, also known as Bullgors, are massive bull-headed monstrosities that constantly hunger for blood and meat. Twice the height of a man and substantially more muscular, their horns can eviscerate with a single thrust. When called to war, Minotaurs charge with a thundering impact and hack apart their hapless victims with formidable weapons.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='4' BS='3' S='5' T='4' W='3' I='3' A='3' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<ImpactHit Val="1"/>
					<Bloodgreed/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>				
					<Shield PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<AdditionalWeapon PointsPerModel="4" Dependency="Weapon"/>
					<GreatWeapon PointsPerModel="8" Dependency="Weapon"/>				
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="20" Name="Bloodkine" Magic="Type: Hero, Points: 25"/>
						<Musician Points="10"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="20"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Centigor</Name>
				<Points>25</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Description>Centigors are drunken, jealous creatures and carry out extreme acts of cruelty and violence on the battlefield. Each Centigor carries either a crude spear or horn, and wears limited amounts of chainmail and cloth, while their shields and decorations display both skull and chaos motifs. Rising up from clawed hooves, their muscular torsos lead to a cruel-looking head, from which protrudes large, ribbed horns.</Description>
				<Profile M='8' WS='4' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='2' A='2' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<Original>Drunken</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Spear/>
					<LightArmour/>
					<Shield/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<ThrowingAxes PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<GreatWeaponSpecific PointsPerModel="2"/>
					<Command>
						<Option>
							<Name>Gorehoof</Name>
							<Dependency/>
							<Command/>
							<Points>14</Points>
						</Option>
						<Option>
							<Name>Ghorros Warhoof</Name>
							<Dependency/>
							<Command/>
							<OnlyOneInArmy/>
							<Points>155</Points>
						</Option>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Harpies</Name>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Size>5-10</Size>
				<Description>Upon the thermals of the sacrificial pyres soar the Harpies - winged beasts with a savage beauty. They are creatures of cruel temperament, that is for sure, for flocks of Harpies delight in tormenting their victims and feast upon raw flesh.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='2' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Claws</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Scout PointsPerModel="3"/>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Bestigor herd</Name>
				<Points>12</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Description>Bestigor are the strongest and meanest of all the brayherd footsoldiers, and are prone to acts of excessive violence. In battle Bestigors form a solid, armoured mass of muscle and iron that charges forward, huge axes levelled, ready to hew the foe limb from limb and trample his broken body beneath their unshod hooves.</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='3' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='7'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<Original>Despoilers</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Gouge-horn" Magic="Type: Hero, Points: 25"/>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Razorgor Chariot</Name>
				<Points>145</Points>
				<Chariot>2</Chariot>
				<Mount>Razorgor</Mount>
				<Description>Razorgor Chariots are a much larger and far more hard-punching variant of the more common Tuskgor Chariot, but instead of having two Tuskgors pull the chariot, one massive Razorgor is instead. Such is the size of these monsters that few can truly survive a charge from even just a single of these beasts on the open battlefield.</Description>
				<Profile M='7' WS='4' BS='3' S='5' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='2' Ld='7' AS='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<ImpactHit Val="D6+1"/>
					<PrimalFury/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Chariot</Rule>
						<Rule>Thunderous Charge</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<Spear/>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Razorgor herd</Name>
				<Points>55</Points>
				<Description>Razorgor are massive cousins of the Tuskgors, mountains of muscle and hair that are deadly in the extreme. Such is a Razorgor's appetite and fearsome metabolism that they are able to gobble down a knight in full plate mail and his barded horse in a matter of seconds.</Description>
				<Profile M='7' WS='3' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='3' I='2' A='4' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Original>Thunderous Charge</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Tusks, hooves and a bad attitude</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Cygor</Name>
				<Points>275</Points>
				<Description>Cygors are distant cousins of the Minotaurs, but they have diverged significantly from their kin. Where once they could see the mortal world with two eyes, they can now only see the swirling Winds of Chaos with one.</Description>
				<Profile M='7' WS='2' BS='1' S='6' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='5' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Stubborn/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<MagicResistance Val="2"/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>When fighting enemy Wizards, models with any sort of magic item or magical attacks, Undead, or creatures with a ward save, the Cygor may re-roll any failed To Hit rolls</Rule>
						<Rule>Hurl Attack</Rule>
						<Rule>Enemy Wizards within 24" of one or more Cygors must take a Leadership test at the beginning of the Magic phase, if the test is failed any spell he fails to cast this Magic phase will result in a miscast</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Massively over-sized claws and horns</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Chorgon</Name>
				<Points>275</Points>
				<Description>Ghorgons are the huge, four-armed, ox-headed monsters used by the Beastmen herds. They have evolved from those Minotaurs, whose extreme overconsumption of tainted flesh triggered rapid growth and extreme mutation. As such, they now tower above the Gor Herds, sprouting a line of rigid spikes in the back and an extra pair of arms, ending in bone blades instead of true hands.</Description>
				<Profile M='7' WS='4' BS='0' S='6' T='6' W='6' I='3' A='6' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<Frenzy/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Bloodgreed/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>May forego all of its normal attacks and instead make a single special attack at an Initiative of 1: this attack has the Killing Blow ability, but To Wound rolls of a 4, 5 or 6 act as Killing Blow attacks, instead of just rolls of 6</Rule>
						<Rule>Each time a Ghorgon causes a Killing Blow with its Swallow Whole ability, it regains D3 Wounds that it has lost earlier in the battle</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Cleaver-limbs</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Chaos Spawn</Name>
				<Points>55</Points>
				<Description>Chaos Spawn are creatures which have become so mutated through their servitude to Chaos they have devolved into twisted and insane abominations. Those seeking immortality and power through Daemonhood face the constant possibility of being reduced to Chaos Spawn, either by accumulating too many mutations or being cast aside by their Chaos patrons as unworthy.</Description>
				<Profile M='2D6' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='5' W='3' I='2' A='D6+1' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Flailing Appendages</Rule>
						<Rule>Lurching Horror</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Tentacles, claws and teeth</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Giant</Name>
				<Points>225</Points>
				<Description>Bellowing primitive warcries from maws crammed with rotten, jagged fangs, the Chaos Giant tribes lumber to war. Corrupted by the hideous powers they worship, these beings are twisted perversions of their former selves, monsters dedicated to killing for Chaos.</Description>
				<Profile M='6' WS='3' BS='3' S='6' T='5' W='6' I='3' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<Stubborn/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Giant/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Fall Over</Rule>
						<Rule>Giant Special Attacks</Rule>
						<Rule>Longshanks</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Large club and bad breath</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Jabberslythe</Name>
				<Points>275</Points>
				<Description>Jabberslythes are some of the most ancient creatures of the world, and are certainly the most vile. They are an unwholesome union of toad, sludge-drake and insect, a creature so unearthly and grotesque that even the clearest of nature's pools will never reflect that abomination. Sentient creatures fare even worse, with many humans known to die of sheer shock or madness that the appearance of this creature invariably induces.</Description>
				<Profile M='8' WS='4' BS='4' S='5' T='5' W='5' I='3' A='5' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<PoisonAttack/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Fly/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Each enemy unit within 12" of one or more Jabberslythes at the beginning of the Beastmen Magic phase must take a Leadership test: for every point by which a unit fails its test, it suffers a wound with no armour saves allowed - some of its members have gone irrevocably insane!</Rule>
						<Rule>Slythey Tongue</Rule>
						<Rule>For every wound caused on a Jabberslythe in close combat, the attacking unit immediately suffers a S5 hit, randomised as shooting</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Biting jaw and catching claw</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>