<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArmyBook>
	<Introduction>
		<Info>
			<Army>Dark Elves</Army>
			<Edition>6</Edition>
			<Released>2001</Released>
			<Authors>Gav Thorpe, Space McQuirk and Tuomas Pirinen</Authors>
			<Description>The Dark Elves, or the Druchii as they call themselves in their own tongue, also known as the Naggarothi or the "Dark Ones", are one of the most ancient, powerful, and certainly the most sadistic of the three Elven civilisations of the world.\n\nIn the bleak, chilly lands of the continent of Naggaroth in the New World lies the Dark Elven kingdoms of the Witch King Malekith, a realm born from the depths of malice and hate, a kingdom that seeks nothing more than to despoil a world its people believe loathes their existence. With malevolent eyes, the Dark Elves watch this dying world, knowing it is their birthright to rule all that they survey and those that live upon it are born to do nothing more than to grovel at their feet.\n\nThe Druchii are raiders, slavers and heartless reavers of the first degree, their every whim being nothing more than to sow misery and pain to all that oppose them, for misery and pain is the very lifeblood of their existence. Thus do their Black Arks and Corsair Fleets ply the great waters of the world, raiding and enslaving all before them as a tribute to their own avaricious desires</Description>
		</Info>
		<Styles>
			<Images>
				<Cover>DarkElves6ed.png</Cover>
				<Symbol>DarkElves.png</Symbol>
				<Illustration>DarkElves6ed.jpg</Illustration>
				<Units>6edition</Units>
			</Images>
			<Colors>
				<Front>9c228a</Front>
				<Back>cd3cb7</Back>
				<Grid>f2eaf2</Grid>
				<Tooltip>c9b6d1</Tooltip>
				<Upgraded>e18ad3, d762c5, d24fbe</Upgraded>
			</Colors>
			<MagicItems>Sorcerous Items</MagicItems>
		</Styles>
		<Internal>DarkElves</Internal>
		<Magic>
			<Name>Dark Magic</Name>
			<Options>Lore of Shadow, Death</Options>
			<Magic>
				<Spell Name="Nagaelythe the Chillwind" Cast="5"/>
				<Spell Name="Doombolt of Kharaidon" Cast="6"/>
				<Spell Name="Chroesh Word of Pain" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Anchan-Rogar the Soul Stealer" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Lamehk's Dominion" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Arnizipal's Black Horror" Cast="12"/>
			</Magic>
			<Enemy>High Elves, High Magic Spells</Enemy>
			<Dispell>
				<Spell Name="Walk Between Worlds" Cast="6"/>
				<Spell Name="Curse of Arrow Attraction" Cast="8"/>
				<Spell Name="Fortune is Fickle" Cast="9"/>
				<Spell Name="Fury of Khaine" Cast="10"/>
				<Spell Name="Flame of the Phoenix" Cast="13"/>
				<Spell Name="Vaul's Unmaking" Cast="14"/>
			</Dispell>
		</Magic>
		<LocalSpecialRules>
			<HateHighElves/>
			<SectEnmity/>
			<NoxiousBreath/>
		</LocalSpecialRules>
		<LocalOption>
			<SeaDragonCloak Name="Sea Dragon Cloak">
				AddToArmour: 6
			</SeaDragonCloak>
			<RepeaterCrossbow/>
		</LocalOption>
	</Introduction>
	<Content>
		<Artefacts>
			<Group Name="Common magic items">
				<SwordOfStriking Points="30"/>
				<SwordOfBattle Points="25"/>
				<SwordOfMight Points="20"/>
				<BitingBlade Points="10"/>
				<EnchantedShield Points="10"/>
				<TalismanOfProtection Points="15"/>
				<StaffOfSorcery Points="50"/>
				<DispellScroll Points="25"/>
				<PowerStone Points="25"/>
				<WarBanner Points="25"/>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Magic weapons">
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Executioner's Axe</Name>
					<Only>Infantry</Only>
					<Points>80</Points>
					<Rule>Strength double that of his target's Toughness</Rule>
					<WoundOn Val="2"/>
					<HitLast/>
					<Description>When rolling to wound in close combat and for armour save modifier purposes, the wielder counts as having a Strength double that of his target's Toughness. However, the Executioner's Axe is two-handed and the wielder always strikes last except in the turn he the turn he charges</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Venom Sword</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Rule>Any model which loses a wound to the Venom Sword (after saves, etc) must roll equal to or under its Toughness on 2D6 or is automatically slain</Rule>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Blade of Ruin</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<NoArmour/>
					<Description>No armour saves may be taken against hits from the Sword of Ruin. Ward saves may be taken as normal</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Hydra Blade</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Rule>D3 additional attacks</Rule>
					<Description>A character wielding the Hydra Blade gains D3 additional attacks (roll each Close Combat phase the Hydra Blade is used)</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Crimson Death</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<StrengthTo Val="6"/>
					<Description>A model wielding Crimson Death always strikes with Strength 6. No other modifiers will ever reduce this. Requires two hands to use</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Lifetaker</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Rule>Crossbow hits on a 2+, may re-roll to wound</Rule>
					<Description>Lifetaker is treated like an ordinary repeater crossbow, with the following additional rules. Lifetaker always hits on 2+, regardless of To Hit modifiers. You may re-roll failed rolls to wound with Lifetaker. Remember that a dice can never be re-rolled more than once</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Web of Shadows</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Enemy automatically takes 2D6 Strength 3 hits, one use only</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. The character uses the Web of Shadows instead of making any normal attacks that round. When used, one model in base contact with the character automatically takes 2D6 Strength 3 hits. A character with a Web of Shadows may also take an ordinary close combat weapon (but not another magic weapon)</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Heartseeker</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Reroll>ToHit</Reroll>
					<Description>The character may re-roll all missed attacks with Heartseeker. Remember a dice can never be re-rolled more than once</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Chill Blade</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Any model wounded may not attack for the rest of that combat round</Rule>
					<Description>Any model wounded by a Chill Blade (after saves, etc) may not attack for the rest of that combat round</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Dark sword</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>Any model losing one or more wounds becomes subject to the rules for stupidity for the remainder of the battle</Rule>
					<Description>Any model losing one or more wounds (after saves, etc) to the Dark Sword becomes subject to the rules for stupidity for the remainder of the battle</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Magic armour">
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Living Death</Name>
					<Points>100</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<AddToToughness Val="1"/>
					<AddToWounds Val="1"/>
					<Description>The Armour of Living Death counts as heavy armour, giving a 5+ armour save, which can be combined with other armour as normal. In addition, the model has +1 Toughness and +1 Wound</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Eternal Servitude</Name>
					<Points>60</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Regeneration/>
					<Description>This light armour gives a basic 6+ save, which can be combined with other armour as normal. In addition, the wearer can regenerate</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Shield>
					<Name>Shield of Ghrond</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="6"/>
					<Rule>All hits the character suffers will be resolved with -1 Strength</Rule>
					<Description>The Shield of Ghrond is treated like a normal shield, and in addition all hits the character suffers will be resolved with -1 Strength</Description>
				</Shield>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Armour of Darkness</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<ArmourTo Val="2"/>
					<Description>This armour includers a shield and gives a save of 2+ which cannot be improved in any way</Description>
				</Armour>
				<Armour>
					<Name>Blood Armour</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
					<Rule>For every inflicted wound in close combat, armour save is improved by one point</Rule>
					<Description>Blood Armour is treated as a suit of normal heavy armour (5+ save) and can be combined with other armour as normal. For every unsaved wound the wearer inflicts, their save is improuved by 1 (to 4+ then 3+, etc) up to maximum of 1+</Description>
				</Armour>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Talismans">
				<Additional>
					<Name>Black Amulet</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Rule>If ward save test is passed, the attacking model suffers 1 wound instead (with no armour save allowed)</Rule>
					<Description>The wearer has a 5+ Ward save against close combat hits. If the wearer of the Black Amulet passes his Ward save then the attacking model suffers 1 wound instead (with no armour save allowed)</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Deathmask</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Terror/>
					<Description>The wearer of mask causes terror</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Crown of Black Iron</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Rule>Completely immune to the effects of Light Magic and High Magic</Rule>
					<Description>The character has a 5+ Ward save. In addition to this, the wearer is completely immune to the effects of Light Magic and High Magic spells. Note that this is not a Dispel and thus other models (excluding the character's mount) may be affected by High Magic and Light Magic.</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Seal of Ghrond</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<AddToDispell Val="1"/>
					<Description>The seal of Ghrond adds one dice to the Dispel dice pool of the army</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Ring of Hotek</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>Any magic user (friend or foe) attempting to cast a spell within 6" of the wearer will miscast on the roll of any double</Rule>
					<Description>Any magic user (friend or foe) attempting to cast a spell within 6" of the wearer will miscast on the roll of any double. If they roll a double 6 they cast the spell (with Irresistible Force) and then suffer a Miscast</Description>
				</Additional>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Enchanted items">
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rubric of Dark Dimensions</Name>
					<Points>50</Points>
					<Only>Infantry</Only>
					<Rule>Bound spell, power level 3, one use only: all enemy models in base contact must roll equal to or under their Strength on a D6 or be slain</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. Bound spell, power level 5. All enemy models in base contact with the bearer must roll equal to or under their Strength on a D6 (6 always fails) or be sucked into the dimension of Eternal Nightmares (and count as slain!)</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Ring of Darkness</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, power level 4, remains in play: attacks in close combat against the wearer require a 6 to hit</Rule>
					<Description>Attacks in close combat against the wearer require a 6 to hit regardless of Weapon Skills and modifiers. Remains in play</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Crystal of Midnight</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Bound spell, power level 3, one use only: enemy Wizard must pass a Leadership test on 3D6 otherwise they forget one randomly spell</Rule>
					<Description>One use only. Nominate a Wizard anywhere on the table. The Wizard must pass a Leadership test on 3D6 otherwise he forgets one randomly determined spell for the rest of the battle</Description>
				</Additional>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Arcane items">
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Soulstone</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Rule>Immune to the effects of her first Miscast</Rule>
					<Description>A Soulstone makes the Sorceress immune to the effects of her first Miscast. Note that a Miscast spell still fails regardless of the actual dice score rolled</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Black Staff</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<Rule>There is no maximum number of Power dice to attempt a spell</Rule>
					<Description>There is no maximum number of Power dice the wielder can use to attempt a spell</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Darkstar Cloak</Name>
					<Points>20</Points>
					<AddToCast Val="1"/>
					<Description>The cloak gives the Sorceress +1 power dice in each of her own Magic phase. Only she may use this extra dice</Description>
				</Arcane>
				<Arcane>
					<Name>Tome of Furion</Name>
					<Points>15</Points>
					<Rule>1 additional spell</Rule>
					<Description>The Tome of Furion grants its bearer one additional spell</Description>
				</Arcane>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Magic banner">
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of Nagarythe</Name>
					<Points>150</Points>
					<Unbreakable/>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="1"/>
					<Description>This standard adds +1 to the combat resolution of all units withn 6" and the unit carrying the banner is Unbreakable</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Hydra Banner</Name>
					<Points>80</Points>
					<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
					<Description>All models in the unit (including mounts) gain +1 Attack in the first round of any hand-to-hand combat</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Dread Banner</Name>
					<Points>75</Points>
					<Fear/>
					<Description>The unit carrying this standard causes fear</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Banner of Murder</Name>
					<Points>45</Points>
					<Rule>+D6" into its charge moves</Rule>
					<Description>The unit adds +D6" into its charge moves. Declare charges first and then roll. If the charge is failed the unit will move forward its normal failed charge distance</Description>
				</Banner>
				<Banner>
					<Name>Standard of Slaughter</Name>
					<Points>35</Points>
					<AddToCloseCombat Val="D3"/>
					<Description>The unit gains +D3 to its combat resolution the first time it charges</Description>
				</Banner>
			</Group>
			<Group Name="Gifts of Khaine">
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Manbane</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<Rule>Counts their Strength as one higher than their target's Toughness, unless their Strength would normally be more than this, up to a maximum of Strength 6</Rule>
					<Description>A character with a weapon coated with Manbane always counts their Strength as one higher than their target's Toughness, unless their Strength would normally be more than this, up to a maximum of Strength 6. In effect, this means that they almost always wound opponents on a roll of 3+. This modified Strength is also used to calculate armour save modifiers</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Black Lotus</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<Rule>For every Wound suffers a enemy model (after saves, etc) also lose 1 point from all of their other characteristics except Movement</Rule>
					<Description>For every Wound a model suffers from a weapon poisoned with Black Lotus (after saves, etc) they also lose 1 point from all of their other characteristics except Movement. This lasts for the rest of the battle</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Dark Venom</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<PoisonAttack/>
					<Description>The model is considered to have Poisoned Attacks</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Dance of Doom</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<AddToWard Val="5"/>
					<Description>The model has a 5+ Ward save</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Touch of Death</Name>
					<Points>30</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<Description>The model has the Killing Blow special ability</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Rune of Khaine</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
					<Rule>Must always pursue fleeing enemies</Rule>
					<Description>The Rune of Khaine grants +1 Attack to its bearer. A model marked with the Rune of Khaine must always pursue fleeing enemies</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Hand of Khaine</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<Rule>Any one model in base contact will lose one Attack</Rule>
					<Description>Any one model (chosen by a Dark Elf player) in base contact will lose one Attack. Against mounted models, the Dark Elf player must choose either the mount/monster or the rider. If the model has several types of attack (an extra bite, for example) the Dark Elf player chooses which type of attack is lost. Models which are immune to psychology are not affected by the Hand of Khaine</Description>
				</Weapon>
				<Additional>
					<Name>Witchbrew</Name>
					<Points>25</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<Rule>Enemy units cannot claim the +1 combat resolution bonuses for outnumbering, flank and rear attacks or higher ground</Rule>
					<Description>Hags only. The Hag and her unit drink the Witchbrew before the battle. Enemy units cannot claim the +1 combat resolution bonuses for outnumbering, flank and rear attacks or higher ground</Description>
				</Additional>
				<Weapon>
					<Name>Cry of War</Name>
					<Points>10</Points>
					<Only>Khainite</Only>
					<Rule>A unit charged character must pass a Leadership test or reduce their Weapon Skill by -1 for the duration of that Close Combat phase</Rule>
					<Description>A unit charged by a warrior with a Cry of War must pass a Leadership test or reduce their Weapon Skill by -1 (to a minimum of 1) for the duration of that Close Combat phase</Description>
				</Weapon>
			</Group>
		</Artefacts>
		<Heroes>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Malekith</Name>
				<Points>945</Points>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Character/>
				<Mount>Seraphon</Mount>
				<Description>Malekith, the Witch King of Naggaroth</Description>
				<Profile M='5' WS='8' BS='5' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='8' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<General/>
					<ImmuneToPsychology/>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Use Dark Magic</Rule>
						<Rule>If your army is led by Malekith, Black Guard are no longer a 0-1 choice - you may include as many units as you have Rare choices</Rule>
						<Rule>May re-roll missed close combat attacks against High Elves in any round of combat, not just the first round</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Destroyer</Name>
						<Rule>If Malekith hits an opponent with a magic weapon or with magic armour, instead of rolling to wound you may choose to destroy one item (opponent's choice)</Rule>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Hand of Khaine</Name>
						<StrengthTo Val="6"/>
						<NoArmour/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Armour of Midnight</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="5"/>
						<AddToWard Val="2"/>
						<NoMultiWounds/>
						<Rule>2+ Ward save against non-magical attacks</Rule>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Morathi</Name>
				<Points>470</Points>
				<Wizard>4</Wizard>
				<Mount>Dark Pegasus Sulephet</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Morathi, the Hag Sorceress</Description>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='6' A='3' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Original>
						<Rule>Always use Dark Magic, you may choose which four spells she has at the start of the battle</Rule>
						<Rule>Adds +2 to all of her casting rolls</Rule>
						<Rule>Any Witch Elves within 12" may use her Leadership value, as if she was their army General</Rule>
					</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Heartrender</Name>
						<KillingBlow/>
						<AddToStrength Val="2"/>
					</HandWeapon>
					<Arcane>
						<Name>Thousand and One Dark Blessing</Name>
						<AddToWard Val="4"/>
						<Rule>Magic Resistance (1)</Rule>
					</Arcane>
					<Arcane>
						<Name>Enchanting Beauty</Name>
						<Rule>Any enemy model in base contact with Morathi at the start of round of combat must pass a Leadership test or have their WS reduced to 1 for the duration of that round</Rule>
					</Arcane>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Malus Darkblade</Name>
				<Points>350</Points>
				<Mount>Spite</Mount>
				<Character/>
				<Description>Malus Darkblade, Scion of Hag Graef</Description>
				<Image>Malus</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='7' BS='5' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='8' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<Frenzy/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Warpsword of Khaine</Name>
						<NoArmour/>
						<Reroll>ToWound</Reroll>
					</HandWeapon>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Demon>
						<Name>Tz'arkan</Name>
						<AddToWeaponSkill Val="1"/>
						<AddToStrength Val="1"/>
						<AddToToughness Val="2"/>
						<AddToInitiative Val="2"/>
						<Rule>If Malus is in base contact with a friendly model and not in contact with the enemy in any close combat phase, roll a D6: on a 4+ Tz'arkan's murderous rage drives Malus to attack his allies</Rule>
					</Demon>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>Dark Elf Highborn</Name>
				<Points>125</Points>
				<Image>Highborn</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='7' BS='6' S='4' T='3' W='3' I='8' A='4' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Hero"/>
					<HateHighElves/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="6"/>
					<Halberd Points="6"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="6"/>
					<Lance Points="6" Only="Mount"/>
					<RepeaterCrossbow Points="15"/>
					<LightArmour Points="3" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="6" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<SeaDragonCloak Points="6"/>
					<Shield Points="3"/>
					<Mount Name="Cold One" Points="39"/>
					<Mount Name="Dark Steed" Points="18"/>
					<Mount Name="Dark Pegasus" Points="55"/>
					<Mount Name="Manticore" Points="190"/>
					<Mount Name="Black Dragon" Points="320"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Lord>
				<Name>High Sorceress</Name>
				<Points>225</Points>
				<Wizard>3</Wizard>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='3' I='5' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="100" Type="Wizard"/>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<SectEnmity/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="4" Points="40"/>
					<Mount Name="Dark Steed" Points="18"/>
					<Mount Name="Cold One" Points="39"/>
					<Mount Name="Dark Pegasus" Points="55"/>
					<Mount Name="Manticore" Points="190"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Lord>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Dark Elf Noble</Name>
				<Points>70</Points>
				<Image>Noble</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='6' BS='6' S='4' T='3' W='2' I='7' A='3' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<HateHighElves/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="4"/>
					<GreatWeapon Points="4"/>
					<Halberd Points="4"/>
					<Lance Points="4" Only="Mount"/>
					<RepeaterCrossbow Points="10"/>
					<LightArmour Points="2" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<HeavyArmour Points="4" Dependency="Armour"/>
					<SeaDragonCloak Points="6"/>
					<Shield Points="2"/>
					<Mount Name="Dark Steed" Points="12"/>
					<Mount Name="Cold One" Points="26"/>
					<Mount Name="Dark Pegasus" Points="55"/>
					<BattleStandardBearer Points="25"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Sorceress</Name>
				<Points>90</Points>
				<Wizard>3</Wizard>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Wizard"/>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<SectEnmity/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<Wizard Level="2" Points="40"/>
					<Mount Name="Dark Steed" Points="12"/>
					<Mount Name="Cold One" Points="26"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Beastmaster</Name>
				<Points>40</Points>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='2' I='6' A='2' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<MagicItems Points="25" Type="Hero"/>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<Original>Beastmaster</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="4"/>
					<Mount Name="Dark Pegasus" Points="55"/>
					<Mount Name="Cold One" Points="26"/>
					<Option>
						<Name>Manticore</Name>
						<Slots>Hero</Slots>
						<Points>190</Points>
						<Mount/>
					</Option>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>Whip</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
			<Hero>
				<Name>Assassin</Name>
				<Points>125</Points>
				<Group>Khainite</Group>
				<Homologue>Assassin</Homologue>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='6' WS='9' BS='9' S='4' T='3' W='2' I='10' A='3' Ld='10'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<NotALeader/>
					<MagicItems Points="50" Type="Hero"/>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<Original>Hidden</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Options>
					<AdditionalWeapon Points="4"/>
				</Options>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
			</Hero>
		</Heroes>
		<Mounts>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Dark Steed</Name>
				<Profile M='9' WS='3' BS='0' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='5'/>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Cold One</Name>
				<Profile M='7' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='1' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
					<Stupidity/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<ThickSkinned/>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Spite</Name>
				<Profile M='7' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='1' I='3' A='2' Ld='3'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fear/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<ThickSkinned/>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Dark Pegasus</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ChargeStrengthBonus Val="1"/>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Dark Pegasus Sulephet</Name>
				<Profile M='8' WS='3' BS='0' S='4' T='4' W='3' I='4' A='2' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<ChargeStrengthBonus Val="1"/>
					<Fly/>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Manticore</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='5' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='4' I='5' A='4' Ld='5'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Fly/>
					<Original>Uncontrollable</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Black Dragon</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='0' S='6' T='6' W='6' I='3' A='5' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<Fly/>
					<NoxiousBreath/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Scaly skin</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="3"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
			<Mount>
				<Name>Seraphon</Name>
				<Profile M='6' WS='6' BS='0' S='6' T='6' W='6' I='4' A='5' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<Slots>Hero</Slots>
					<Fly/>
					<NoxiousBreath/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Armour>
						<Name>Scaly skin</Name>
						<AddToArmour Val="3"/>
					</Armour>
				</Equipments>
			</Mount>
		</Mounts>
		<Units>
			<Core>
				<Name>Dark Elf Warriors</Name>
				<Points>9</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>Warriors</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HateHighElves/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Spear/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Shield PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Crossbow PointsPerModel="4"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10"/>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Lordling"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Corsairs</Name>
				<Points>10</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HateHighElves/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
					<LightArmour/>
					<SeaDragonCloak/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="5"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="10" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="10" Name="Reaver"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Core>
				<Name>Dark Riders</Name>
				<Points>18</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Dark Steed</Mount>
				<Image>DarkRider</Image>
				<Profile M='9' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<Original>Fast Cavalry</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<Spear/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Crossbow PointsPerModel="6"/>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14"/>
						<Champion Points="14" Name="Herald"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Core>
			<Special>
				<Name>Shades</Name>
				<Points>14</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Image>Shade</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='4' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Skirmishers/>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<Original>Scouts</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<RepeaterCrossbow/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<LightArmour PointsPerModel="1"/>
					<Option>
						<Name>Bloodshadde</Name>
						<Points>12</Points>
					</Option>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Witch Elves of Khaine</Name>
				<Group>Khainite</Group>
				<Points>13</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image>WitchElves</Image>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='6' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Frenzy/>
					<PoisonAttack/>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<Original>Devotees of Khaine</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<TwoHandsWeapons/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Hag" Magic="Type: Hero, Points: 25"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Cold One Chariot</Name>
				<Points>95</Points>
				<Chariot>2</Chariot>
				<Mount>Cold One</Mount>
				<Image/>
				<Homologue>ColdOneChariot</Homologue>
				<Profile M='7' WS='4' BS='4' S='4' T='5' W='4' I='5' A='1' Ld='9' AS='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Stupidity/>
					<Fear/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<ImpactHit Val="D6"/>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<Original>Chariot</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Crossbow Points="10"/>
					<Spear Points="2"/>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Cold One Knights</Name>
				<Points>29</Points>
				<Size>5+</Size>
				<Mount>Cold One</Mount>
				<Image>ColdOneKnight</Image>
				<Profile M='7' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Stupidity/>
					<Fear/>
					<HateHighElves/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Lance/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
					<Shield/>
					<ThickSkinned/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="9"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="18" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="18" Name="Dread Knight"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Executioners</Name>
				<Points>11</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='5' A='1' Ld='8'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<KillingBlow/>
					<HateHighElves/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<GreatWeapon/>
					<HandWeapon/>
					<LightArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="6"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="12" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 50"/>
						<Champion Points="12" Name="Draich-master"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Special>
			<Special>
				<Name>Harpies</Name>
				<Points>13</Points>
				<Size>5-20</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='4' WS='3' BS='3' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='4' A='1' Ld='6'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Fly/>
					<Original>Beasts</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<HandWeapon>
						<Name>Vicious claws and temperament</Name>
						<AddToAttacks Val="1"/>
					</HandWeapon>
				</Equipments>
			</Special>
			<Rare>
				<Name>War Hydra</Name>
				<Points>220</Points>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='6' WS='4' BS='0' S='5' T='5' W='6' I='2' A='7' Ld='6' AS='4'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Terror/>
					<LargeBase/>
					<LargeTarget/>
					<HateHighElves/>
					<Original>Breathe Fire</Original>
				</SpecialRules>
			</Rare>
			<Rare>
				<Name>Black Guard</Name>
				<Points>16</Points>
				<Size>10+</Size>
				<Singleton/>
				<Image/>
				<Profile M='5' WS='5' BS='4' S='3' T='3' W='1' I='6' A='1' Ld='9'/>
				<SpecialRules>
					<Stubborn/>
					<Hate/>
				</SpecialRules>
				<Equipments>
					<Halberd/>
					<HeavyArmour/>
				</Equipments>
				<Options>
					<Command>
						<Musician Points="7"/>
						<StandardBearer Points="14" Magic="Type: Unit, Points: 75"/>
						<Champion Points="14" Name="Master"/>
					</Command>
				</Options>
			</Rare>
		</Units>
	</Content>
</ArmyBook>